<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  Copyright (c) Koninklijke Philips N.V., 2018
  All rights are reserved. Reproduction or dissemination
  in whole or in part is prohibited without the prior written
  consent of the copyright holder.
  -->


<resources>
  <string name="BA_Add_Edit_Temp">Ajouter ou modifier la température </string>
  <string name="BA_AppFramework">AppFramework </string>
  <string name="BA_HSDP_login_not_available">Connexion HSDP indisponible</string>
  <string name="BA_Sync_Settings">Paramètres de synchronisation</string>
  <string name="RA_AboutScreen_Title">À propos</string>
  <string name="RA_About_App_Version">Version</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Description_New">[fr]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Menu_Title">À propos</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsDescription">[fr]\"Special offers, promotions and first hand information about new product releases.\nTailored for you!\n\nJoin 140.000 of your peers now!\"</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsTitle">[fr]What do we have to offer?</string>
  <string name="RA_Cancel">Annuler</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_AppInfra">[fr]AppInfra is the component\'s top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_Connectivity">[fr]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ConsumerCare">[fr]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_DataServices">[fr]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data: Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_InAppPurchase">[fr]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ProductRegistration">[fr]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UIToolkit">[fr]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UserRegistration">[fr]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization / social media specific credentials</string>
  <string name="RA_ConnectivityScreen_Title">Connectivité</string>
  <string name="RA_Done_Button_Text">Terminé</string>
  <string name="RA_Empty_Invalid_Data">Champ de données vide ou invalide</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Body_Text">Le texte grand format de la proposition spécifique se place dans le corps </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Header_Text">Le titre de la proposition spécifique se place ici </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Menu_Title">Accueil de l\'application mobile</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Title">Accueil de l\'application mobile</string>
  <string name="RA_Invalid_Param_Msg">Vous avez saisi ou sélectionné des valeurs de paramètre invalides. Veuillez sélectionner des valeurs de paramètre valides puis relancer.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Binary_Hosting_Consent">[fr]I allow Philips to store binary data</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Click_Stream_Hosting_Consent">[fr]I allow Philips to use my mobile application usage statistics</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Coaching_Consent">[fr]I allow Philips to use my data for Coaching purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Binary_Help_Text">[fr]The actual content of the binary consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream">J\'autorise Philips à recueillir les données de mon application pour aider au fonctionnement, à l\'amélioration et à la personnalisation de l\'application, pour l\'intégration avec les réseaux sociaux et l\'affichage de publicités et contenus pertinents.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream_Help_Text">Déclaration relative aux cookies\n\nCette application utilise Adobe Analytics, un service d\'analyse (« Adobe Analytics ») fourni par Adobe Systems Software Ireland Limited (« Adobe »). Adobe Analytics utilise des « cookies » ou techniques similaires, qui sont des fichiers texte placés dans votre application, afin d\'aider l\'application à analyser les modèles de trafic global au sein de l\'application. Lors de la transmission des informations générées par les cookies concernant l\'utilisation de l\'application à Adobe, l\'adresse IP est anonymisée avant géolocalisation et sera remplacée par une adresse IP générique avant stockage. Au nom de Philips, Adobe va utiliser ces informations pour évaluer votre utilisation de l\'application, compiler des rapports sur l\'activité de l\'application pour Philips et fournir d\'autres services relatifs à l\'activité et l\'utilisation de l\'application à Philips. Adobe n\'associera pas votre adresse IP avec toute autre donnée détenue par Adobe. Vous pouvez empêcher Adobe et Philips de recueillir et d\'utiliser des données (cookies et adresse IP) si vous choisissez de vous désinscrire après la fermeture de cet écran.\n</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Coaching_Help_Text">[fr]The actual content of the coaching consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Marketing_Help_Text">Suite à votre consentement, les entreprises du groupe Philips peuvent vous contacter à des fins publicitaires. Nous pouvons vous contacter par e-mail, SMS ou d\'autres médias numériques, par exemple les applications mobiles ou les réseaux sociaux. Afin d\'adapter les communications à vos préférences et à votre comportement, et afin de vous proposer une expérience la plus aboutie et la plus personnalisée possible, nous pouvons analyser et regrouper vos données personnelles. Ces données peuvent inclure : \n\nLes données que vous nous transmettez\nLes données que vous nous communiquez activement : nom, date de naissance ou âge, adresse e-mail, adresse postale, pays, sexe, numéro de téléphone, profil sur les réseaux sociaux.\n\nLes données obtenues suite à vos interactions avec Philips\nLes données concernant vos interactions et votre utilisation des médias numériques Philips, tels que les réseaux sociaux, les sites Web, les e-mails, les applications et les produits connectés. Ces données peuvent inclure : l\'adresse IP, les cookies, les informations sur l\'appareil, les communications sur lesquelles vous cliquez, votre emplacement et les sites Web que vous visitez\n\nPhilips vous offre la possibilité de retirer votre consentement à tout moment.\nPour en savoir plus, veuillez consulter la déclaration de confidentialité de Philips et la déclaration relative aux cookies de Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Moment_Help_Text">[fr]The actual content of the moment consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Research_Analytics_Help_Text">[fr]The actual content of the research and analytics consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Moment_Consent">[fr]I allow Philips to store my data in cloud</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Research_Analytics_Consent">[fr]I allow Philips to use my data for Research and Analytics purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_NO_Order_History">Historique de commande indisponible</string>
  <string name="RA_OK">OK</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Dismiss">[fr]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Shop_Text">[fr]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Support_Text">[fr]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions product informations and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Benefit_Text">Étendre votre garantie de 24 mois.\nBénéficier de 10 % de remise sur la boutique Philips.\nRecevoir gratuitement des accessoires</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Email_Text">Un e-mail contenant un contrat d\'extension de garantie vous a été envoyé</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Extentende_Warranty">Votre période de garantie a été prolongée jusqu\'à l\'année prochaine</string>
  <string name="RA_Philips_Shop_Menu_Title">Boutique Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_Product_Registration_Text">Enregistrez votre produit</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title">Recevoir des communications promotionnelles de la part de Philips en fonction de mes préférences et de mon comportement en ligne</string>
  <string name="RA_SettingsScreen_Title">Paramètres du compte</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Login">Connexion</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout">Déconnexion</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout_Alert">Êtes-vous sûr de vouloir vous déconnecter ?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_MyAccount">Mon compte</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_OrderHistory">Historique de commande</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Promo_Question_Text">Qu\'est-ce que cela signifie ?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Purchases">Achats</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Screen_Header_Title">Réglages</string>
  <string name="RA_Skip_Button_Text">Saut</string>
  <string name="RA_SplashScreen_Title">Applications mobiles</string>
  <string name="RA_SupportScreen_Title">Assistance</string>
  <string name="RA_Support_Menu_Title">Assistance</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert">Modifier la configuration</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert_Msg">La configuration peut uniquement être modifiée lors de l\'exécution. Vous devez relancer l\'application pour effectuer des modifications</string>
  <string name="RA_Update_Userdata_Error">Une erreur s\'est produite lors de la mise à jour des données utilisateur. Veuillez réessayer ultérieurement</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_A">Paramètres A de l\'application verticale</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_B">Paramètres B de l\'application verticale</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_C">Paramètres C de l\'application verticale</string>
  <string name="RA_Warning">AVERTISSEMENT</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Text">[fr]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Title">[fr]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Text">[fr]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 Platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Title">[fr]What\'s in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Text">[fr]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Title">[fr]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Text">[fr]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Title">[fr]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Text">[fr]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Title">[fr]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Text">[fr]The Security &amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rules.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Title">[fr]Secure &amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Text">[fr]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Title">[fr]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Text">[fr]Functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Title">[fr]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro">[fr]This app integrates the common components to development new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro_Title">[fr]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_You_are_not_LoggedIn">Vous n\'êtes pas connecté. Veuillez accéder aux paramètres et vous connecter.</string>
  <string name="RA_reference_device_scan">Balayage appareil de référence</string>
  <string name="RA_something_wrong">Un problème est survenu</string>
</resources>
