<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  Copyright (c) Koninklijke Philips N.V., 2018
  All rights are reserved. Reproduction or dissemination
  in whole or in part is prohibited without the prior written
  consent of the copyright holder.
  -->


<resources>
  <string name="BA_Add_Edit_Temp">기온 추가 또는 편집 </string>
  <string name="BA_AppFramework">앱 프레임워크 </string>
  <string name="BA_HSDP_login_not_available">사용할 수 없는 HSDP 로그인</string>
  <string name="BA_Sync_Settings">동기화 설정</string>
  <string name="RA_AboutScreen_Title">정보</string>
  <string name="RA_About_App_Version">버전</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Description_New">[ko]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Menu_Title">정보</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsDescription">[ko]\"Special offers, promotions and first hand information about new product releases.\nTailored for you!\n\nJoin 140.000 of your peers now!\"</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsTitle">[ko]What do we have to offer?</string>
  <string name="RA_Cancel">취소</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_AppInfra">[ko]AppInfra is the component\'s top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_Connectivity">[ko]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ConsumerCare">[ko]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_DataServices">[ko]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data: Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_InAppPurchase">[ko]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ProductRegistration">[ko]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UIToolkit">[ko]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UserRegistration">[ko]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization / social media specific credentials</string>
  <string name="RA_ConnectivityScreen_Title">연결성</string>
  <string name="RA_Done_Button_Text">완료</string>
  <string name="RA_Empty_Invalid_Data">데이터 필드가 비어있거나 유효하지 않음</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Body_Text">제안별 대형 텍스트는 본문에 옵니다. </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Header_Text">여기에는 제안별 타이틀이 옵니다. </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Menu_Title">모바일 앱 홈</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Title">모바일 앱 홈</string>
  <string name="RA_Invalid_Param_Msg">유효하지 않은 파라미터 값을 입력 또는 선택하셨습니다. 올바른 파라미터 값을 선택한 후 다시 시작하십시오.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Binary_Hosting_Consent">[ko]I allow Philips to store binary data</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Click_Stream_Hosting_Consent">[ko]I allow Philips to use my mobile application usage statistics</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Coaching_Consent">[ko]I allow Philips to use my data for Coaching purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Binary_Help_Text">[ko]The actual content of the binary consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream">본인은 앱의 기능과 개선, 맞춤화, 소셜 미디어와의 통합, 관련 내용 및 광고의 표시를 위해 필립스에서 앱 데이터를 수집할 수 있도록 허용합니다.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream_Help_Text">쿠키 정책\n\n이 앱에는 Adobe Systems Software Ireland Limited(“어도비”)에서 제공한 분석 서비스인 Adobe Analytics가 사용됩니다. Adobe Analytics는 “쿠키” 및 유사한 기술을 활용하며, 이는 당사의 앱을 통한 전체적인 트래픽 패턴을 분석할 수 있도록 사용자의 앱에 문서 파일 형태로 존재합니다. 쿠키에서 생성된 앱 사용 정보는 Adobe로 전송되며 저장되기 전에 먼저 익명화된 지리 위치와 IP주소를 일반 IP주소로 변환하도록 설정을 통해 관리합니다. Adobe는 필립스를 대신하여 앱 활동 및 앱 사용 관련 기타 정보를 필립스에 제공할 목적으로 앱 활동 관련 보고서를 수집하고 앱의 사용 평가에 관한 정보를 활용합니다. Adobe는 귀하의 IP 주소를 Adobe에서 소유한 다른 데이터와 연결하지 않습니다. 이 화면을 닫은 후에 참여하지 않기를 선택하면 Adobe와 필립스에 자료(쿠키 및 IP주소) 제공을 거부할 수 있습니다.\n</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Coaching_Help_Text">[ko]The actual content of the coaching consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Marketing_Help_Text">귀하께서 동의하신 결과로 필립스 그룹은 홍보를 위해 이메일, SMS를 비롯한 모바일 앱, 소셜 미디어 등 기타 디지털 채널을 통해 귀하께 연락을 드릴 수 있습니다. 귀하의 선호도와 행동 양식 기반의 맞춤형 커뮤니케이션 및 최상의 개인 맞춤형 경험을 제공하기 위해 귀하의 개인정보를 분석하고 조합할 수 있습니다. 이러한 정보는 다음과 같습니다. \n\n귀하께서 제공하신 정보\n당사와 공유하신 개인 정보에는 이름, 생년월일, 나이, 이메일 주소, 자택/회사 주소, 국가, 성별, 전화번호, 소셜 미디어 프로필 등이 있습니다.\n\n필립스와의 소통 과정에서 취득된 정보\n소셜 미디어, 웹 사이트, 이메일, 앱, 연계 제품 등 필립스 디지털 채널과의 소통 및 디지털 채널 사용을 통해 제공된 정보로, IP 주소, 쿠키, 장치 정보, 클릭한 커뮤니케이션, 위치 정보, 방문한 웹 사이트 등이 해당됩니다.\n\n언제라도 동의를 철회하실 수 있습니다.\n자세한 내용은 필립스 개인정보 보호정책 및 필립스 쿠키 정책을 참조하십시오.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Moment_Help_Text">[ko]The actual content of the moment consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Research_Analytics_Help_Text">[ko]The actual content of the research and analytics consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Moment_Consent">[ko]I allow Philips to store my data in cloud</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Research_Analytics_Consent">[ko]I allow Philips to use my data for Research and Analytics purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_NO_Order_History">사용할 수 없는 주문 내역</string>
  <string name="RA_OK">확인</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Dismiss">[ko]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Shop_Text">[ko]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Support_Text">[ko]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions product informations and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Benefit_Text">보증 기간이 24개월 간 연장됩니다.\n필립스에서 10% 할인을 받으실 수 있습니다.\n제품 악세서리 무료로 받기</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Email_Text">연장된 보증 계약서가 포함된 이메일이 고객님의 이메일 주소로 전송되었습니다.</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Extentende_Warranty">보증 기간이 내년까지 연장되었습니다.</string>
  <string name="RA_Philips_Shop_Menu_Title">필립스 매장</string>
  <string name="RA_Product_Registration_Text">제품 등록</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title">선호도와 온라인 활동을 바탕으로 한 필립스의 홍보성 커뮤니케이션을 수신</string>
  <string name="RA_SettingsScreen_Title">계정 설정</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Login">로그인</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout">로그아웃</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout_Alert">로그아웃하시겠습니까?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_MyAccount">내 계정</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_OrderHistory">주문 내역</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Promo_Question_Text">이는 무슨 의미입니까?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Purchases">구매</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Screen_Header_Title">설정</string>
  <string name="RA_Skip_Button_Text">건너뛰기</string>
  <string name="RA_SplashScreen_Title">모바일 앱</string>
  <string name="RA_SupportScreen_Title">지원</string>
  <string name="RA_Support_Menu_Title">지원</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert">구성 변경</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert_Msg">구성은 시작 시에 변경됩니다. 변경 사항을 적용하려면 앱을 다시 시작해야 합니다</string>
  <string name="RA_Update_Userdata_Error">사용자 데이터 업데이트 중 오류가 발생했습니다. 다시 시도해주십시오.</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_A">수직 앱 설정 A</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_B">수직 앱 설정 B</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_C">수직 앱 설정 C</string>
  <string name="RA_Warning">경고</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Text">[ko]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Title">[ko]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Text">[ko]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 Platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Title">[ko]What\'s in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Text">[ko]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Title">[ko]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Text">[ko]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Title">[ko]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Text">[ko]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Title">[ko]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Text">[ko]The Security &amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rules.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Title">[ko]Secure &amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Text">[ko]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Title">[ko]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Text">[ko]Functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Title">[ko]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro">[ko]This app integrates the common components to development new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro_Title">[ko]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_You_are_not_LoggedIn">로그인되어 있지 않습니다. 설정에서 로그인하십시오.</string>
  <string name="RA_reference_device_scan">레퍼런스 장치 스캔</string>
  <string name="RA_something_wrong">오류가 발생했습니다.</string>
</resources>
