<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  Copyright (c) Koninklijke Philips N.V., 2018
  All rights are reserved. Reproduction or dissemination
  in whole or in part is prohibited without the prior written
  consent of the copyright holder.
  -->


<resources>
  <string name="BA_Add_Edit_Temp">Pievienot vai rediģēt temperatūru </string>
  <string name="BA_AppFramework">Lietotnes platforma </string>
  <string name="BA_HSDP_login_not_available">HSDP pieteikšanās nav pieejama</string>
  <string name="BA_Sync_Settings">Sinhronizācijas iestatījumi</string>
  <string name="RA_AboutScreen_Title">Par</string>
  <string name="RA_About_App_Version">Versija</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Description_New">[lv]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Menu_Title">Par</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra">[lv]ail : App Infrastructure Library</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra_desc">[lv]AppInfra is the components top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC">[lv]dcc : Consumer Care</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC_desc">[lv]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_Connectivity">[lv]cml : CommLib</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_Connectivity_desc">[lv]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_DS">[lv]dsc : Data Services</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_DS_desc">[lv]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data -\n&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP">[lv]iap : In-app Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP_desc">[lv]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR">[lv]prg : Product Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR_desc">[lv]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UIKIT">[lv]uit : Mobile UI Toolkit Non DLS</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UIKIT_desc">[lv]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR">[lv]usr : User Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR_desc">[lv]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization social media specific credentials.</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsDescription">[lv]\"Special offers, promotions and first hand information about new product releases.\nTailored for you!\n\nJoin 140.000 of your peers now!\"</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsTitle">[lv]What do we have to offer?</string>
  <string name="RA_Cancel">Atcelt</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_AppInfra">[lv]AppInfra is the component\'s top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_Connectivity">[lv]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ConsumerCare">[lv]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_DataServices">[lv]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data: Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_InAppPurchase">[lv]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ProductRegistration">[lv]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UIToolkit">[lv]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UserRegistration">[lv]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization / social media specific credentials</string>
  <string name="RA_Coco_Version">[lv]App Info</string>
  <string name="RA_ConnectivityScreen_Title">Savienojamība</string>
  <string name="RA_DLSS_avatar_default_text">[lv]Hello User, \nPlease sign in.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Philips_Shop">[lv]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Support_screen_sub">[lv]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions, product information and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_copyright">[lv]Copyright \u00A9 2017 Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_description">[lv]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_privacy">[lv]Privacy policy</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_terms">[lv]Terms &amp;amp;amp; conditions</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_check_internet_connectivity">[lv]Check Internet Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_data_fetch_error">[lv]Not able to fetch data</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_data_fetch_wait">[lv]Wait..While we fetch your sleep data from device</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_enable_bluetooth">[lv]Please enable bluetooth</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_healthy_sleep_title">[lv]Healthy Sleep Score</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_sub_text">[lv]ReferenceApp is a base platform used by all propositions to develop and maintain features both generic and specific to the propositions. App infra, Data Gateway, App FWK, and UIToolkit allow Apps to be created from uApps and UI-less services/libraries. ReferenceApp acts as a foundation over which CDP2 uApps and proposition specific uApps are integrated to form individual apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_text">[lv]Reference App</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_insights_error">[lv]Error loading Insights</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_no_internet_connectivity">[lv]Internet connection is not available</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_sub_text">[lv]This app integrates the common components required to develop new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_title">[lv]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_sub_text">[lv]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_title">[lv]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_sub_text">[lv]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_title">[lv]What is in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_sub_text">[lv]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_title">[lv]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_sub_text">[lv]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_title">[lv]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_sub_text">[lv]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_title">[lv]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_sub_text">[lv]The Security &amp;amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rule.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_title">[lv]Secure &amp;amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_sub_text">[lv]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_title">[lv]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_sub_text">[lv]&lt;html&gt;The CDP&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;2&lt;small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;sup&gt; platform is fully integrated with HSDP and IT to ensure all functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_title">[lv]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_overlay_got_it">[lv]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_actual">[lv]Actual</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_connectivity">[lv]PowerSleep Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_deep_sleep_title">[lv]Time spent in deep sleep</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_default_data">[lv]--</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_ideal_deep_sleep">[lv](Ideal 120 mins)</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_ideal_sleep_time">[lv](Ideal 450-540 mins)</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_percentage_label">[lv]of 100</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_time_sleep">[lv]Time asleep</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_ps_tips_title">[lv]Tips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_sleep_element">[lv]Sleep element</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_splash_title">[lv]&lt;html&gt;&lt;b&gt;CDP&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;2&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Reference App&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_theme_title">[lv]Theme Setting</string>
  <string name="RA_Demo_Menu_Title">[lv]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_Done_Button_Text">Pabeigts</string>
  <string name="RA_Empty_Invalid_Data">Datu lauks ir tukšs vai nederīgs</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Body_Text">Pamattekstā paredzēts konkrētā piedāvājuma teksts </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Header_Text">Šeit paredzēts konkrētā piedāvājuma nosaukums </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Menu_Title">Mobilās lietotnes sākums</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Title">Mobilās lietotnes sākums</string>
  <string name="RA_Invalid_Param_Msg">Ir ievadītas vai atlasītas nederīgas parametru vērtības. Lūdzu, atlasiet atbilstošas parametru vērtības un palaidiet vēlreiz</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Binary_Hosting_Consent">[lv]I allow Philips to store binary data</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Click_Stream_Hosting_Consent">[lv]I allow Philips to use my mobile application usage statistics</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Coaching_Consent">[lv]I allow Philips to use my data for Coaching purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Binary_Help_Text">[lv]The actual content of the binary consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream">Es atļauju Philips ievākt manus lietotnes datus, lai palīdzētu lietotnei darboties, lai uzlabotu lietotni, lai personalizētu lietotni, lai integrētu lietotni sociālajos tīklos un lai redzētu atbilstošu saturu un reklāmas.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream_Help_Text">Paziņojums par sīkfailiem\n\nŠī lietotne izmanto Adobe Analytics, analīzes pakalpojumu (“Adobe Analytics”), ko nodrošina Adobe Systems Software Ireland Limited (“Adobe”). Adobe Analytics izmanto sīkfailus vai līdzīgas metodes, kas ir jūsu lietotnē ievietoti teksta faili, lai palīdzētu lietotnei analizēt vispārējo trafika modeli lietotnē. Pārsūtot sīkfailu savākto informāciju par lietotnes izmantošanu uz Adobe, iestatījumi nodrošina, lai IP adrese pirms ģeogrāfiskās atrašanās vietas noteikšanas tiktu anonimizēta un pirms saglabāšanas tiktu aizstāta ar ģenērisku IP adresi. Philips uzdevumā Adobe izmantos šo informāciju, lai novērtētu jūsu lietotnes izmantošanu, sastādītu pārskatus Philips vajadzībām par lietotnes aktivitāti un lai uzņēmumam Philips sniegtu citus pakalpojumus saistībā ar lietotnes aktivitāti un izmantošanu. Adobe nesaistīts jūsu IP adresi ne ar kādiem citiem Adobe rīcībā esošiem datiem. Jūs varat neļaut Adobe un Philips ievākt un izmantot datus (sīkfailus un IP adresi), pēc šī ekrāna aizvēršanas atlasot “opt-out” (Atteikties).\n</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Coaching_Help_Text">[lv]The actual content of the coaching consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Marketing_Help_Text">Pēc jūsu piekrišanas Philips grupas uzņēmumi var ar jums sazināties ar dažādiem reklāmas materiāliem pa e-pastu, sūtot SMS un citiem digitālajiem kanāliem, piemēram, mobilajām lietotnēm un sociālajiem tīkliem. Lai pielāgotu saziņu jūsu izvēlēm un darbībai un sniegtu jums vislabāko personalizēto pieredzi, mēs varam analizēt un kombinēt jūsu personas datus. Šie dati var ietvert: \n\nJūsu norādītie dati\nDati, kurus vēlaties aktīvi mums sniegt: jūsu vārds un uzvārds, dzimšanas datums vai vecums, e-pasta adrese, faktiskā adrese, valsts, dzimums, tālruņa numurs, sociālā tīkla profils.\n\nDati, kurus mēs iegūstam no jūsu mijiedarbības ar Philips\nDati par jūsu mijiedarbību ar Philips digitālajiem kanāliem un to izmantošanu, piemēram, sociālajiem tīkliem, tīmekļa vietnēm, e-pastu, lietotnēm un savienotajiem produktiem. Šie dati var ietvert: IP adresi, sīkfailus, ierīces informāciju, saziņas funkcijas, uz kurām noklikšķināt, atrašanās vietas informāciju un apmeklētās tīmekļa vietnes\n\nPhilips sniegs jums iespēju jebkurā brīdī atteikties no piekrišanas.\nLai iegūtu papildinformāciju, lūdzu, izlasiet Philips paziņojumu par konfidencialitāti un Philips paziņojumu par sīkfailiem.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Moment_Help_Text">[lv]The actual content of the moment consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Research_Analytics_Help_Text">[lv]The actual content of the research and analytics consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Moment_Consent">[lv]I allow Philips to store my data in cloud</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Research_Analytics_Consent">[lv]I allow Philips to use my data for Research and Analytics purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_Menu_title_Demo">[lv]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_NO_Order_History">Pasūtījumu vēsture nav pieejama</string>
  <string name="RA_OK">Labi</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Dismiss">[lv]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Shop_Text">[lv]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Support_Text">[lv]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions product informations and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Benefit_Text">Pagariniet garantiju līdz 24 mēnešiem.\nSaņemiet no Philips 10% atlaidi.\nSaņemiet produkta piederumus bez maksas</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Email_Text">Uz jūsu e-pasta adresi ir nosūtīts e-pasta ziņojums ar pagarinātu garantijas līgumu</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Extentende_Warranty">Jūsu garantijas termiņš ir pagarināts līdz nākamajam gadam</string>
  <string name="RA_Philips_Shop_Menu_Title">Philips veikals</string>
  <string name="RA_Product_Registration_Text">Reģistrējiet savu produktu</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_ACTIVATE_SCREEN_LOCK">[lv]Activate screenlock</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_DONT_SHOW_MESSAGE">[lv]Do not show this message again</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[lv]We’ve detected that you have rooted the device or jailbroken, thereby making it easier for others to access your data and no security on your application data.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_NO_THANKS">[lv]No thanks</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_PASSCODE_AND_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[lv]We’ve detected that you have jailbroken and not activated screenlock, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SCREEN_LOCK">[lv]We’ve detected the screenlock of your mobile phone is to enabled, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SECURE_YOUR_DATA">[lv]Secure your data</string>
  <string name="RA_See_a_doctor_Menu_Title">[lv]See a doctor</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title">Saņemt Philips reklāmas akciju piedāvājumus, pamatojoties uz manām izvēlēm un darbībām tiešsaistē</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title_Only">[lv]Receive Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_SettingsScreen_Title">Konta iestatījumi</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Login">Pieteikties</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout">Iziet</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout_Alert">Vai tiešām vēlaties atteikties?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_MyAccount">Mans konts</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_OrderHistory">Pasūtījumu vēsture</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Promo_Question_Text">Ko tas nozīmē?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Purchases">Pirkumi</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Screen_Header_Title">Iestatījumi</string>
  <string name="RA_Skip_Button_Text">Izlaist</string>
  <string name="RA_SplashScreen_Title">Mobilās lietotnes</string>
  <string name="RA_SupportScreen_Title">Atbalsts</string>
  <string name="RA_Support_Menu_Title">Atbalsts</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert">Mainīt konfigurāciju</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert_Msg">Konfigurāciju var mainīt tikai lietotnes palaišanas laikā. Lai mainītu konfigurāciju, ir vēlreiz jāpalaiž lietotne</string>
  <string name="RA_Update_Userdata_Error">Radās kļūda, atjauninot lietotāja datus. Lūdzu, mēģiniet pēc brīža</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_A">Vertikālais lietotnes iestatījums A</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_B">Vertikālais lietotnes iestatījums B</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_C">Vertikālais lietotnes iestatījums C</string>
  <string name="RA_Warning">BRĪDINĀJUMS</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Text">[lv]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Title">[lv]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Text">[lv]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 Platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Title">[lv]What\'s in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Text">[lv]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Title">[lv]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Text">[lv]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Title">[lv]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Text">[lv]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Title">[lv]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Text">[lv]The Security &amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rules.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Title">[lv]Secure &amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Text">[lv]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Title">[lv]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Text">[lv]Functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Title">[lv]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro">[lv]This app integrates the common components to development new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro_Title">[lv]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_You_are_not_LoggedIn">Jūs neesat pieteicies. Lūdzu, atveriet iestatījumu sadaļu un piesakieties</string>
  <string name="RA_change_config_desc">[lv]Configuration can only be changed at launch time. You need to relaunch the app to change it.</string>
  <string name="RA_loading_articles">[lv]Loading Article</string>
  <string name="RA_reference_device_scan">Atsauces ierīces skens</string>
  <string name="RA_something_wrong">Radās nezināma kļūda</string>
  <string name="chapters">[lv]Chapters</string>
  <string name="common_components">[lv]Common Components</string>
  <string name="description_close">[lv]Close</string>
  <string name="label_last_synced">[lv]Last updated: %1$s</string>
  <string name="label_last_synced_default">[lv]Last updated: No update yet</string>
  <string name="label_sleep_time_format">[lv]%d mins</string>
  <string name="label_sleep_tips">[lv]How can I improve my sleep score?</string>
  <string name="mya_config_tab">[lv]Configuration tab</string>
</resources>
