<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  Copyright (c) Koninklijke Philips N.V., 2018
  All rights are reserved. Reproduction or dissemination
  in whole or in part is prohibited without the prior written
  consent of the copyright holder.
  -->


<resources>
  <string name="BA_Add_Edit_Temp">Adăugare sau editare temperatură </string>
  <string name="BA_AppFramework">Cadru aplicaţie </string>
  <string name="BA_HSDP_login_not_available">Conectare HSDP indisponibilă</string>
  <string name="BA_Sync_Settings">Setări de sincronizare</string>
  <string name="RA_AboutScreen_Title">Despre</string>
  <string name="RA_About_App_Version">Versiune</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Description_New">[ro]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Menu_Title">Despre</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra">[ro]ail : App Infrastructure Library</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra_desc">[ro]AppInfra is the components top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC">[ro]dcc : Consumer Care</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC_desc">[ro]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_Connectivity">[ro]cml : CommLib</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_Connectivity_desc">[ro]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_DS">[ro]dsc : Data Services</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_DS_desc">[ro]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data -\n&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP">[ro]iap : In-app Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP_desc">[ro]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR">[ro]prg : Product Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR_desc">[ro]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UIKIT">[ro]uit : Mobile UI Toolkit Non DLS</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UIKIT_desc">[ro]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR">[ro]usr : User Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR_desc">[ro]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization social media specific credentials.</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsDescription">[ro]\"Special offers, promotions and first hand information about new product releases.\nTailored for you!\n\nJoin 140.000 of your peers now!\"</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsTitle">[ro]What do we have to offer?</string>
  <string name="RA_Cancel">Anulare</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_AppInfra">[ro]AppInfra is the component\'s top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_Connectivity">[ro]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ConsumerCare">[ro]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_DataServices">[ro]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data: Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_InAppPurchase">[ro]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ProductRegistration">[ro]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UIToolkit">[ro]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UserRegistration">[ro]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization / social media specific credentials</string>
  <string name="RA_Coco_Version">[ro]App Info</string>
  <string name="RA_ConnectivityScreen_Title">Conectivitate</string>
  <string name="RA_DLSS_avatar_default_text">[ro]Hello User, \nPlease sign in.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Philips_Shop">[ro]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Support_screen_sub">[ro]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions, product information and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_HomeScreen_Title">[ro]Reference App Home</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_copyright">[ro]Copyright \u00A9 2017 Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_description">[ro]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_privacy">[ro]Privacy policy</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_terms">[ro]Terms &amp;amp;amp; conditions</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_check_internet_connectivity">[ro]Check Internet Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_data_fetch_error">[ro]Not able to fetch data</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_data_fetch_wait">[ro]Wait..While we fetch your sleep data from device</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_enable_bluetooth">[ro]Please enable bluetooth</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_healthy_sleep_title">[ro]Healthy Sleep Score</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_sub_text">[ro]ReferenceApp is a base platform used by all propositions to develop and maintain features both generic and specific to the propositions. App infra, Data Gateway, App FWK, and UIToolkit allow Apps to be created from uApps and UI-less services/libraries. ReferenceApp acts as a foundation over which CDP2 uApps and proposition specific uApps are integrated to form individual apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_text">[ro]Reference App</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_insights_error">[ro]Error loading Insights</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_no_internet_connectivity">[ro]Internet connection is not available</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_sub_text">[ro]This app integrates the common components required to develop new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_title">[ro]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_sub_text">[ro]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_title">[ro]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_sub_text">[ro]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_title">[ro]What is in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_sub_text">[ro]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_title">[ro]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_sub_text">[ro]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_title">[ro]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_sub_text">[ro]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_title">[ro]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_sub_text">[ro]The Security &amp;amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rule.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_title">[ro]Secure &amp;amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_sub_text">[ro]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_title">[ro]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_sub_text">[ro]&lt;html&gt;The CDP&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;2&lt;small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;sup&gt; platform is fully integrated with HSDP and IT to ensure all functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_title">[ro]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_overlay_got_it">[ro]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_actual">[ro]Actual</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_connectivity">[ro]PowerSleep Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_deep_sleep_title">[ro]Time spent in deep sleep</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_default_data">[ro]--</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_ideal_deep_sleep">[ro](Ideal 120 mins)</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_ideal_sleep_time">[ro](Ideal 450-540 mins)</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_percentage_label">[ro]of 100</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_time_sleep">[ro]Time asleep</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_ps_tips_title">[ro]Tips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_sleep_element">[ro]Sleep element</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_splash_title">[ro]&lt;html&gt;&lt;b&gt;CDP&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;2&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Reference App&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_theme_title">[ro]Theme Setting</string>
  <string name="RA_Demo_Menu_Title">[ro]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_Done_Button_Text">Finalizat</string>
  <string name="RA_Empty_Invalid_Data">Câmpul de date este gol sau nevalid</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Body_Text">Textul mare specific ofertei apare în corp </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Header_Text">Titlul specific ofertei apare aici </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Menu_Title">Pagina principală a aplicaţiei mobile</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Title">Pagina principală a aplicaţiei mobile</string>
  <string name="RA_Invalid_Param_Msg">Ai introdus sau selectat valori nevalide ale parametrilor. Selectează valori corespunzătoare ale parametrilor şi lansează din nou aplicaţia.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Binary_Hosting_Consent">[ro]I allow Philips to store binary data</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Click_Stream_Hosting_Consent">[ro]I allow Philips to use my mobile application usage statistics</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Coaching_Consent">[ro]I allow Philips to use my data for Coaching purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Binary_Help_Text">[ro]The actual content of the binary consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream">Permit Philips să îmi colecteze datele aplicaţiei pentru a ajuta aplicaţia să funcţioneze, pentru a îmbunătăţi aplicaţia, pentru integrare cu reţelele de socializare şi pentru a afişa conţinut şi reclame relevante.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream_Help_Text">Notificare privind modulele cookie\n\nAceastă aplicaţie foloseşte Adobe Analytics, un serviciu de analiză („Adobe Analytics”) furnizat de Adobe Systems Software Ireland Limited („Adobe”). Adobe Analytics foloseşte „module cookie” sau tehnici similare, care sunt fişiere text plasate în aplicaţie pentru a o ajuta să recunoască tiparele generale de trafic din aplicaţie. Atunci când informaţiile generate de modulele cookie despre utilizarea aplicaţiei sunt trimise la Adobe, anumite setări se asigură că adresa IP este anonimizată înainte de localizarea geografică şi va fi înlocuită de o adresă IP generică înainte de stocare. În numele Philips, Adobe va folosi aceste informaţii pentru a evalua modul în care utilizezi aplicaţia, generând rapoarte despre activitatea în aplicaţie pentru Philips şi în scopul de a furniza Philips alte servicii legate de activitatea din aplicaţie şi utilizarea aplicaţiei. Adobe nu va asocia adresa ta IP cu alte date deţinute de Adobe. Poţi să împiedici Adobe şi Philips să colecteze şi să utilizeze astfel de date (module cookie şi adrese IP) dacă renunţi la această la această opţiune după ce închizi acest ecran.\n</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Coaching_Help_Text">[ro]The actual content of the coaching consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Marketing_Help_Text">Ca urmare a consimţământului tău, companiile din grupul Philips ar putea să te contacteze cu comunicări promoţionale prin e-mail, SMS şi alte canale digitale, precum aplicaţii mobile şi reţele de socializare. Pentru a putea să adaptăm comunicările la comportamentul şi preferinţele tale şi să îţi oferim o experienţă optimă, personalizată, este posibil să îţi analizăm şi combinăm datele personale. Aceste date pot include: \n\nDate furnizate de tine\nDatele pe care doreşti să le partajezi activ cu noi, precum numele, data naşterii sau vârsta, adresa de e-mail, adresa fizică, ţara, sexul, numărul de telefon, profilul din reţelele de socializare.\n\nDate pe care le primim din interacţiunile tale cu Philips\nDate cu privire la interacţiunile şi utilizarea canalelor digitale Philips, precum reţele de socializare, site-uri web, e-mailuri, aplicaţii şi produse conectate. Aceste date pot include: adresa IP, module cookie, informaţii despre dispozitiv, comunicări pe care le accesezi cu clic, detalii privind locaţia şi site-uri web pe care le vizitezi\n\nPhilips îţi oferă oportunitatea să-ţi retragi consimţământul în orice moment.\nPentru mai multe informaţii, citeşte Notificarea de confidenţialitate Philips şi Notificarea privind modulele cookie Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Moment_Help_Text">[ro]The actual content of the moment consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Research_Analytics_Help_Text">[ro]The actual content of the research and analytics consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Moment_Consent">[ro]I allow Philips to store my data in cloud</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Research_Analytics_Consent">[ro]I allow Philips to use my data for Research and Analytics purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_Menu_title_Demo">[ro]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_NO_Order_History">Istoricul comenzilor este indisponibil</string>
  <string name="RA_OK">OK</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Dismiss">[ro]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Shop_Text">[ro]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Support_Text">[ro]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions product informations and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Benefit_Text">Extinde garanţia cu 24 de luni.\nPrimeşte o reducere de 10 % la produsele cumpărate din magazinul Philips.\nPrimeşte accesorii gratuite pentru produse</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Email_Text">Un e-mail cu contractul de garanţie extins a fost trimis la adresa ta de e-mail</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Extentende_Warranty">Perioada de garanţie a fost extinsă până anul următor</string>
  <string name="RA_Philips_Shop_Menu_Title">Magazin Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_Product_Registration_Text">Înregistrează-ţi produsul</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_ACTIVATE_SCREEN_LOCK">[ro]Activate screenlock</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_DONT_SHOW_MESSAGE">[ro]Do not show this message again</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[ro]We’ve detected that you have rooted the device or jailbroken, thereby making it easier for others to access your data and no security on your application data.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_NO_THANKS">[ro]No thanks</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_PASSCODE_AND_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[ro]We’ve detected that you have jailbroken and not activated screenlock, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SCREEN_LOCK">[ro]We’ve detected the screenlock of your mobile phone is to enabled, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SECURE_YOUR_DATA">[ro]Secure your data</string>
  <string name="RA_See_a_doctor_Menu_Title">[ro]See a doctor</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title">Primeşte comunicări promoţionale de la Philips în funcţie de preferinţe şi de comportamentul tău online</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title_Only">[ro]Receive Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_SettingsScreen_Title">Setările contului</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Login">Conectare</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout">Deconectare</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout_Alert">Sigur vrei să te deconectezi?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_MyAccount">Contul meu</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_OrderHistory">Istoricul comenzilor</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Promo_Question_Text">Ce înseamnă aceasta?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Purchases">Achiziţii</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Screen_Header_Title">Setări</string>
  <string name="RA_Skip_Button_Text">Omitere</string>
  <string name="RA_SplashScreen_Title">Aplicaţii mobile</string>
  <string name="RA_SupportScreen_Title">Asistenţă</string>
  <string name="RA_Support_Menu_Title">Asistenţă</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert">Schimbă configuraţia</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert_Msg">Configuraţia poate fi schimbată doar la momentul lansării. Trebuie să lansezi din nou aplicaţia pentru a o modifica.</string>
  <string name="RA_Update_Userdata_Error">A apărut o eroare la actualizarea datelor utilizatorului. Încearcă din nou mai târziu.</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_A">Setare aplicaţie verticală A</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_B">Setare aplicaţie verticală B</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_C">Setare aplicaţie verticală C</string>
  <string name="RA_Warning">AVERTISMENT</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Text">[ro]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Title">[ro]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Text">[ro]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 Platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Title">[ro]What\'s in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Text">[ro]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Title">[ro]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Text">[ro]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Title">[ro]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Text">[ro]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Title">[ro]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Text">[ro]The Security &amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rules.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Title">[ro]Secure &amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Text">[ro]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Title">[ro]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Text">[ro]Functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Title">[ro]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro">[ro]This app integrates the common components to development new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro_Title">[ro]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_You_are_not_LoggedIn">Nu te-ai conectat. Accesează Setările şi conectează-te</string>
  <string name="RA_change_config_desc">[ro]Configuration can only be changed at launch time. You need to relaunch the app to change it.</string>
  <string name="RA_loading_articles">[ro]Loading Article</string>
  <string name="RA_reference_device_scan">Scanare dispozitiv de referinţă</string>
  <string name="RA_something_wrong">A apărut o eroare</string>
  <string name="chapters">[ro]Chapters</string>
  <string name="common_components">[ro]Common Components</string>
  <string name="description_close">[ro]Close</string>
  <string name="label_last_synced">[ro]Last updated: %1$s</string>
  <string name="label_last_synced_default">[ro]Last updated: No update yet</string>
  <string name="label_sleep_time_format">[ro]%d mins</string>
  <string name="label_sleep_tips">[ro]How can I improve my sleep score?</string>
  <string name="mya_config_tab">[ro]Configuration tab</string>
</resources>
