<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  Copyright (c) Koninklijke Philips N.V., 2018
  All rights are reserved. Reproduction or dissemination
  in whole or in part is prohibited without the prior written
  consent of the copyright holder.
  -->


<resources>
  <string name="BA_Add_Edit_Temp">เพิ่มหรือแก้ไขอุณหภูมิ </string>
  <string name="BA_AppFramework">AppFramework </string>
  <string name="BA_HSDP_login_not_available">ไม่สามารถล็อกอิน HSDP ได้</string>
  <string name="BA_Sync_Settings">การตั้งค่าการซิงค์</string>
  <string name="RA_AboutScreen_Title">เกี่ยวกับ</string>
  <string name="RA_About_App_Version">เวอร์ชัน</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Description_New">[th]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Menu_Title">เกี่ยวกับ</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra">[th]ail : App Infrastructure Library</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra_desc">[th]AppInfra is the components top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC">[th]dcc : Consumer Care</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC_desc">[th]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_Connectivity">[th]cml : CommLib</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_Connectivity_desc">[th]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_DS">[th]dsc : Data Services</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_DS_desc">[th]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data -\n&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP">[th]iap : In-app Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP_desc">[th]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR">[th]prg : Product Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR_desc">[th]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UIKIT">[th]uit : Mobile UI Toolkit Non DLS</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UIKIT_desc">[th]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR">[th]usr : User Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR_desc">[th]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization social media specific credentials.</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsDescription">[th]\"Special offers, promotions and first hand information about new product releases.\nTailored for you!\n\nJoin 140.000 of your peers now!\"</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsTitle">[th]What do we have to offer?</string>
  <string name="RA_Cancel">ยกเลิก</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_AppInfra">[th]AppInfra is the component\'s top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_Connectivity">[th]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ConsumerCare">[th]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_DataServices">[th]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data: Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_InAppPurchase">[th]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ProductRegistration">[th]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UIToolkit">[th]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UserRegistration">[th]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization / social media specific credentials</string>
  <string name="RA_Coco_Version">[th]App Info</string>
  <string name="RA_ConnectivityScreen_Title">การเชื่อมต่อ</string>
  <string name="RA_DLSS_avatar_default_text">[th]Hello User, \nPlease sign in.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Philips_Shop">[th]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Support_screen_sub">[th]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions, product information and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_copyright">[th]Copyright \u00A9 2017 Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_description">[th]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_privacy">[th]Privacy policy</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_terms">[th]Terms &amp;amp;amp; conditions</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_check_internet_connectivity">[th]Check Internet Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_data_fetch_error">[th]Not able to fetch data</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_data_fetch_wait">[th]Wait..While we fetch your sleep data from device</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_enable_bluetooth">[th]Please enable bluetooth</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_healthy_sleep_title">[th]Healthy Sleep Score</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_sub_text">[th]ReferenceApp is a base platform used by all propositions to develop and maintain features both generic and specific to the propositions. App infra, Data Gateway, App FWK, and UIToolkit allow Apps to be created from uApps and UI-less services/libraries. ReferenceApp acts as a foundation over which CDP2 uApps and proposition specific uApps are integrated to form individual apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_text">[th]Reference App</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_insights_error">[th]Error loading Insights</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_no_internet_connectivity">[th]Internet connection is not available</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_sub_text">[th]This app integrates the common components required to develop new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_title">[th]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_sub_text">[th]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_title">[th]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_sub_text">[th]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_title">[th]What is in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_sub_text">[th]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_title">[th]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_sub_text">[th]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_title">[th]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_sub_text">[th]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_title">[th]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_sub_text">[th]The Security &amp;amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rule.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_title">[th]Secure &amp;amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_sub_text">[th]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_title">[th]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_sub_text">[th]&lt;html&gt;The CDP&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;2&lt;small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;sup&gt; platform is fully integrated with HSDP and IT to ensure all functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_title">[th]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_overlay_got_it">[th]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_actual">[th]Actual</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_connectivity">[th]PowerSleep Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_deep_sleep_title">[th]Time spent in deep sleep</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_default_data">[th]--</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_ideal_deep_sleep">[th](Ideal 120 mins)</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_ideal_sleep_time">[th](Ideal 450-540 mins)</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_percentage_label">[th]of 100</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_time_sleep">[th]Time asleep</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_ps_tips_title">[th]Tips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_sleep_element">[th]Sleep element</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_splash_title">[th]&lt;html&gt;&lt;b&gt;CDP&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;2&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Reference App&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_theme_title">[th]Theme Setting</string>
  <string name="RA_Demo_Menu_Title">[th]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_Done_Button_Text">เสร็จ</string>
  <string name="RA_Empty_Invalid_Data">ฟิลด์ข้อมูลว่างเปล่าหรือไม่ถูกต้อง</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Body_Text">ส่วนข้อความเฉพาะขนาดใหญ่ให้ใส่ที่บอดี้ </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Header_Text">ส่วนหัวเรื่องเฉพาะให้ใส่ที่นี่ </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Menu_Title">หน้าแรกแอปมือถือ</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Title">หน้าแรกแอปมือถือ</string>
  <string name="RA_Invalid_Param_Msg">คุณได้ป้อนหรือเลือกค่าพารามิเตอร์ที่ไม่ถูกต้อง โปรดเลือกค่าพารามิเตอร์ที่เหมาะสม แล้วเริ่มอีกครั้ง</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Binary_Hosting_Consent">[th]I allow Philips to store binary data</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Click_Stream_Hosting_Consent">[th]I allow Philips to use my mobile application usage statistics</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Coaching_Consent">[th]I allow Philips to use my data for Coaching purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Binary_Help_Text">[th]The actual content of the binary consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream">ฉันอนุญาตให้ Philips เก็บข้อมูลแอปพลิเคชันของฉันเพื่อช่วยให้แอปพลิเคชันทำงาน เพื่อพัฒนาแอปพลิเคชัน เพื่อปรับแต่งแอปพลิเคชัน เพื่อรวมเข้ากับสื่อสังคมออนไลน์ และเพื่อแสดงเนื้อหาและโฆษณาที่เกี่ยวข้อง</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream_Help_Text">ประกาศเกี่ยวกับคุกกี้\n\nแอปพลิเคชันนี้ใช้ Adobe Analytics ซึ่งเป็นบริการการวิเคราะห์ (“Adobe Analytics”) จากบริษัท Adobe Systems Software Ireland จำกัด (“Adobe”) Adobe Analytics ใช้ “คุกกี้” ซึ่งเป็นไฟล์ข้อความที่อยู่ในแอปพลิเคชันของคุณหรือเทคนิคอื่นๆ ที่คล้ายกัน เพื่อช่วยให้แอปพลิเคชันวิเคราะห์ภาพรวมของรูปแบบความหนาแน่นของข้อมูลบนแอปพลิเคชันของเรา ด้วยการถ่ายโอนข้อมูลเกี่ยวกับการใช้งานแอปพลิเคชันที่สร้างโดยคุกกี้ไปยัง Adobe การตั้งค่าจะทำให้แน่ใจว่าจะไม่มีการระบุชื่อ IP แอดเดรสก่อนมีการกำหนดตำแหน่งที่ตั้งทางภูมิศาสตร์และจะมีการแทนที่ด้วย IP แอดเดรสทั่วไปก่อนเก็บบันทึก ในนามของ Philips Adobe จะใช้ข้อมูลนี้สำหรับการประเมินการใช้งานแอปพลิเคชันของคุณ รวบรวมรายงานเกี่ยวกับกิจกรรมของแอปพลิเคชันสำหรับ Philips และเพื่อให้บริการอื่นๆ ที่เกี่ยวข้องกับกิจกรรมของแอปพลิเคชันและการใช้งานแอปพลิเคชันแก่ Philips โดย Adobe จะไม่เชื่อมโยง IP แอดเดรสของคุณเข้ากับข้อมูลอื่นๆ ที่ Adobe มี คุณสามารถป้องกันการเก็บและการใช้ข้อมูลของ Adobe และ Philips (คุกกี้และ IP แอดเดรส) หากคุณเลือกไม่เข้าร่วมหลังจากปิดหน้าจอนี้\n</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Coaching_Help_Text">[th]The actual content of the coaching consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Marketing_Help_Text">อันเนื่องมาจากการยินยอมของคุณ กลุ่มบริษัท Philips อาจติดต่อคุณพร้อมด้วยการสื่อสารเพื่อส่งเสริมการขายผ่านอีเมล SMS หรือช่องทางดิจิตอลอื่นๆ เช่น แอปมือถือและสื่อสังคมออนไลน์ นอกจากนี้ เราอาจทำการวิเคราะห์และผสานข้อมูลส่วนบุคคลของคุณเพื่อออกแบบการติดต่อสื่อสารให้ตรงกับความต้องการและพฤติกรรมการใช้งานของคุณ และเพื่อส่งมอบประสบการณ์ที่เหมาะสมและดีเยี่ยมที่สุดสำหรับคุณ ข้อมูลนี้ประกอบด้วย: \n\nข้อมูลที่คุณให้แก่เรา\nข้อมูลที่คุณต้องการแบ่งปันกับเราเช่น: ชื่อของคุณ, วันเกิดหรืออายุ, อีเมล์, ที่อยู่, ประเทศ, เพศ, หมายเลขโทรศัพท์, โปรไฟล์สื่อสังคมออนไลน์\n\nข้อมูลที่เราได้จากการที่คุณมีปฏิสัมพันธ์กับ Philips\nข้อมูลเกี่ยวกับการมีปฏิสัมพันธ์และการใช้งานช่องทางดิจิตอลของ Philips ของคุณ เช่น สื่อสังคมออนไลน์ เว็บไซต์ อีเมล์ แอปพลิเคชันและผลิตภัณฑ์ที่เชื่อมต่อ ข้อมูลนี้ประกอบด้วย: IP แอดเดรส, คุกกี้, ข้อมูลอุปกรณ์, การสื่อสารที่คุณคลิก, รายละเอียดของสถานที่ และเว็บไซต์ที่คุณเยี่ยมชม\n\nPhilips ให้โอกาสคุณในการเพิกถอนคำยินยอมเมื่อใดก็ได้\nสำหรับข้อมูลเพิ่มเติม โปรดอ่านประกาศเกี่ยวกับความเป็นส่วนตัวของ Philips และประกาศเกี่ยวกับการใช้คุกกี้ของ Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Moment_Help_Text">[th]The actual content of the moment consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Research_Analytics_Help_Text">[th]The actual content of the research and analytics consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Moment_Consent">[th]I allow Philips to store my data in cloud</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Research_Analytics_Consent">[th]I allow Philips to use my data for Research and Analytics purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_Menu_title_Demo">[th]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_NO_Order_History">ไม่สามารถดูประวัติการสั่งซื้อได้</string>
  <string name="RA_OK">ตกลง</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Dismiss">[th]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Shop_Text">[th]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Support_Text">[th]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions product informations and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Benefit_Text">ขยายการรับประกันของคุณออกไปอีก 24 เดือน\nรับส่วนลด 10% ใน Philips\nรับสินค้าอุปกรณ์เสริมฟรี</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Email_Text">เราได้ส่งอีเมล์ที่มีสัญญาการรับประกันที่ขยายเพิ่มเติมไปยังอีเมล์แอดเดรสของคุณแล้ว</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Extentende_Warranty">ระยะเวลาการรับประกันของคุณได้ขยายออกไปเป็นปีหน้า</string>
  <string name="RA_Philips_Shop_Menu_Title">ร้านค้า Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_Product_Registration_Text">ลงทะเบียนผลิตภัณฑ์ของคุณ</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_ACTIVATE_SCREEN_LOCK">[th]Activate screenlock</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_DONT_SHOW_MESSAGE">[th]Do not show this message again</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[th]We’ve detected that you have rooted the device or jailbroken, thereby making it easier for others to access your data and no security on your application data.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_NO_THANKS">[th]No thanks</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_PASSCODE_AND_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[th]We’ve detected that you have jailbroken and not activated screenlock, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SCREEN_LOCK">[th]We’ve detected the screenlock of your mobile phone is to enabled, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SECURE_YOUR_DATA">[th]Secure your data</string>
  <string name="RA_See_a_doctor_Menu_Title">[th]See a doctor</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title">รับการแจ้งข่าวสารด้านโปรโมชันของ Philips ตามความต้องการและพฤติกรรมในโลกออนไลน์ของฉัน</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title_Only">[th]Receive Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_SettingsScreen_Title">การตั้งค่าบัญชี</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Login">ล็อกอิน</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout">ล็อกเอาต์</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout_Alert">คุณแน่ใจหรือไม่ว่าต้องการล็อกเอาท์</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_MyAccount">บัญชีของฉัน</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_OrderHistory">ประวัติการสั่งซื้อ</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Promo_Question_Text">หมายความว่าอย่างไร</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Purchases">สั่งซื้อ</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Screen_Header_Title">การตั้งค่า</string>
  <string name="RA_Skip_Button_Text">ข้าม</string>
  <string name="RA_SplashScreen_Title">แอปมือถือ</string>
  <string name="RA_SupportScreen_Title">ฝ่ายสนับสนุน</string>
  <string name="RA_Support_Menu_Title">ฝ่ายสนับสนุน</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert">เปลี่ยนการกำหนดค่า</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert_Msg">สามารถเปลี่ยนการกำหนดค่าได้ในเวลาเริ่มใช้เท่านั้น คุณจำเป็นต้องเริ่มแอปใหม่อีกครั้งเพื่อเปลี่ยน</string>
  <string name="RA_Update_Userdata_Error">มีข้อผิดพลาดในการอัพเดตข้อมูลผู้ใช้ โปรดลองอีกครั้งในภายหลัง</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_A">การตั้งค่าเวอร์ติคอลแอป A</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_B">การตั้งค่าเวอร์ติคอลแอป B</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_C">การตั้งค่าเวอร์ติคอลแอป C</string>
  <string name="RA_Warning">คำเตือน</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Text">[th]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Title">[th]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Text">[th]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 Platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Title">[th]What\'s in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Text">[th]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Title">[th]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Text">[th]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Title">[th]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Text">[th]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Title">[th]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Text">[th]The Security &amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rules.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Title">[th]Secure &amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Text">[th]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Title">[th]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Text">[th]Functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Title">[th]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro">[th]This app integrates the common components to development new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro_Title">[th]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_You_are_not_LoggedIn">คุณยังไม่ได้ล็อกอิน โปรดไปที่การตั้งค่าแล้วล็อกอิน</string>
  <string name="RA_change_config_desc">[th]Configuration can only be changed at launch time. You need to relaunch the app to change it.</string>
  <string name="RA_loading_articles">[th]Loading Article</string>
  <string name="RA_reference_device_scan">สแกนอุปกรณ์อ้างอิง</string>
  <string name="RA_something_wrong">มีข้อผิดพลาดเกิดขึ้น</string>
  <string name="chapters">[th]Chapters</string>
  <string name="common_components">[th]Common Components</string>
  <string name="description_close">[th]Close</string>
  <string name="label_last_synced">[th]Last updated: %1$s</string>
  <string name="label_last_synced_default">[th]Last updated: No update yet</string>
  <string name="label_sleep_time_format">[th]%d mins</string>
  <string name="label_sleep_tips">[th]How can I improve my sleep score?</string>
  <string name="mya_config_tab">[th]Configuration tab</string>
</resources>
