<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  Copyright (c) Koninklijke Philips N.V., 2018
  All rights are reserved. Reproduction or dissemination
  in whole or in part is prohibited without the prior written
  consent of the copyright holder.
  -->


<resources>
  <string name="BA_Add_Edit_Temp">温度を追加または編集 </string>
  <string name="BA_AppFramework">アプリフレームワーク </string>
  <string name="BA_HSDP_login_not_available">HSDP ログインはできません</string>
  <string name="BA_Sync_Settings">同期設定</string>
  <string name="RA_AboutScreen_Title">バージョン情報</string>
  <string name="RA_About_App_Version">バージョン</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Description_New">[ja]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Menu_Title">バージョン情報</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsDescription">[ja]\"Special offers, promotions and first hand information about new product releases.\nTailored for you!\n\nJoin 140.000 of your peers now!\"</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsTitle">[ja]What do we have to offer?</string>
  <string name="RA_Cancel">キャンセル</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_AppInfra">[ja]AppInfra is the component\'s top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_Connectivity">[ja]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ConsumerCare">[ja]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_DataServices">[ja]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data: Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_InAppPurchase">[ja]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ProductRegistration">[ja]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UIToolkit">[ja]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UserRegistration">[ja]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization / social media specific credentials</string>
  <string name="RA_ConnectivityScreen_Title">接続性</string>
  <string name="RA_Done_Button_Text">完了</string>
  <string name="RA_Empty_Invalid_Data">データフィールドが空か無効</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Body_Text">本文に特定の大きいテキストを提案 </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Header_Text">ここに特定のタイトルを提案 </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Menu_Title">モバイルアプリホーム</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Title">モバイルアプリホーム</string>
  <string name="RA_Invalid_Param_Msg">無効なパラメーター値が入力または選択されました。適切なパラメーター値を選択してから再起動してください。</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Binary_Hosting_Consent">[ja]I allow Philips to store binary data</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Click_Stream_Hosting_Consent">[ja]I allow Philips to use my mobile application usage statistics</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Coaching_Consent">[ja]I allow Philips to use my data for Coaching purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Binary_Help_Text">[ja]The actual content of the binary consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream">私は、アプリ機能の実現、アプリの改善、アプリのパーソナライズ、ソーシャルメディアとの統合、ならびに関連コンテンツおよび広告の表示を目的として、フィリップスが私のアプリデータを収集することを許可します。</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream_Help_Text">cookie に関する通知\n\nこのアプリでは、Adobe Systems Software Ireland Limited（「Adobe」）が提供するアナリティクスサービス（「Adobe Analytics」）を使用します。Adobe Analytics では、アプリを介した全トラフィックパターンを解析するために、アプリ内に保存されるテキストファイルである「cookie」または類似の技術を使用します。cookie によって生成された、アプリの使用に関する情報を Adobe に伝送することにより、IP アドレスがジオローカライズ前に匿名化され、汎用 IP アドレスに置き換えてから保管されるように設定します。Adobe はフィリップスの代理として、アプリの使用の評価、フィリップス向けアプリアクティビティレポートのコンパイル、アプリアクティビティとアプリの使用に関連する他のサービスのフィリップスへの提供を目的として、この情報を使用します。Adobe は、同社が保持するその他のいかなるデータともお客様の IP アドレスを関連付けることはありません。お客様は、この画面を閉じた後で、Adobe およびフィリップスによるデータの収集および使用拒否を選択することができます。\n</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Coaching_Help_Text">[ja]The actual content of the coaching consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Marketing_Help_Text">お客様にご同意いただいた場合、フィリップスグループ各社が、メール、SMS、モバイルアプリやソーシャルメディアなどのその他デジタルチャネルを利用して直接ご連絡させていただく場合があります。お客様の嗜好や行動に応じて最適な情報をご提供するために、当社では、お客様の個人データを分析したり結びつけたりする場合があります。それらのデータには次が含まれます： \n\nお客様にご提供いただいたデータ\nお客様のお名前、生年月日、年齢、メールアドレス、住所、お住まいの国、性別、電話番号、ソーシャルメディアプロフィールなど、お客様のご希望でご提供いただいたデータ。\n\nお客様とのやり取りで当社が入手したデータ\nソーシャルメディア、ウェブサイト、メール、アプリ、コネクテッド製品などのフィリップスのデジタルチャネルでのやり取りおよび使用に関するデータ。これらのデータには、IP アドレス、cookie、デバイス情報、お客様がクリックしたやり取り、位置情報の詳細、アクセスしたウェブサイトなども含まれます。\n\nお客様はいつでも同意を取り消すことができます。\n詳細については、当社のプライバシーに関する通知および cookie に関するポリシーをお読みください。</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Moment_Help_Text">[ja]The actual content of the moment consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Research_Analytics_Help_Text">[ja]The actual content of the research and analytics consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Moment_Consent">[ja]I allow Philips to store my data in cloud</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Research_Analytics_Consent">[ja]I allow Philips to use my data for Research and Analytics purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_NO_Order_History">注文履歴を確認できません</string>
  <string name="RA_OK">OK</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Dismiss">[ja]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Shop_Text">[ja]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Support_Text">[ja]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions product informations and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Benefit_Text">保証を 24 か月延長いたします\nフィリップス ショップで 10% 割引を適用いたします\n製品アクセサリを無料で差し上げます</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Email_Text">保証延長契約に関するメールがお客様のメールアドレスに送信されました</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Extentende_Warranty">保証期間が来年まで延長されました。</string>
  <string name="RA_Philips_Shop_Menu_Title">フィリップス ショップ</string>
  <string name="RA_Product_Registration_Text">製品を登録</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title">自分の嗜好やオンラインアクティビティに基づいたフィリップスのプロモーション情報の受信を希望します</string>
  <string name="RA_SettingsScreen_Title">アカウント設定</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Login">ログイン</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout">ログアウト</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout_Alert">ログアウトしますか？</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_MyAccount">マイアカウント</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_OrderHistory">注文履歴</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Promo_Question_Text">どういう意味ですか？</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Purchases">購入</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Screen_Header_Title">設定</string>
  <string name="RA_Skip_Button_Text">スキップ</string>
  <string name="RA_SplashScreen_Title">モバイルアプリ</string>
  <string name="RA_SupportScreen_Title">サポート</string>
  <string name="RA_Support_Menu_Title">サポート</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert">設定を変更</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert_Msg">設定を変更できるのは起動時のみです。変更するにはアプリを起動し直す必要があります。</string>
  <string name="RA_Update_Userdata_Error">ユーザーデータの更新時にエラーが発生しました。しばらくしてから再試行ください。</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_A">バーティカルアプリ設定 A</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_B">バーティカルアプリ設定 B</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_C">バーティカルアプリ設定 C</string>
  <string name="RA_Warning">警告</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Text">[ja]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Title">[ja]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Text">[ja]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 Platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Title">[ja]What\'s in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Text">[ja]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Title">[ja]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Text">[ja]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Title">[ja]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Text">[ja]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Title">[ja]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Text">[ja]The Security &amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rules.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Title">[ja]Secure &amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Text">[ja]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Title">[ja]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Text">[ja]Functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Title">[ja]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro">[ja]This app integrates the common components to development new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro_Title">[ja]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_You_are_not_LoggedIn">ログインしていません。［設定］からログインしてください</string>
  <string name="RA_reference_device_scan">リファレンスデバイススキャン</string>
  <string name="RA_something_wrong">問題が発生しました</string>
</resources>
