<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  Copyright (c) Koninklijke Philips N.V., 2018
  All rights are reserved. Reproduction or dissemination
  in whole or in part is prohibited without the prior written
  consent of the copyright holder.
  -->


<resources>
  <string name="BA_Add_Edit_Temp">Dodaj lub edytuj temperaturę </string>
  <string name="BA_AppFramework">Struktura aplikacji </string>
  <string name="BA_HSDP_login_not_available">Login HSDP niedostępny</string>
  <string name="BA_Sync_Settings">Ustawienia synchronizacji</string>
  <string name="RA_AboutScreen_Title">Informacje</string>
  <string name="RA_About_App_Version">Wersja</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Description_New">[pl]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Menu_Title">Informacje</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra">[pl]ail : App Infrastructure Library</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra_desc">[pl]AppInfra is the components top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC">[pl]dcc : Consumer Care</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC_desc">[pl]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_Connectivity">[pl]cml : CommLib</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_Connectivity_desc">[pl]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_DS">[pl]dsc : Data Services</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_DS_desc">[pl]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data -\n&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP">[pl]iap : In-app Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP_desc">[pl]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR">[pl]prg : Product Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR_desc">[pl]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UIKIT">[pl]uit : Mobile UI Toolkit Non DLS</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UIKIT_desc">[pl]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR">[pl]usr : User Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR_desc">[pl]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization social media specific credentials.</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsDescription">[pl]\"Special offers, promotions and first hand information about new product releases.\nTailored for you!\n\nJoin 140.000 of your peers now!\"</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsTitle">[pl]What do we have to offer?</string>
  <string name="RA_Cancel">Anuluj</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_AppInfra">[pl]AppInfra is the component\'s top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_Connectivity">[pl]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ConsumerCare">[pl]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_DataServices">[pl]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data: Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_InAppPurchase">[pl]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ProductRegistration">[pl]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UIToolkit">[pl]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UserRegistration">[pl]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization / social media specific credentials</string>
  <string name="RA_Coco_Version">[pl]App Info</string>
  <string name="RA_ConnectivityScreen_Title">Możliwości połączeń</string>
  <string name="RA_DLSS_avatar_default_text">[pl]Hello User, \nPlease sign in.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Philips_Shop">[pl]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Support_screen_sub">[pl]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions, product information and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_HomeScreen_Title">[pl]Reference App Home</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_copyright">[pl]Copyright \u00A9 2017 Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_description">[pl]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_privacy">[pl]Privacy policy</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_terms">[pl]Terms &amp;amp;amp; conditions</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_check_internet_connectivity">[pl]Check Internet Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_data_fetch_error">[pl]Not able to fetch data</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_data_fetch_wait">[pl]Wait..While we fetch your sleep data from device</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_enable_bluetooth">[pl]Please enable bluetooth</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_healthy_sleep_title">[pl]Healthy Sleep Score</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_sub_text">[pl]ReferenceApp is a base platform used by all propositions to develop and maintain features both generic and specific to the propositions. App infra, Data Gateway, App FWK, and UIToolkit allow Apps to be created from uApps and UI-less services/libraries. ReferenceApp acts as a foundation over which CDP2 uApps and proposition specific uApps are integrated to form individual apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_text">[pl]Reference App</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_insights_error">[pl]Error loading Insights</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_no_internet_connectivity">[pl]Internet connection is not available</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_sub_text">[pl]This app integrates the common components required to develop new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_title">[pl]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_sub_text">[pl]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_title">[pl]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_sub_text">[pl]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_title">[pl]What is in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_sub_text">[pl]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_title">[pl]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_sub_text">[pl]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_title">[pl]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_sub_text">[pl]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_title">[pl]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_sub_text">[pl]The Security &amp;amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rule.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_title">[pl]Secure &amp;amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_sub_text">[pl]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_title">[pl]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_sub_text">[pl]&lt;html&gt;The CDP&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;2&lt;small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;sup&gt; platform is fully integrated with HSDP and IT to ensure all functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_title">[pl]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_overlay_got_it">[pl]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_actual">[pl]Actual</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_connectivity">[pl]PowerSleep Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_deep_sleep_title">[pl]Time spent in deep sleep</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_default_data">[pl]--</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_ideal_deep_sleep">[pl](Ideal 120 mins)</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_ideal_sleep_time">[pl](Ideal 450-540 mins)</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_percentage_label">[pl]of 100</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_time_sleep">[pl]Time asleep</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_ps_tips_title">[pl]Tips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_sleep_element">[pl]Sleep element</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_splash_title">[pl]&lt;html&gt;&lt;b&gt;CDP&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;2&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Reference App&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_theme_title">[pl]Theme Setting</string>
  <string name="RA_Demo_Menu_Title">[pl]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_Done_Button_Text">Gotowe</string>
  <string name="RA_Empty_Invalid_Data">Pole danych jest puste lub nieprawidłowe</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Body_Text">W treści umieszczony jest duży tekst dla konkretnej propozycji </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Header_Text">W tym miejscu umieszczony jest tytuł dla konkretnej propozycji </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Menu_Title">Ekran główny aplikacji mobilnej</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Title">Ekran główny aplikacji mobilnej</string>
  <string name="RA_Invalid_Param_Msg">Wprowadzono lub wybrano nieprawidłowe wartości parametrów. Wybierz odpowiednie wartości parametrów i uruchom ponownie</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Binary_Hosting_Consent">[pl]I allow Philips to store binary data</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Click_Stream_Hosting_Consent">[pl]I allow Philips to use my mobile application usage statistics</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Coaching_Consent">[pl]I allow Philips to use my data for Coaching purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Binary_Help_Text">[pl]The actual content of the binary consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream">Zezwalam firmie Philips na gromadzenie moich danych z aplikacji w celu usprawnienia jej działania, personalizacji, integracji z mediami społecznościowymi oraz wyświetlania odpowiednich treści i reklam.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream_Help_Text">Oświadczenie o plikach cookie\n\nTa aplikacja wykorzystuje usługę analityczną Adobe Analytics („Adobe Analytics”) świadczoną przez Adobe Systems Software Ireland Limited („Adobe”). Adobe Analytics wykorzystuje pliki cookie (pliki tekstowe) lub podobne techniki zastosowane w aplikacji użytkownika, aby pomóc aplikacji w analizowaniu zachodzących w niej ogólnych cykli związanych z ruchem sieciowym. W trakcie przesyłania do Adobe generowanych przez pliki cookie informacji na temat użytkowania aplikacji odpowiednie ustawienie powoduje, że adres IP jest anonimizowany przed uruchomieniem procesu geolokalizacji oraz zmieniany na ogólny adres IP przed archiwizacją. W imieniu firmy Philips Adobe będzie korzystać z tych informacji w celu oceny użytkowania aplikacji, tworzenia raportów aktywności aplikacji dla firmy Philips oraz świadczenia firmie Philips innych usług związanych z aktywnością i użytkowaniem aplikacji. Firma Adobe nie będzie łączyła adresu IP użytkownika z żadnymi innymi danymi będącymi w jej posiadaniu. Użytkownik może zapobiec gromadzeniu i korzystaniu z informacji (pliki cookie i adres IP) przez firmy Adobe i Philips, jeśli nie wyraża na to zgody — należy wybrać odpowiednią opcję po zamknięciu tego okna.\n</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Coaching_Help_Text">[pl]The actual content of the coaching consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Marketing_Help_Text">Wyrażenie zgody oznacza, że spółki grupy Philips mogą kontaktować się z Tobą w celu dostarczenia komunikatów promocyjnych za pośrednictwem poczty elektronicznej, wiadomości SMS i innych kanałów cyfrowych, takich jak aplikacje mobilne i media społecznościowe. Możemy analizować i łączyć Twoje dane osobowe w celu dostosowania komunikatów do Twoich preferencji i zachowań, a tym samym zapewnienia optymalnie spersonalizowanych usług. Dane te mogą obejmować: \n\nDane przekazywane nam przez Ciebie\nDane, które chcesz nam aktywnie udostępniać, takie jak imię i nazwisko, data urodzenia lub wiek, adres e-mail, adres zamieszkania, kraj, płeć, numer telefonu czy profil społecznościowy.\n\nDane uzyskiwane w ramach interakcji z firmą Philips\nDane dotyczące interakcji i korzystania z kanałów cyfrowych Philips, takich jak media społecznościowe, strony internetowe, wiadomości e-mail, aplikacje i połączone produkty. Dane te mogą zawierać: adres IP, pliki cookie, informacje o urządzeniu, kliknięte komunikaty, szczegóły na temat lokalizacji i odwiedzone strony internetowe.\n\nFirma Philips umożliwia wycofanie zgody w dowolnym momencie.\nAby uzyskać więcej informacji, zapoznaj się z oświadczeniami firmy Philips o prywatności i o plikach cookie.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Moment_Help_Text">[pl]The actual content of the moment consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Research_Analytics_Help_Text">[pl]The actual content of the research and analytics consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Moment_Consent">[pl]I allow Philips to store my data in cloud</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Research_Analytics_Consent">[pl]I allow Philips to use my data for Research and Analytics purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_Menu_title_Demo">[pl]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_NO_Order_History">Historia zamówień niedostępna</string>
  <string name="RA_OK">OK</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Dismiss">[pl]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Shop_Text">[pl]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Support_Text">[pl]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions product informations and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Benefit_Text">Przedłuż swoją gwarancję o 24 miesiące.\nSkorzystaj z 10-procentowej zniżki na zakupy w sklepie firmy Philips.\nOdbierz bezpłatne akcesoria do produktów</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Email_Text">Na Twój adres e-mail wysłano wiadomość z umową dotyczącą przedłużonej gwarancji</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Extentende_Warranty">Okres gwarancji został przedłużony do przyszłego roku</string>
  <string name="RA_Philips_Shop_Menu_Title">Sklep Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_Product_Registration_Text">Rejestracja produktu</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_ACTIVATE_SCREEN_LOCK">[pl]Activate screenlock</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_DONT_SHOW_MESSAGE">[pl]Do not show this message again</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[pl]We’ve detected that you have rooted the device or jailbroken, thereby making it easier for others to access your data and no security on your application data.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_NO_THANKS">[pl]No thanks</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_PASSCODE_AND_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[pl]We’ve detected that you have jailbroken and not activated screenlock, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SCREEN_LOCK">[pl]We’ve detected the screenlock of your mobile phone is to enabled, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SECURE_YOUR_DATA">[pl]Secure your data</string>
  <string name="RA_See_a_doctor_Menu_Title">[pl]See a doctor</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title">Otrzymuj informacje promocyjne od firmy Philips w oparciu o swoje preferencje i zachowania w Internecie</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title_Only">[pl]Receive Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_SettingsScreen_Title">Ustawienia konta</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Login">Zaloguj</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout">Wyloguj</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout_Alert">Czy na pewno chcesz się wylogować?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_MyAccount">Moje konto</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_OrderHistory">Historia zamówienia</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Promo_Question_Text">Co to oznacza?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Purchases">Zakupy</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Screen_Header_Title">Ustawienia</string>
  <string name="RA_Skip_Button_Text">Pomijanie</string>
  <string name="RA_SplashScreen_Title">Aplikacje mobilne</string>
  <string name="RA_SupportScreen_Title">Pomoc techniczna</string>
  <string name="RA_Support_Menu_Title">Pomoc techniczna</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert">Zmień konfigurację</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert_Msg">Konfigurację można zmienić tylko w momencie uruchomienia. Aby dokonać zmian w aplikacji, trzeba ją uruchomić ponownie</string>
  <string name="RA_Update_Userdata_Error">Podczas aktualizacji danych użytkownika wystąpił błąd. Spróbuj za jakiś czas</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_A">Ustawienie A aplikacji pionowej</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_B">Ustawienie B aplikacji pionowej</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_C">Ustawienie C aplikacji pionowej</string>
  <string name="RA_Warning">OSTRZEŻENIE</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Text">[pl]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Title">[pl]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Text">[pl]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 Platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Title">[pl]What\'s in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Text">[pl]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Title">[pl]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Text">[pl]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Title">[pl]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Text">[pl]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Title">[pl]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Text">[pl]The Security &amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rules.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Title">[pl]Secure &amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Text">[pl]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Title">[pl]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Text">[pl]Functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Title">[pl]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro">[pl]This app integrates the common components to development new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro_Title">[pl]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_You_are_not_LoggedIn">Nie jesteś zalogowany. Przejdź do ustawień i zaloguj się</string>
  <string name="RA_change_config_desc">[pl]Configuration can only be changed at launch time. You need to relaunch the app to change it.</string>
  <string name="RA_loading_articles">[pl]Loading Article</string>
  <string name="RA_reference_device_scan">Skan. urządzenia referencyjnego</string>
  <string name="RA_something_wrong">Wystąpił błąd</string>
  <string name="chapters">[pl]Chapters</string>
  <string name="common_components">[pl]Common Components</string>
  <string name="description_close">[pl]Close</string>
  <string name="label_last_synced">[pl]Last updated: %1$s</string>
  <string name="label_last_synced_default">[pl]Last updated: No update yet</string>
  <string name="label_sleep_time_format">[pl]%d mins</string>
  <string name="label_sleep_tips">[pl]How can I improve my sleep score?</string>
  <string name="mya_config_tab">[pl]Configuration tab</string>
</resources>
