<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  Copyright (c) Koninklijke Philips N.V., 2018
  All rights are reserved. Reproduction or dissemination
  in whole or in part is prohibited without the prior written
  consent of the copyright holder.
  -->


<resources>
  <string name="BA_Add_Edit_Temp">Tilføj eller rediger temperatur </string>
  <string name="BA_AppFramework">AppFramework </string>
  <string name="BA_HSDP_login_not_available">HSDP-login ikke tilgængeligt</string>
  <string name="BA_Sync_Settings">Synkroniseringsindstillinger</string>
  <string name="RA_AboutScreen_Title">Om</string>
  <string name="RA_About_App_Version">Version</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Description_New">[da]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Menu_Title">Om</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra">[da]ail : App Infrastructure Library</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra_desc">[da]AppInfra is the components top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC">[da]dcc : Consumer Care</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC_desc">[da]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_Connectivity">[da]cml : CommLib</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_Connectivity_desc">[da]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_DS">[da]dsc : Data Services</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_DS_desc">[da]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data -\n&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP">[da]iap : In-app Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP_desc">[da]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR">[da]prg : Product Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR_desc">[da]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UIKIT">[da]uit : Mobile UI Toolkit Non DLS</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UIKIT_desc">[da]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR">[da]usr : User Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR_desc">[da]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization social media specific credentials.</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsDescription">[da]\"Special offers, promotions and first hand information about new product releases.\nTailored for you!\n\nJoin 140.000 of your peers now!\"</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsTitle">[da]What do we have to offer?</string>
  <string name="RA_Cancel">Annuller</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_AppInfra">[da]AppInfra is the component\'s top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_Connectivity">[da]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ConsumerCare">[da]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_DataServices">[da]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data: Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_InAppPurchase">[da]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ProductRegistration">[da]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UIToolkit">[da]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UserRegistration">[da]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization / social media specific credentials</string>
  <string name="RA_Coco_Version">[da]App Info</string>
  <string name="RA_ConnectivityScreen_Title">Tilslutningsmuligheder</string>
  <string name="RA_DLSS_avatar_default_text">[da]Hello User, \nPlease sign in.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Philips_Shop">[da]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Support_screen_sub">[da]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions, product information and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_HomeScreen_Title">[da]Reference App Home</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_copyright">[da]Copyright \u00A9 2017 Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_description">[da]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_privacy">[da]Privacy policy</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_terms">[da]Terms &amp;amp;amp; conditions</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_check_internet_connectivity">[da]Check Internet Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_data_fetch_error">[da]Not able to fetch data</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_data_fetch_wait">[da]Wait..While we fetch your sleep data from device</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_enable_bluetooth">[da]Please enable bluetooth</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_healthy_sleep_title">[da]Healthy Sleep Score</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_sub_text">[da]ReferenceApp is a base platform used by all propositions to develop and maintain features both generic and specific to the propositions. App infra, Data Gateway, App FWK, and UIToolkit allow Apps to be created from uApps and UI-less services/libraries. ReferenceApp acts as a foundation over which CDP2 uApps and proposition specific uApps are integrated to form individual apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_text">[da]Reference App</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_insights_error">[da]Error loading Insights</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_no_internet_connectivity">[da]Internet connection is not available</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_sub_text">[da]This app integrates the common components required to develop new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_title">[da]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_sub_text">[da]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_title">[da]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_sub_text">[da]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_title">[da]What is in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_sub_text">[da]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_title">[da]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_sub_text">[da]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_title">[da]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_sub_text">[da]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_title">[da]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_sub_text">[da]The Security &amp;amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rule.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_title">[da]Secure &amp;amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_sub_text">[da]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_title">[da]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_sub_text">[da]&lt;html&gt;The CDP&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;2&lt;small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;sup&gt; platform is fully integrated with HSDP and IT to ensure all functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_title">[da]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_overlay_got_it">[da]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_actual">[da]Actual</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_connectivity">[da]PowerSleep Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_deep_sleep_title">[da]Time spent in deep sleep</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_default_data">[da]--</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_ideal_deep_sleep">[da](Ideal 120 mins)</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_ideal_sleep_time">[da](Ideal 450-540 mins)</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_percentage_label">[da]of 100</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_time_sleep">[da]Time asleep</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_ps_tips_title">[da]Tips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_sleep_element">[da]Sleep element</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_splash_title">[da]&lt;html&gt;&lt;b&gt;CDP&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;2&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Reference App&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_theme_title">[da]Theme Setting</string>
  <string name="RA_Demo_Menu_Title">[da]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_Done_Button_Text">Udført</string>
  <string name="RA_Empty_Invalid_Data">Datafelt er tomt eller ugyldigt</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Body_Text">Tilbudsspecifik stor tekst skal stå i brødteksten </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Header_Text">Tilbudsspecifik titel her </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Menu_Title">Startside for mobilapp</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Title">Startside for mobilapp</string>
  <string name="RA_Invalid_Param_Msg">Du har indtastet eller valgt ugyldige parameterværdier. Vælg korrekte parameterværdier, og start igen</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Binary_Hosting_Consent">[da]I allow Philips to store binary data</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Click_Stream_Hosting_Consent">[da]I allow Philips to use my mobile application usage statistics</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Coaching_Consent">[da]I allow Philips to use my data for Coaching purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Binary_Help_Text">[da]The actual content of the binary consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream">Jeg giver Philips tilladelse til at indsamle oplysninger om appen for at understøtte appens funktion, for at forbedre appen, for at muliggøre integration med sociale medier og for at vise relevant indhold og relevante annoncer.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream_Help_Text">Meddelelse om cookies\n\nDenne App bruger Adobe Analytics, en analysetjeneste (\"Adobe Analytics\"), der leveres af Adobe Systems Software Ireland Limited (\"Adobe\"). Adobe Analytics anvender \"cookies\" eller lignende teknikker, dvs. tekstfiler placeret i din App, for at hjælpe Appen med at analysere de generelle trafikmønstre. Når du overfører oplysningerne fra cookien om brug af Appen til Adobe, anonymiseres IP-adressen før registreringen af din geografiske placering og erstattes af en generisk IP-adresse, før oplysningerne gemmes. På vegne af Philips bruger Adobe disse oplysninger til at evaluere, hvordan du bruger Appen, til at udarbejde rapporter til Philips om appaktivitet og til at levere andre tjenester, som har med appaktivitet og brug af Appen at gøre, til Philips. Adobe knytter ikke din IP-adresse til andre oplysninger, som indehaves af Adobe. Du kan forhindre Adobe og Philips i at indsamle og gøre brug af oplysninger (cookies og IP-adresse), hvis du fravælger det, når du lukker dette skærmbillede.\n</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Coaching_Help_Text">[da]The actual content of the coaching consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Marketing_Help_Text">Som et resultat af dit samtykke må Philips\' koncernselskaber kontakte dig med salgsfremmende kommunikation via e-mail, sms og andre digitale kanaler, såsom mobilapps og sociale medier. For at kunne tilpasse kommunikationen til dine præferencer og din adfærd og give dig den bedste personlige oplevelse må vi analysere og kombinere dine personlige oplysninger. Disse oplysninger kan omfatte: \n\nOplysninger, som du deler med os\nOplysninger, som du aktivt ønsker at dele med os, f.eks.: dit navn, din fødselsdato eller alder, din e-mailadresse, fysiske adresse, dit land, køn, telefonnummer og din profil på sociale medier.\n\nOplysninger, som vi får via dine interaktioner med Philips\nOplysninger om dine interaktioner med og brug af Philips\' digitale kanaler, såsom sociale medier, hjemmesider, e-mails, apps og tilknyttede produkter. Disse oplysninger kan indeholde: IP-adresse, cookies, enhedsoplysninger, kommunikation, som du klikker på, placeringsoplysninger og hjemmesider, du besøger\n\nPhilips giver dig mulighed for at tilbagekalde dit samtykke til enhver tid.\nDu kan få flere oplysninger ved at læse Philips\' meddelelse om beskyttelse af personlige oplysninger og Philips\' meddelelse om brugen af cookies.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Moment_Help_Text">[da]The actual content of the moment consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Research_Analytics_Help_Text">[da]The actual content of the research and analytics consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Moment_Consent">[da]I allow Philips to store my data in cloud</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Research_Analytics_Consent">[da]I allow Philips to use my data for Research and Analytics purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_Menu_title_Demo">[da]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_NO_Order_History">Ordrehistorik ikke tilgængelig</string>
  <string name="RA_OK">OK</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Dismiss">[da]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Shop_Text">[da]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Support_Text">[da]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions product informations and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Benefit_Text">Udvid din garanti med 24 måneder.\nFå 10 % rabat i Philips-butikken.\nFå gratis produkttilbehør</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Email_Text">Vi har sendt en e-mail til din e-mailadresse med kontrakten vedr. din forlængede garanti</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Extentende_Warranty">Din garantiperiode er blevet forlænget til næste år</string>
  <string name="RA_Philips_Shop_Menu_Title">Philips-butik</string>
  <string name="RA_Product_Registration_Text">Registrer dit produkt</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_ACTIVATE_SCREEN_LOCK">[da]Activate screenlock</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_DONT_SHOW_MESSAGE">[da]Do not show this message again</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[da]We’ve detected that you have rooted the device or jailbroken, thereby making it easier for others to access your data and no security on your application data.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_NO_THANKS">[da]No thanks</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_PASSCODE_AND_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[da]We’ve detected that you have jailbroken and not activated screenlock, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SCREEN_LOCK">[da]We’ve detected the screenlock of your mobile phone is to enabled, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SECURE_YOUR_DATA">[da]Secure your data</string>
  <string name="RA_See_a_doctor_Menu_Title">[da]See a doctor</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title">Modtag Philips\' markedsføringsmateriale på baggrund af mine præferencer og min onlineadfærd</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title_Only">[da]Receive Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Login">Log ind</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout">Log af</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout_Alert">Er du sikker på, at du vil logge af?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_MyAccount">Min konto</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_OrderHistory">Ordrehistorik</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Promo_Question_Text">Hvad betyder dette?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Purchases">Køb</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Screen_Header_Title">Indstillinger</string>
  <string name="RA_Skip_Button_Text">Skip</string>
  <string name="RA_SplashScreen_Title">Mobilapps</string>
  <string name="RA_SupportScreen_Title">Support</string>
  <string name="RA_Support_Menu_Title">Support</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert">Skift konfiguration</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert_Msg">Konfigurationen kan kun ændres på opstartstidspunktet. Du skal genstarte appen for at ændre den</string>
  <string name="RA_Update_Userdata_Error">Der opstod en fejl under opdatering af brugerdata. Prøv igen senere</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_A">Lodret app-indstilling A</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_B">Lodret app-indstilling B</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_C">Lodret app-indstilling C</string>
  <string name="RA_Warning">ADVARSEL</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Text">[da]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Title">[da]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Text">[da]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 Platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Title">[da]What\'s in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Text">[da]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Title">[da]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Text">[da]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Title">[da]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Text">[da]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Title">[da]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Text">[da]The Security &amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rules.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Title">[da]Secure &amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Text">[da]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Title">[da]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Text">[da]Functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Title">[da]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro">[da]This app integrates the common components to development new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro_Title">[da]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_You_are_not_LoggedIn">Du er ikke logget på. Gå til Indstillinger, og log på</string>
  <string name="RA_change_config_desc">[da]Configuration can only be changed at launch time. You need to relaunch the app to change it.</string>
  <string name="RA_loading_articles">[da]Loading Article</string>
  <string name="RA_reference_device_scan">Scanning af referenceenhed</string>
  <string name="RA_something_wrong">Noget gik galt</string>
  <string name="chapters">[da]Chapters</string>
  <string name="common_components">[da]Common Components</string>
  <string name="description_close">[da]Close</string>
  <string name="label_last_synced">[da]Last updated: %1$s</string>
  <string name="label_last_synced_default">[da]Last updated: No update yet</string>
  <string name="label_sleep_time_format">[da]%d mins</string>
  <string name="label_sleep_tips">[da]How can I improve my sleep score?</string>
  <string name="mya_config_tab">[da]Configuration tab</string>
</resources>
