<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  Copyright (c) Koninklijke Philips N.V., 2018
  All rights are reserved. Reproduction or dissemination
  in whole or in part is prohibited without the prior written
  consent of the copyright holder.
  -->


<resources>
  <string name="BA_Add_Edit_Temp">Agregar o editar la temperatura </string>
  <string name="BA_AppFramework">AppFramework </string>
  <string name="BA_HSDP_login_not_available">El inicio de sesión HSDP no está disponible</string>
  <string name="BA_Sync_Settings">Ajustes de sincronización</string>
  <string name="RA_AboutScreen_Title">Acerca de</string>
  <string name="RA_About_App_Version">Versión</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Description_New">[es-MX]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Menu_Title">Acerca de</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra">[es-MX]ail : App Infrastructure Library</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra_desc">[es-MX]AppInfra is the components top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC">[es-MX]dcc : Consumer Care</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC_desc">[es-MX]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_Connectivity">[es-MX]cml : CommLib</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_Connectivity_desc">[es-MX]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_DS">[es-MX]dsc : Data Services</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_DS_desc">[es-MX]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data -\n&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP">[es-MX]iap : In-app Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP_desc">[es-MX]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR">[es-MX]prg : Product Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR_desc">[es-MX]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UIKIT">[es-MX]uit : Mobile UI Toolkit Non DLS</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UIKIT_desc">[es-MX]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR">[es-MX]usr : User Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR_desc">[es-MX]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization social media specific credentials.</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsDescription">[es-MX]\"Special offers, promotions and first hand information about new product releases.\nTailored for you!\n\nJoin 140.000 of your peers now!\"</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsTitle">[es-MX]What do we have to offer?</string>
  <string name="RA_Cancel">Cancelar</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_AppInfra">[es-MX]AppInfra is the component\'s top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_Connectivity">[es-MX]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ConsumerCare">[es-MX]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_DataServices">[es-MX]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data: Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_InAppPurchase">[es-MX]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ProductRegistration">[es-MX]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UIToolkit">[es-MX]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UserRegistration">[es-MX]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization / social media specific credentials</string>
  <string name="RA_Coco_Version">[es-MX]App Info</string>
  <string name="RA_ConnectivityScreen_Title">Conectividad</string>
  <string name="RA_DLSS_avatar_default_text">[es-MX]Hello User, \nPlease sign in.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Philips_Shop">[es-MX]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Support_screen_sub">[es-MX]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions, product information and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_HomeScreen_Title">[es-MX]Reference App Home</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_copyright">[es-MX]Copyright \u00A9 2017 Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_description">[es-MX]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_privacy">[es-MX]Privacy policy</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_terms">[es-MX]Terms &amp;amp;amp; conditions</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_check_internet_connectivity">[es-MX]Check Internet Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_data_fetch_error">[es-MX]Not able to fetch data</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_data_fetch_wait">[es-MX]Wait..While we fetch your sleep data from device</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_enable_bluetooth">[es-MX]Please enable bluetooth</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_healthy_sleep_title">[es-MX]Healthy Sleep Score</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_sub_text">[es-MX]ReferenceApp is a base platform used by all propositions to develop and maintain features both generic and specific to the propositions. App infra, Data Gateway, App FWK, and UIToolkit allow Apps to be created from uApps and UI-less services/libraries. ReferenceApp acts as a foundation over which CDP2 uApps and proposition specific uApps are integrated to form individual apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_text">[es-MX]Reference App</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_insights_error">[es-MX]Error loading Insights</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_no_internet_connectivity">[es-MX]Internet connection is not available</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_sub_text">[es-MX]This app integrates the common components required to develop new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_title">[es-MX]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_sub_text">[es-MX]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_title">[es-MX]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_sub_text">[es-MX]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_title">[es-MX]What is in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_sub_text">[es-MX]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_title">[es-MX]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_sub_text">[es-MX]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_title">[es-MX]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_sub_text">[es-MX]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_title">[es-MX]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_sub_text">[es-MX]The Security &amp;amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rule.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_title">[es-MX]Secure &amp;amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_sub_text">[es-MX]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_title">[es-MX]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_sub_text">[es-MX]&lt;html&gt;The CDP&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;2&lt;small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;sup&gt; platform is fully integrated with HSDP and IT to ensure all functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_title">[es-MX]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_overlay_got_it">[es-MX]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_actual">[es-MX]Actual</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_connectivity">[es-MX]PowerSleep Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_deep_sleep_title">[es-MX]Time spent in deep sleep</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_default_data">[es-MX]--</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_ideal_deep_sleep">[es-MX](Ideal 120 mins)</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_ideal_sleep_time">[es-MX](Ideal 450-540 mins)</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_percentage_label">[es-MX]of 100</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_time_sleep">[es-MX]Time asleep</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_ps_tips_title">[es-MX]Tips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_sleep_element">[es-MX]Sleep element</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_splash_title">[es-MX]&lt;html&gt;&lt;b&gt;CDP&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;2&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Reference App&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_theme_title">[es-MX]Theme Setting</string>
  <string name="RA_Demo_Menu_Title">[es-MX]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_Done_Button_Text">Listo</string>
  <string name="RA_Empty_Invalid_Data">El campo de datos está vacío o no es válido</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Body_Text">El texto grande específico para la proposición va en el contenido </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Header_Text">El título específico para la proposición va aquí </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Menu_Title">Inicio de la aplicación móvil</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Title">Inicio de la aplicación móvil</string>
  <string name="RA_Invalid_Param_Msg">Ingresó o seleccionó valores de parámetro no válidos. Seleccione los valores de los parámetros apropiados e inicie de nuevo</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Binary_Hosting_Consent">[es-MX]I allow Philips to store binary data</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Click_Stream_Hosting_Consent">[es-MX]I allow Philips to use my mobile application usage statistics</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Coaching_Consent">[es-MX]I allow Philips to use my data for Coaching purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Binary_Help_Text">[es-MX]The actual content of the binary consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream">Doy mi autorización para que Philips recopile mis datos de aplicación con el fin de que la aplicación funcione de mejor manera, se personalice, se integre con las redes sociales y muestre contenido y publicidad pertinentes.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream_Help_Text">Aviso de cookies\n\nEsta aplicación utiliza Adobe Analytics, un servicio de análisis (“Adobe Analytics”) proporcionado por Adobe Systems Software Ireland Limited (“Adobe”). Este servicio utiliza “cookies” u otras técnicas similares, que corresponden a archivos de texto integrados en la aplicación, con el fin de que la aplicación analice patrones de tráfico generales mediante nuestra aplicación. A través de la transmisión de información generada por la cookie con respecto al uso de la aplicación a Adobe, la configuración garantiza que la dirección IP se anonimice antes de la geolocalización y se reemplazará por una dirección IP genérica antes del almacenamiento. Adobe, en nombre de Philips, utilizará esta información para evaluar tu uso de la aplicación y generará informes sobre la actividad de la aplicación para Philips con el fin de proporcionar otros servicios relacionados con la actividad y el uso de la aplicación a Philips. Adobe no asociará tu dirección IP con ningún otro dato administrado por Adobe. Puedes evitar que Adobe y Philips recopilen y usen datos (cookies y dirección IP) si dejas de participar después de cerrar esta pantalla.\n</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Coaching_Help_Text">[es-MX]The actual content of the coaching consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Marketing_Help_Text">Tras otorgar tu autorización, es posible que las empresas del grupo Philips se comuniquen contigo para enviarte comunicaciones promocionales a través de correo electrónico, SMS y otros medios digitales, tales como aplicaciones móviles y redes sociales. Para personalizar las comunicaciones según tus preferencias y comportamiento, y ofrecerte la mejor experiencia personalizada, es posible que analicemos y combinemos tus datos personales. Entre estos datos se pueden incluir los siguientes: \n\nLos datos que nos entregaste\nLos datos que desees compartir activamente con nosotros, como tu nombre, fecha de nacimiento o edad, dirección de correo electrónico, dirección postal, país, sexo, número de teléfono o perfil en medios sociales.\n\nLos datos que obtenemos de tus interacciones con Philips\nLos datos acerca de tus interacciones y el uso de los canales digitales de Philips, tales como redes sociales, sitios web, correos electrónicos, aplicaciones y productos conectados. Entre estos datos se pueden incluir los siguientes: dirección IP, cookies, información de dispositivos, comunicaciones en las que debe hacer clic, detalles de ubicaciones y sitios web que visites\n\nPhilips te da la oportunidad de retirar tu consentimiento en cualquier momento.\nPara obtener más información, consulta el aviso de privacidad y el aviso de cookies de Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Moment_Help_Text">[es-MX]The actual content of the moment consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Research_Analytics_Help_Text">[es-MX]The actual content of the research and analytics consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Moment_Consent">[es-MX]I allow Philips to store my data in cloud</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Research_Analytics_Consent">[es-MX]I allow Philips to use my data for Research and Analytics purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_Menu_title_Demo">[es-MX]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_NO_Order_History">El historial de pedidos no está disponible</string>
  <string name="RA_OK">OK</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Dismiss">[es-MX]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Shop_Text">[es-MX]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Support_Text">[es-MX]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions product informations and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Benefit_Text">Aumente su garantía en 24 meses.\nRecibirá un 10% de descuento en la tienda de Philips.\nRecibirá accesorios del producto gratuitamente</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Email_Text">Se envió un correo electrónico con el contrato de la garantía extendida a su dirección de correo electrónico</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Extentende_Warranty">Se ha extendido el período de garantía hasta el próximo año</string>
  <string name="RA_Philips_Shop_Menu_Title">Tienda Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_Product_Registration_Text">Registrar producto</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_ACTIVATE_SCREEN_LOCK">[es-MX]Activate screenlock</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_DONT_SHOW_MESSAGE">[es-MX]Do not show this message again</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[es-MX]We’ve detected that you have rooted the device or jailbroken, thereby making it easier for others to access your data and no security on your application data.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_NO_THANKS">[es-MX]No thanks</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_PASSCODE_AND_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[es-MX]We’ve detected that you have jailbroken and not activated screenlock, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SCREEN_LOCK">[es-MX]We’ve detected the screenlock of your mobile phone is to enabled, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SECURE_YOUR_DATA">[es-MX]Secure your data</string>
  <string name="RA_See_a_doctor_Menu_Title">[es-MX]See a doctor</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title">Recibir información promocional de Philips según mis preferencias y comportamientos en línea</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title_Only">[es-MX]Receive Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Login">Iniciar sesión</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout">Cerrar sesión</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout_Alert">¿Está seguro de que desea cerrar la sesión?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_MyAccount">Mi cuenta</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_OrderHistory">Historial de pedidos</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Promo_Question_Text">¿Qué significa?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Purchases">Compras</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Screen_Header_Title">Ajustes</string>
  <string name="RA_Skip_Button_Text">Salto</string>
  <string name="RA_SplashScreen_Title">Aplicaciones móviles</string>
  <string name="RA_SupportScreen_Title">Asistencia técnica</string>
  <string name="RA_Support_Menu_Title">Asistencia técnica</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert">Cambiar la configuración</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert_Msg">Solo se puede cambiar la configuración durante el inicio. Debe iniciar la aplicación de nuevo para cambiarlo</string>
  <string name="RA_Update_Userdata_Error">Se produjo un error durante la actualización de datos del usuario. Inténtelo de nuevo más tarde</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_A">Ajustes de la aplicación vertical A</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_B">Ajustes de la aplicación vertical B</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_C">Ajustes de la aplicación vertical C</string>
  <string name="RA_Warning">ADVERTENCIA</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Text">[es-MX]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Title">[es-MX]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Text">[es-MX]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 Platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Title">[es-MX]What\'s in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Text">[es-MX]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Title">[es-MX]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Text">[es-MX]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Title">[es-MX]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Text">[es-MX]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Title">[es-MX]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Text">[es-MX]The Security &amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rules.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Title">[es-MX]Secure &amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Text">[es-MX]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Title">[es-MX]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Text">[es-MX]Functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Title">[es-MX]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro">[es-MX]This app integrates the common components to development new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro_Title">[es-MX]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_You_are_not_LoggedIn">No ha iniciado sesión. Vaya a Ajustes e iníciela</string>
  <string name="RA_change_config_desc">[es-MX]Configuration can only be changed at launch time. You need to relaunch the app to change it.</string>
  <string name="RA_loading_articles">[es-MX]Loading Article</string>
  <string name="RA_reference_device_scan">Análisis del dispositivo de referencia</string>
  <string name="RA_something_wrong">Ocurrió un error</string>
  <string name="chapters">[es-MX]Chapters</string>
  <string name="common_components">[es-MX]Common Components</string>
  <string name="description_close">[es-MX]Close</string>
  <string name="label_last_synced">[es-MX]Last updated: %1$s</string>
  <string name="label_last_synced_default">[es-MX]Last updated: No update yet</string>
  <string name="label_sleep_time_format">[es-MX]%d mins</string>
  <string name="label_sleep_tips">[es-MX]How can I improve my sleep score?</string>
  <string name="mya_config_tab">[es-MX]Configuration tab</string>
</resources>
