<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  Copyright (c) Koninklijke Philips N.V., 2018
  All rights are reserved. Reproduction or dissemination
  in whole or in part is prohibited without the prior written
  consent of the copyright holder.
  -->


<resources>
  <string name="BA_Add_Edit_Temp">Sıcaklık Ekle veya Sıcaklığı Ayarla </string>
  <string name="BA_AppFramework">Uygulama Çerçevesi </string>
  <string name="BA_HSDP_login_not_available">HSDP oturum açma kullanılamıyor</string>
  <string name="BA_Sync_Settings">Senkronizasyon Ayarları</string>
  <string name="RA_AboutScreen_Title">Hakkında</string>
  <string name="RA_About_App_Version">Sürüm</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Description_New">[tr]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Menu_Title">Hakkında</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra">[tr]ail : App Infrastructure Library</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra_desc">[tr]AppInfra is the components top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC">[tr]dcc : Consumer Care</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC_desc">[tr]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_Connectivity">[tr]cml : CommLib</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_Connectivity_desc">[tr]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_DS">[tr]dsc : Data Services</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_DS_desc">[tr]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data -\n&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP">[tr]iap : In-app Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP_desc">[tr]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR">[tr]prg : Product Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR_desc">[tr]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UIKIT">[tr]uit : Mobile UI Toolkit Non DLS</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UIKIT_desc">[tr]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR">[tr]usr : User Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR_desc">[tr]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization social media specific credentials.</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsDescription">[tr]\"Special offers, promotions and first hand information about new product releases.\nTailored for you!\n\nJoin 140.000 of your peers now!\"</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsTitle">[tr]What do we have to offer?</string>
  <string name="RA_Cancel">İptal</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_AppInfra">[tr]AppInfra is the component\'s top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_Connectivity">[tr]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ConsumerCare">[tr]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_DataServices">[tr]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data: Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_InAppPurchase">[tr]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ProductRegistration">[tr]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UIToolkit">[tr]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UserRegistration">[tr]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization / social media specific credentials</string>
  <string name="RA_Coco_Version">[tr]App Info</string>
  <string name="RA_ConnectivityScreen_Title">Bağlantı</string>
  <string name="RA_DLSS_avatar_default_text">[tr]Hello User, \nPlease sign in.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Philips_Shop">[tr]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Support_screen_sub">[tr]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions, product information and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_HomeScreen_Title">[tr]Reference App Home</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_copyright">[tr]Copyright \u00A9 2017 Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_description">[tr]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_privacy">[tr]Privacy policy</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_terms">[tr]Terms &amp;amp;amp; conditions</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_check_internet_connectivity">[tr]Check Internet Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_data_fetch_error">[tr]Not able to fetch data</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_data_fetch_wait">[tr]Wait..While we fetch your sleep data from device</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_enable_bluetooth">[tr]Please enable bluetooth</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_healthy_sleep_title">[tr]Healthy Sleep Score</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_sub_text">[tr]ReferenceApp is a base platform used by all propositions to develop and maintain features both generic and specific to the propositions. App infra, Data Gateway, App FWK, and UIToolkit allow Apps to be created from uApps and UI-less services/libraries. ReferenceApp acts as a foundation over which CDP2 uApps and proposition specific uApps are integrated to form individual apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_text">[tr]RA_SettingsScreen_Title</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_insights_error">[tr]Error loading Insights</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_no_internet_connectivity">[tr]Internet connection is not available</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_sub_text">[tr]This app integrates the common components required to develop new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_title">[tr]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_sub_text">[tr]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_title">[tr]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_sub_text">[tr]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_title">[tr]What is in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_sub_text">[tr]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_title">[tr]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_sub_text">[tr]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_title">[tr]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_sub_text">[tr]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_title">[tr]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_sub_text">[tr]The Security &amp;amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rule.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_title">[tr]Secure &amp;amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_sub_text">[tr]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_title">[tr]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_sub_text">[tr]&lt;html&gt;The CDP&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;2&lt;small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;sup&gt; platform is fully integrated with HSDP and IT to ensure all functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_title">[tr]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_overlay_got_it">[tr]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_actual">[tr]Actual</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_connectivity">[tr]PowerSleep Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_deep_sleep_title">[tr]Time spent in deep sleep</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_default_data">[tr]--</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_ideal_deep_sleep">[tr](Ideal 120 mins)</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_ideal_sleep_time">[tr](Ideal 450-540 mins)</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_percentage_label">[tr]of 100</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_time_sleep">[tr]Time asleep</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_ps_tips_title">[tr]Tips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_sleep_element">[tr]Sleep element</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_splash_title">[tr]&lt;html&gt;&lt;b&gt;CDP&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;2&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Reference App&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_theme_title">[tr]Theme Setting</string>
  <string name="RA_Demo_Menu_Title">[tr]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_Done_Button_Text">Tamamlandı</string>
  <string name="RA_Empty_Invalid_Data">Veri alanı boş veya geçersiz</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Body_Text">Teklife bağlı büyük metni gövdeye ekleyin </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Header_Text">Teklife bağlı Başlığı buraya ekleyin </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Menu_Title">Mobil Uygulama giriş sayfası</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Title">Mobil Uygulama giriş sayfası</string>
  <string name="RA_Invalid_Param_Msg">Geçersiz parametre değerleri girdiniz veya seçtiniz. Lütfen uygun parametre değerlerini seçin ve tekrar başlatın</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Binary_Hosting_Consent">[tr]I allow Philips to store binary data</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Click_Stream_Hosting_Consent">[tr]I allow Philips to use my mobile application usage statistics</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Coaching_Consent">[tr]I allow Philips to use my data for Coaching purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Binary_Help_Text">[tr]The actual content of the binary consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Binary_Revoke_Warning_Text">[tr]By revoking consent your data will be deleted from our servers.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream">Philips\'in uygulamayı çalıştırmak, geliştirmek, kişiselleştirmek, sosyal medya ile entegre etmek ve uygulamada ilgili içerik ve reklamların gösterilmesini sağlamak amacıyla uygulama verilerimi toplamasına izin veriyorum.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream_Help_Text">Tanımlama Bilgisi Bildirimi\n\nBu Uygulama Adobe Systems Software Ireland Limited (\"Adobe\") tarafından sağlanan bir analiz hizmeti olan (\"Adobe Analytics\") Adobe Analytics\'i kullanır. Adobe Analytics, Uygulama\'nın, Uygulama\'daki genel trafik düzenini analiz etmesine yardımcı olmak amacıyla \"tanımlama bilgilerini\" veya Uygulama içine yerleştirilen metin dosyaları olan benzer teknikleri kullanır. Tanımlama bilgisi tarafından oluşturulan Uygulama kullanım verileri, Adobe\'ye aktarıldığında konum belirlenmeden önce IP adresi anonim hale getirilir ve depolama işleminden önce genel bir IP adresi ile değiştirilir. Adobe, Philips adına Uygulama kullanımınızı değerlendirmek amacıyla Philips\'e Uygulama etkinliği raporları derlemek ve Philips\'e Uygulama etkinliği ve kullanımına ilişkin başka hizmetler sunmak için bu bilgileri kullanır. Adobe, IP adresinizi Adobe\'de saklanan diğer verilerle ilişkilendirmez. Bu ekranı kapattıktan sonra izninizi geri alarak Adobe ve Philips tarafından verilerinizin (tanımlama bilgileri ve IP adresi) toplanmasını ve kullanılmasını önleyebilirsiniz.\n</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Clickstream_Revoke_Warning_Text">[tr]By revoking consent your data will be deleted from our servers.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Coaching_Help_Text">[tr]The actual content of the coaching consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Coaching_Revoke_Warning_Text">[tr]By revoking consent your data will be deleted from our servers.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Marketing_Help_Text">Onayınız doğrultusunda Philips şirketler grubu promosyon iletişimleri ile ilgili e-posta, SMS ve mobil uygulamalar ve sosyal medya gibi diğer dijital kanallar üzerinden sizinle iletişime geçebilir. İletişimleri tercihlerinize ve davranışlarınıza göre şekillendirmek ve sizlere en iyi kişiselleştirilmiş deneyimi sunmak için kişisel verilerinizi analiz edebilir ve birleştirebiliriz. Bu verilere şunlar dahildir: \n\nBize sağladığınız veriler\nBizimle aktif olarak paylaşmak istediğiniz veriler: adınız, doğum tarihiniz veya yaşınız, e-posta adresiniz, posta adresiniz, ülkeniz, cinsiyetiniz, telefon numaranız, sosyal medya profiliniz.\n\nPhilips ile olan etkileşimlerinizden elde ettiğimiz veriler\nSosyal medya, web siteleri, e-postalar, uygulamalar ve bağlı ürünler gibi Philips dijital kanallarıyla olan etkileşiminiz ve bu kanalları kullanımınıza ilişkin veriler. Bu verilere şunlar dahil olabilir: IP adresi, tanımlama bilgileri, cihaz bilgileri, tıkladığınız iletişimler, konum ayrıntıları ve ziyaret ettiğiniz web siteleri\n\nPhilips, her zaman onayınızı geri çekme fırsatı sunar.\nDaha fazla bilgi için lütfen Philips Gizlilik bildirimini ve Philips Tanımlama Bilgisi bildirimini okuyun.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Moment_Help_Text">[tr]The actual content of the moment consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Moments_Revoke_Warning_Text">[tr]By revoking consent your data will be deleted from our servers.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Research_Analytics_Help_Text">[tr]The actual content of the research and analytics consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Research_Analytics_Revoke_Warning_Text">[tr]By revoking consent your data will be deleted from our servers.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Moment_Consent">[tr]I allow Philips to store my data in cloud</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Research_Analytics_Consent">[tr]I allow Philips to use my data for Research and Analytics purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_Menu_title_Demo">[tr]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_NO_Order_History">Sipariş Geçmişi Kullanılamıyor</string>
  <string name="RA_OK">OK</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Dismiss">[tr]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Shop_Text">[tr]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Support_Text">[tr]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions product informations and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Benefit_Text">Garanti sürenizi 24 ay uzatın.\nPhilips mağazalarından %10 indirim kazanın.\nÜcretsiz ürün aksesuarları alın</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Email_Text">Genişletilmiş garanti sözleşmesi, e-posta adresinize gönderildi</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Extentende_Warranty">Garanti süreniz gelecek yıla kadar uzatıldı</string>
  <string name="RA_Philips_Shop_Menu_Title">Philips Mağaza</string>
  <string name="RA_Product_Registration_Text">Ürününüzü Kaydettirin</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_ACTIVATE_SCREEN_LOCK">[tr]Activate screenlock</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_DONT_SHOW_MESSAGE">[tr]Do not show this message again</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[tr]We’ve detected that you have rooted the device or jailbroken, thereby making it easier for others to access your data and no security on your application data.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_NO_THANKS">[tr]No thanks</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_PASSCODE_AND_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[tr]We’ve detected that you have jailbroken and not activated screenlock, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SCREEN_LOCK">[tr]We’ve detected the screenlock of your mobile phone is to enabled, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SECURE_YOUR_DATA">[tr]Secure your data</string>
  <string name="RA_See_a_doctor_Menu_Title">[tr]See a doctor</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title">Tercihlerime ve çevrimiçi davranışıma göre Philips\'in tanıtım amaçlı bildirimlerini al</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title_Only">[tr]Receive Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Login">Oturum Aç</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout">Oturumu Kapat</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout_Alert">Oturumu kapatmak istediğinizden emin misiniz?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_MyAccount">Hesabım</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_OrderHistory">Sipariş Geçmişi</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Promo_Question_Text">Bu ne anlama geliyor?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Purchases">Satın Almalar</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Screen_Header_Title">Ayarlar</string>
  <string name="RA_Skip_Button_Text">Atlama</string>
  <string name="RA_SplashScreen_Title">Mobil Uygulamalar</string>
  <string name="RA_SupportScreen_Title">Destek</string>
  <string name="RA_Support_Menu_Title">Destek</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert">Yapılandırmayı değiştir</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert_Msg">Yapılandırma yalnızca başlatma süresinde değiştirilebilir. Yapılandırmayı değiştirmek için uygulamayı yeniden başlatmanız gerekir</string>
  <string name="RA_Update_Userdata_Error">Kullanıcı Verileri güncellenirken bir hata oluştu. Lütfen bir süre sonra tekrar deneyin</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_A">Dikey Uygulama Ayarı A</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_B">Dikey Uygulama Ayarı B</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_C">Dikey Uygulama Ayarı C</string>
  <string name="RA_Warning">UYARI</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Text">[tr]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Title">[tr]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Text">[tr]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 Platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Title">[tr]What\'s in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Text">[tr]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Title">[tr]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Text">[tr]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Title">[tr]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Text">[tr]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Title">[tr]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Text">[tr]The Security &amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rules.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Title">[tr]Secure &amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Text">[tr]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Title">[tr]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Text">[tr]Functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Title">[tr]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro">[tr]This app integrates the common components to development new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro_Title">[tr]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_You_are_not_LoggedIn">Oturumunuz Açık Değil. Lütfen Ayarlar\'a gidip Oturum Açın</string>
  <string name="RA_change_config_desc">[tr]Configuration can only be changed at launch time. You need to relaunch the app to change it.</string>
  <string name="RA_loading_articles">[tr]Loading Article</string>
  <string name="RA_reference_device_scan">Referans Cihaz Taraması</string>
  <string name="RA_something_wrong">Bir sorun oluştu</string>
  <string name="chapters">[tr]Chapters</string>
  <string name="common_components">[tr]Common Components</string>
  <string name="description_close">[tr]Close</string>
  <string name="label_last_synced">[tr]Last updated: %1$s</string>
  <string name="label_last_synced_default">[tr]Last updated: No update yet</string>
  <string name="label_sleep_time_format">[tr]%d mins</string>
  <string name="label_sleep_tips">[tr]How can I improve my sleep score?</string>
  <string name="mya_config_tab">[tr]Configuration tab</string>
</resources>
