<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  Copyright (c) Koninklijke Philips N.V., 2018
  All rights are reserved. Reproduction or dissemination
  in whole or in part is prohibited without the prior written
  consent of the copyright holder.
  -->


<resources>
  <string name="BA_Add_Edit_Temp">Dodajte ili uredite temperaturu </string>
  <string name="BA_AppFramework">AppFramework </string>
  <string name="BA_HSDP_login_not_available">Prijava za HSDP nije dostupna</string>
  <string name="BA_Sync_Settings">Postavke sinkronizacije</string>
  <string name="RA_AboutScreen_Title">Više o</string>
  <string name="RA_About_App_Version">Verzija</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Description_New">[hr]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Menu_Title">Više o</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra">[hr]ail : App Infrastructure Library</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra_desc">[hr]AppInfra is the components top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC">[hr]dcc : Consumer Care</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC_desc">[hr]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_Connectivity">[hr]cml : CommLib</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_Connectivity_desc">[hr]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_DS">[hr]dsc : Data Services</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_DS_desc">[hr]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data -\n&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP">[hr]iap : In-app Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP_desc">[hr]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR">[hr]prg : Product Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR_desc">[hr]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UIKIT">[hr]uit : Mobile UI Toolkit Non DLS</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UIKIT_desc">[hr]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR">[hr]usr : User Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR_desc">[hr]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization social media specific credentials.</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsDescription">[hr]\"Special offers, promotions and first hand information about new product releases.\nTailored for you!\n\nJoin 140.000 of your peers now!\"</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsTitle">[hr]What do we have to offer?</string>
  <string name="RA_Cancel">Odustani</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_AppInfra">[hr]AppInfra is the component\'s top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_Connectivity">[hr]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ConsumerCare">[hr]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_DataServices">[hr]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data: Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_InAppPurchase">[hr]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ProductRegistration">[hr]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UIToolkit">[hr]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UserRegistration">[hr]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization / social media specific credentials</string>
  <string name="RA_Coco_Version">[hr]App Info</string>
  <string name="RA_ConnectivityScreen_Title">Mogućnost povezivanja</string>
  <string name="RA_DLSS_avatar_default_text">[hr]Hello User, \nPlease sign in.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Philips_Shop">[hr]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Support_screen_sub">[hr]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions, product information and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_HomeScreen_Title">[hr]Reference App Home</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_copyright">[hr]Copyright \u00A9 2017 Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_description">[hr]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_privacy">[hr]Privacy policy</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_terms">[hr]Terms &amp;amp;amp; conditions</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_check_internet_connectivity">[hr]Check Internet Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_data_fetch_error">[hr]Not able to fetch data</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_data_fetch_wait">[hr]Wait..While we fetch your sleep data from device</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_enable_bluetooth">[hr]Please enable bluetooth</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_healthy_sleep_title">[hr]Healthy Sleep Score</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_sub_text">[hr]ReferenceApp is a base platform used by all propositions to develop and maintain features both generic and specific to the propositions. App infra, Data Gateway, App FWK, and UIToolkit allow Apps to be created from uApps and UI-less services/libraries. ReferenceApp acts as a foundation over which CDP2 uApps and proposition specific uApps are integrated to form individual apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_text">[hr]Reference App</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_insights_error">[hr]Error loading Insights</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_no_internet_connectivity">[hr]Internet connection is not available</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_sub_text">[hr]This app integrates the common components required to develop new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_title">[hr]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_sub_text">[hr]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_title">[hr]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_sub_text">[hr]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_title">[hr]What is in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_sub_text">[hr]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_title">[hr]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_sub_text">[hr]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_title">[hr]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_sub_text">[hr]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_title">[hr]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_sub_text">[hr]The Security &amp;amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rule.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_title">[hr]Secure &amp;amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_sub_text">[hr]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_title">[hr]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_sub_text">[hr]&lt;html&gt;The CDP&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;2&lt;small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;sup&gt; platform is fully integrated with HSDP and IT to ensure all functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_title">[hr]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_overlay_got_it">[hr]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_actual">[hr]Actual</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_connectivity">[hr]PowerSleep Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_deep_sleep_title">[hr]Time spent in deep sleep</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_default_data">[hr]--</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_ideal_deep_sleep">[hr](Ideal 120 mins)</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_ideal_sleep_time">[hr](Ideal 450-540 mins)</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_percentage_label">[hr]of 100</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_time_sleep">[hr]Time asleep</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_ps_tips_title">[hr]Tips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_sleep_element">[hr]Sleep element</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_splash_title">[hr]&lt;html&gt;&lt;b&gt;CDP&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;2&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Reference App&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_theme_title">[hr]Theme Setting</string>
  <string name="RA_Demo_Menu_Title">[hr]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_Done_Button_Text">Gotovo</string>
  <string name="RA_Empty_Invalid_Data">Polje za podatke prazno je ili nije valjano</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Body_Text">Veliki tekst povezan s prijedlogom ide u tijelo teksta </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Header_Text">Naslov povezan s prijedlogom ide ovdje </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Menu_Title">Početna stranica aplikacije za mobilne uređaje</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Title">Početna stranica aplikacije za mobilne uređaje</string>
  <string name="RA_Invalid_Param_Msg">Unijeli ste ili odabrali vrijednosti parametra koje nisu valjane. Odaberite odgovarajuće vrijednosti parametra i pokrenite ponovo</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Binary_Hosting_Consent">[hr]I allow Philips to store binary data</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Click_Stream_Hosting_Consent">[hr]I allow Philips to use my mobile application usage statistics</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Coaching_Consent">[hr]I allow Philips to use my data for Coaching purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Binary_Help_Text">[hr]The actual content of the binary consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream">Dopuštam tvrtki Philips da prikuplja moje podatke o aplikaciji u svrhu njezinog poboljšanja, prilagođavanja i boljeg funkcioniranja, kao i u svrhu integracije s društvenim medijima te prikazivanja relevantnog sadržaja i reklama.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream_Help_Text">Obavijest o kolačićima\n\nOva aplikacija upotrebljava Adobe Analytics, uslugu analize (\"Adobe Analytics\") tvrtke Adobe Systems Software Ireland Limited (\"Adobe\"). Adobe Analytics upotrebljava \"kolačiće\" ili slične tehnike, a to su tekstne datoteke u aplikaciji koje aplikaciji pomažu u analiziranju općenitih uzoraka upotrebe aplikacije. Prijenosom informacija o upotrebi aplikacije koje generira kolačić tvrtki Adobe, postavka osigurava anonimnost IP adrese prije utvrđivanja zemljopisnog položaja i njezinu zamjenu generičkom IP adresom prije spremanja. U ime tvrtke Philips, Adobe će upotrebljavati te informacije za procjenu vaše upotrebe aplikacije, sastavljanje izvješća o aktivnosti aplikacije za Philips te pružanje drugih usluga tvrtki Philips koje se tiču aktivnosti i uporabe aplikacije. Adobe neće povezati vašu IP adresu s drugim podacima koje ima. Tvrtke Adobe i Philips možete spriječiti u prikupljanju i uporabi podataka (kolačića i IP adrese) ako to odbijete nakon zatvaranja ovog zaslona.\n</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Coaching_Help_Text">[hr]The actual content of the coaching consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Marketing_Help_Text">Budući da ste dali suglasnost, tvrtke iz grupacije Philips mogu vas kontaktirati u promocijske svrhe e-poštom, SMS porukom i drugim digitalnim kanalima kao što su mobilne aplikacije i društveni mediji. Kako bismo komunikaciju mogli prilagoditi vašim preferencama i ponašanju te vam pružiti najbolji prilagođeni doživljaj, možemo analizirati i kombinirati vaše osobne podatke. Ti podaci mogu obuhvaćati: \n\nPodatke koje ste nam ustupili\nPodatke koje želite aktivno dijeliti s nama kao što su: vaše ime, datum rođenja ili dob, adresa e-pošte, poštanska adresa, država, spol, telefonski broj, profil društvenih mreža.\n\nPodatke koje prikupimo prilikom vaše interakcije s tvrtkom Philips\nPodatke o vašim interakcijama i upotrebi digitalnih kanala tvrtke Philips kao što su društveni mediji, web-mjesta, e-pošta, aplikacije i srodni proizvodi. Ti podaci mogu obuhvaćati: IP adresu, kolačiće, informacije o uređaju, komunikaciju koju pritisnete, pojedinosti o lokaciji i web-mjesta koja posjećujete\n\nPhilips će vam dati priliku da u bilo koje vrijeme poništite svoju suglasnost.\nViše informacija možete pronaći u Obavijesti o privatnosti tvrtke Philips i Obavijesti o kolačićima tvrtke Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Moment_Help_Text">[hr]The actual content of the moment consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Research_Analytics_Help_Text">[hr]The actual content of the research and analytics consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Moment_Consent">[hr]I allow Philips to store my data in cloud</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Research_Analytics_Consent">[hr]I allow Philips to use my data for Research and Analytics purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_Menu_title_Demo">[hr]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_NO_Order_History">Prethodne narudžbe nisu dostupne</string>
  <string name="RA_OK">OK</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Dismiss">[hr]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Shop_Text">[hr]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Support_Text">[hr]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions product informations and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Benefit_Text">Produžite jamstvo za 24 mjeseca.\nOsigurajte 10 % popusta za proizvode Philips.\nOsigurajte besplatnu dodatnu opremu za proizvod</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Email_Text">Poruka e-pošte s ugovorom za produženo jamstvo poslana je na vašu adresu e-pošte</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Extentende_Warranty">Jamstveno razdoblje produženo je do sljedeće godine</string>
  <string name="RA_Philips_Shop_Menu_Title">Philips trgovina</string>
  <string name="RA_Product_Registration_Text">Registrirajte svoj proizvod</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_ACTIVATE_SCREEN_LOCK">[hr]Activate screenlock</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_DONT_SHOW_MESSAGE">[hr]Do not show this message again</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[hr]We’ve detected that you have rooted the device or jailbroken, thereby making it easier for others to access your data and no security on your application data.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_NO_THANKS">[hr]No thanks</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_PASSCODE_AND_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[hr]We’ve detected that you have jailbroken and not activated screenlock, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SCREEN_LOCK">[hr]We’ve detected the screenlock of your mobile phone is to enabled, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SECURE_YOUR_DATA">[hr]Secure your data</string>
  <string name="RA_See_a_doctor_Menu_Title">[hr]See a doctor</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title">Primajte promotivne materijale tvrtke Philips na temelju svojih preferenci i ponašanja na mreži</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title_Only">[hr]Receive Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_SettingsScreen_Title">Postavke računa</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Login">Prijava</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout">Odjava</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout_Alert">Jeste li sigurni da se želite odjaviti?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_MyAccount">Moj račun</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_OrderHistory">Prethodne narudžbe</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Promo_Question_Text">Što to znači?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Purchases">Kupnje</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Screen_Header_Title">Postavke</string>
  <string name="RA_Skip_Button_Text">Preskoči</string>
  <string name="RA_SplashScreen_Title">Aplikacije za mobilne uređaje</string>
  <string name="RA_SupportScreen_Title">Podrška</string>
  <string name="RA_Support_Menu_Title">Podrška</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert">Promijeni konfiguraciju</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert_Msg">Konfiguracija se može promijeniti samo prilikom pokretanja. Kako biste je promijenili, morate ponovo pokrenuti aplikaciju</string>
  <string name="RA_Update_Userdata_Error">Došlo je do pogreške prilikom ažuriranja korisničkih podataka. Pokušajte nakon određenog vremena</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_A">Okomito postavljanje aplikacije A</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_B">Okomito postavljanje aplikacije B</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_C">Okomito postavljanje aplikacije C</string>
  <string name="RA_Warning">UPOZORENJE</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Text">[hr]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Title">[hr]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Text">[hr]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 Platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Title">[hr]What\'s in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Text">[hr]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Title">[hr]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Text">[hr]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Title">[hr]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Text">[hr]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Title">[hr]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Text">[hr]The Security &amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rules.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Title">[hr]Secure &amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Text">[hr]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Title">[hr]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Text">[hr]Functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Title">[hr]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro">[hr]This app integrates the common components to development new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro_Title">[hr]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_You_are_not_LoggedIn">Niste prijavljeni. Odaberite Postavke i prijavite se</string>
  <string name="RA_change_config_desc">[hr]Configuration can only be changed at launch time. You need to relaunch the app to change it.</string>
  <string name="RA_loading_articles">[hr]Loading Article</string>
  <string name="RA_reference_device_scan">Skeniranje referentnog uređaja</string>
  <string name="RA_something_wrong">Došlo je do pogreške</string>
  <string name="chapters">[hr]Chapters</string>
  <string name="common_components">[hr]Common Components</string>
  <string name="description_close">[hr]Close</string>
  <string name="label_last_synced">[hr]Last updated: %1$s</string>
  <string name="label_last_synced_default">[hr]Last updated: No update yet</string>
  <string name="label_sleep_time_format">[hr]%d mins</string>
  <string name="label_sleep_tips">[hr]How can I improve my sleep score?</string>
  <string name="mya_config_tab">[hr]Configuration tab</string>
</resources>
