<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  Copyright (c) Koninklijke Philips N.V., 2018
  All rights are reserved. Reproduction or dissemination
  in whole or in part is prohibited without the prior written
  consent of the copyright holder.
  -->


<resources>
  <string name="BA_Add_Edit_Temp">הוסף או ערוך טמפרטורה </string>
  <string name="BA_AppFramework">מסגרת היישום </string>
  <string name="BA_HSDP_login_not_available">ההתחברות ל-HSDP אינה זמינה</string>
  <string name="BA_Sync_Settings">הגדרות סנכרון</string>
  <string name="RA_AboutScreen_Title">אודות</string>
  <string name="RA_About_App_Version">גרסה</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Description_New">[he]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Menu_Title">אודות</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsDescription">[he]\"Special offers, promotions and first hand information about new product releases.\nTailored for you!\n\nJoin 140.000 of your peers now!\"</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsTitle">[he]What do we have to offer?</string>
  <string name="RA_Cancel">ביטול</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_AppInfra">[he]AppInfra is the component\'s top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_Connectivity">[he]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ConsumerCare">[he]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_DataServices">[he]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data: Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_InAppPurchase">[he]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ProductRegistration">[he]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UIToolkit">[he]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UserRegistration">[he]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization / social media specific credentials</string>
  <string name="RA_ConnectivityScreen_Title">קישוריות</string>
  <string name="RA_Done_Button_Text">בוצע</string>
  <string name="RA_Empty_Invalid_Data">שדה הנתונים ריק או לא חוקי</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Body_Text">הטקסט הספציפי להצעה יוכנס לגוף </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Header_Text">הכותרת הספציפית להצעה תוכנס לכאן </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Menu_Title">Mobile App – ראשי</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Title">Mobile App – ראשי</string>
  <string name="RA_Invalid_Param_Msg">הזנת או בחרת ערכי פרמטרים לא חוקיים; בחר ערכי פרמטרים מתאימים והפעל שוב</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Binary_Hosting_Consent">[he]I allow Philips to store binary data</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Click_Stream_Hosting_Consent">[he]I allow Philips to use my mobile application usage statistics</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Coaching_Consent">[he]I allow Philips to use my data for Coaching purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Binary_Help_Text">[he]The actual content of the binary consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream">אני מאשר לפיליפס לאסוף נתונים מהאפליקציה שלי כדי לסייע לאפליקציה לפעול, לשפר אותה, להתאים לי אותה אישית, לשלב אותה ברשתות חברתיות ולהציג תוכן ופרסומות בעלי רלוונטיות.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream_Help_Text">הודעה על קובצי Cookie\n\nאפליקציה זו נעזרת ב-Adobe Analytics, שהוא שירות אנליטיקה (להלן Adobe Analytics), מבית Adobe Systems Software Ireland Limited (להלן Adobe). שירות Adobe Analytics משתמש בקובצי Cookie או טכניקות דומות, דהיינו קובצי טקסט המוצבים האפליקציה שלך במטרה לסייע לאפליקציה לנתח את דפוסי התעבורה במבט כולל. על ידי שידור המידע שמפיק קובץ ה-Cookie על השימוש באפליקציה אל Adobe, ההגדרה מבטיחה אנונימיזציה של כתובת ה-IP לפני האיכון הגיאוגרפי, ותוחלף בכתובת IP כללית לפני האחסון. בשם פיליפס, חברת Adobe תשתמש במידע הזה לצורך הערכת דפוסי השימוש שלך באפליקציה, להכנת דוחות על פעילות האפליקציה בשביל פיליפס ולאספקת שירותים אחרים הקשורים לפעולת האפליקציה ולשימוש בה לפיליפס. חברת Adobe לא תשייך את כתובת ה-IP שלך עם שום נתון אחר שבידי Adobe. לאחר שתצא ממסך זה, באפשרותך תוכל למנוע איסוף של הנתונים (קובצי Cookie וכתובות IP) על ידי Adobe ופיליפס ושימוש בהם.\n</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Coaching_Help_Text">[he]The actual content of the coaching consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Marketing_Help_Text">בעקבות הסכמתך, ייתכן שחברות בקבוצת פיליפס יפנו אליך בדואר אלקטרוני, ב-SMS ובערוצים דיגיטליים אחרים, כמו אפליקציות לנייד ורשתות חברתיות. כדי שנוכל להתאים את ההודעות להעדפותיך ולהתנהגותך ולספק לך את החוויה המותאמת אישית הטובה ביותר, ייתכן שננתח ונשלב את הנתונים האישיים שלך. נתונים אלה עשויים לכלול: \n\nהנתונים שאתה מספק לנו\nנתונים שאתה מסכים לשתף עמנו באופן פעיל, כמו למשל: שמך, תאריך הלידה או הגיל שלך, כתובת דואר אלקטרונית, כתובת פיזית, מדינה, מין, מספר טלפון, פרופיל מדיה חברתית.\n\nנתונים שאנו מקבלים מהאינטראקציות שלך עם פיליפס\nנתונים על האינטראקציות והשימוש שלך בערוצים הדיגיטליים של פיליפס, כמו רשתות חברתיות, אתרי אינטרנט, דואר אלקטרוני, אפליקציות ומוצרים קשורים. נתונים אלה עשויים לכלול: כתובת IP, קובצי Cookie, מידע על המכשיר, הודעות שאתה לוחץ עליהן, פרטי מיקום ואתרי אינטרנט שאתה מבקר בהם.\n\nפיליפס תאפשר לך לבטל את הסכמתך בכל עת.\nלמידע נוסף, קרא את הודעת הפרטיות של פיליפס ואת ההודעה של פיליפס על קובצי Cookie.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Moment_Help_Text">[he]The actual content of the moment consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Research_Analytics_Help_Text">[he]The actual content of the research and analytics consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Moment_Consent">[he]I allow Philips to store my data in cloud</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Research_Analytics_Consent">[he]I allow Philips to use my data for Research and Analytics purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_NO_Order_History">היסטוריית ההזמנות אינה זמינה</string>
  <string name="RA_OK">אישור</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Dismiss">[he]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Shop_Text">[he]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Support_Text">[he]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions product informations and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Benefit_Text">הארך את האחריות שלך ב-24 חודשים;\nקבל 10% הנחה בחנות של פיליפס;\nקבל את אבזרי המוצר בחינם</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Email_Text">הודעת דוא\"ל ובה הארכת הסכם האחריות נשלחה לכתובת הדוא\"ל שלך</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Extentende_Warranty">תקופת האחריות שלך הוארכה עד לשנה הבאה</string>
  <string name="RA_Philips_Shop_Menu_Title">החנות של פיליפס</string>
  <string name="RA_Product_Registration_Text">רשום את המוצר שלך</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title">קבל חומרים פרסומיים של פיליפס על בסיס \'ההעדפות שלי\' והתנהגותך המקוונת</string>
  <string name="RA_SettingsScreen_Title">הגדרות חשבון</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Login">התחבר</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout">התנתק</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout_Alert">האם אתה בטוח שברצונך להתנתק?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_MyAccount">החשבון שלי</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_OrderHistory">היסטוריית הזמנות</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Promo_Question_Text">מה זה אומר?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Purchases">רכישות</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Screen_Header_Title">הגדרות</string>
  <string name="RA_Skip_Button_Text">דלג</string>
  <string name="RA_SplashScreen_Title">Mobile Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_SupportScreen_Title">תמיכה</string>
  <string name="RA_Support_Menu_Title">תמיכה</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert">שנה תצורה</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert_Msg">התצורה ניתנת לשינוי רק בשלב ההפעלה; עליך להפעיל את היישום מחדש כדי לשנות זאת</string>
  <string name="RA_Update_Userdata_Error">אירעה שגיאה בעדכון נתוני המשתמש; נסה שוב לאחר זמן מה</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_A">הגדרת יישום אנכי A</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_B">הגדרת יישום אנכי B</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_C">הגדרת יישום אנכי C</string>
  <string name="RA_Warning">אזהרה</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Text">[he]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Title">[he]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Text">[he]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 Platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Title">[he]What\'s in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Text">[he]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Title">[he]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Text">[he]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Title">[he]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Text">[he]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Title">[he]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Text">[he]The Security &amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rules.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Title">[he]Secure &amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Text">[he]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Title">[he]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Text">[he]Functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Title">[he]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro">[he]This app integrates the common components to development new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro_Title">[he]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_You_are_not_LoggedIn">אינך מחובר; עבור אל \'הגדרות\' והתחבר</string>
  <string name="RA_reference_device_scan">סרוק התקן להתייחסות</string>
  <string name="RA_something_wrong">משהו השתבש</string>
</resources>
