<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  Copyright (c) Koninklijke Philips N.V., 2018
  All rights are reserved. Reproduction or dissemination
  in whole or in part is prohibited without the prior written
  consent of the copyright holder.
  -->


<resources>
  <string name="BA_Add_Edit_Temp">Add or Edit Temperature </string>
  <string name="BA_AppFramework">AppFramework </string>
  <string name="BA_HSDP_login_not_available">HSDP login not available</string>
  <string name="BA_Sync_Settings">Sync Settings</string>
  <string name="RA_AboutScreen_Title">About</string>
  <string name="RA_About_App_Version">Version</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Description_New">[en-GB]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Menu_Title">About</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra">[en-GB]ail : App Infrastructure Library</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra_desc">[en-GB]AppInfra is the components top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC">[en-GB]dcc : Consumer Care</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC_desc">[en-GB]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_Connectivity">[en-GB]cml : CommLib</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_Connectivity_desc">[en-GB]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_DS">[en-GB]dsc : Data Services</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_DS_desc">[en-GB]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data -\n&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP">[en-GB]iap : In-app Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP_desc">[en-GB]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR">[en-GB]prg : Product Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR_desc">[en-GB]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UIKIT">[en-GB]uit : Mobile UI Toolkit Non DLS</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UIKIT_desc">[en-GB]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR">[en-GB]usr : User Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR_desc">[en-GB]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization social media specific credentials.</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsDescription">[en-GB]\"Special offers, promotions and first hand information about new product releases.\nTailored for you!\n\nJoin 140.000 of your peers now!\"</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsTitle">[en-GB]What do we have to offer?</string>
  <string name="RA_Cancel">Cancel</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_AppInfra">[en-GB]AppInfra is the component\'s top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_Connectivity">[en-GB]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ConsumerCare">[en-GB]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_DataServices">[en-GB]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data: Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_InAppPurchase">[en-GB]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ProductRegistration">[en-GB]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UIToolkit">[en-GB]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UserRegistration">[en-GB]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization / social media specific credentials</string>
  <string name="RA_Coco_Version">[en-GB]App Info</string>
  <string name="RA_ConnectivityScreen_Title">Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLSS_avatar_default_text">[en-GB]Hello User, \nPlease sign in.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Philips_Shop">[en-GB]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Support_screen_sub">[en-GB]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions, product information and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_HomeScreen_Title">[en-GB]Reference App Home</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_copyright">[en-GB]Copyright \u00A9 2017 Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_description">[en-GB]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_privacy">[en-GB]Privacy policy</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_terms">[en-GB]Terms &amp;amp;amp; conditions</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_check_internet_connectivity">[en-GB]Check Internet Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_data_fetch_error">[en-GB]Not able to fetch data</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_data_fetch_wait">[en-GB]Wait..While we fetch your sleep data from device</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_enable_bluetooth">[en-GB]Please enable bluetooth</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_healthy_sleep_title">[en-GB]Healthy Sleep Score</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_sub_text">[en-GB]ReferenceApp is a base platform used by all propositions to develop and maintain features both generic and specific to the propositions. App infra, Data Gateway, App FWK, and UIToolkit allow Apps to be created from uApps and UI-less services/libraries. ReferenceApp acts as a foundation over which CDP2 uApps and proposition specific uApps are integrated to form individual apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_text">[en-GB]Reference App</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_insights_error">[en-GB]Error loading Insights</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_no_internet_connectivity">[en-GB]Internet connection is not available</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_sub_text">[en-GB]This app integrates the common components required to develop new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_title">[en-GB]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_sub_text">[en-GB]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_title">[en-GB]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_sub_text">[en-GB]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_title">[en-GB]What is in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_sub_text">[en-GB]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_title">[en-GB]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_sub_text">[en-GB]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_title">[en-GB]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_sub_text">[en-GB]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_title">[en-GB]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_sub_text">[en-GB]The Security &amp;amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rule.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_title">[en-GB]Secure &amp;amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_sub_text">[en-GB]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_title">[en-GB]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_sub_text">[en-GB]&lt;html&gt;The CDP&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;2&lt;small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;sup&gt; platform is fully integrated with HSDP and IT to ensure all functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_title">[en-GB]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_overlay_got_it">[en-GB]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_actual">[en-GB]Actual</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_connectivity">[en-GB]PowerSleep Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_deep_sleep_title">[en-GB]Time spent in deep sleep</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_default_data">[en-GB]--</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_ideal_deep_sleep">[en-GB](Ideal 120 mins)</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_ideal_sleep_time">[en-GB](Ideal 450-540 mins)</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_percentage_label">[en-GB]of 100</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_time_sleep">[en-GB]Time asleep</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_ps_tips_title">[en-GB]Tips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_sleep_element">[en-GB]Sleep element</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_splash_title">[en-GB]&lt;html&gt;&lt;b&gt;CDP&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;2&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Reference App&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_theme_title">[en-GB]Theme Setting</string>
  <string name="RA_Demo_Menu_Title">[en-GB]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_Done_Button_Text">Finished</string>
  <string name="RA_Empty_Invalid_Data">Data field is empty or invalid</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Body_Text">Proposition specific large text goes in the body </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Header_Text">Proposition specific Title goes in here </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Menu_Title">Mobile App home</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Title">Mobile App home</string>
  <string name="RA_Invalid_Param_Msg">You have entered or selected invalid parameter values. Please select appropriate parameter values and launch again</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Binary_Hosting_Consent">[en-GB]I allow Philips to store binary data</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Click_Stream_Hosting_Consent">[en-GB]I allow Philips to use my mobile application usage statistics</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Coaching_Consent">[en-GB]I allow Philips to use my data for Coaching purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Binary_Help_Text">[en-GB]The actual content of the binary consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream">I allow Philips to collect my app data to help the app to function, to improve the app, to personalise the app, to integrate with social media and to show relevant content and advertisements.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream_Help_Text">Cookie Notice\n\nThis App uses Adobe Analytics, an analytics service (\"Adobe Analytics\") provided by Adobe Systems Software Ireland Limited (\"Adobe\"). Adobe Analytics uses \"cookies\" or similar techniques, which are text files placed in your App, in order to help the App to analyse overall traffic patterns through our App. By transmitting the information generated by the cookie about the use of the App to Adobe, settings ensure that the IP address is anonymised before geo-localisation and replaced by a generic IP address before storage. On behalf of Philips, Adobe will use this information for the evaluation of your use of the App, compiling reports on App activity for Philips, and in order to provide other services relating to App activity and use of the App to Philips. Adobe will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Adobe. You can prevent Adobe\'s and Philips\' collection and use of data (cookies and IP address) if you opt-out after you close this screen.\n</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Coaching_Help_Text">[en-GB]The actual content of the coaching consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Marketing_Help_Text">As a result of your consent, Philips group companies may contact you with promotional communications via email, SMS and other digital channels, such as mobile apps and social media. To be able to tailor the communications to your preferences and behaviour and provide you with the best, personalised experience, we may analyse and combine your personal data. This data may include: \n\nData you give us\nData that you want to actively share with us such as: your name, date of birth or age, email address, physical address, country, gender, phone number, social media profile\n\nData we get from your interactions with Philips\nData about your interactions and usage of the Philips digital channels, such as social media, websites, emails, apps and connected products. This data may include: IP address, cookies, device information, communications you click on, location details and websites you visit\n\nPhilips will give you the opportunity to withdraw your consent at any time.\nFor more information, please read the Philips Privacy notice and the Philips Cookie notice.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Moment_Help_Text">[en-GB]The actual content of the moment consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Research_Analytics_Help_Text">[en-GB]The actual content of the research and analytics consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Moment_Consent">[en-GB]I allow Philips to store my data in cloud</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Research_Analytics_Consent">[en-GB]I allow Philips to use my data for Research and Analytics purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_Menu_title_Demo">[en-GB]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_NO_Order_History">Order History Not Available</string>
  <string name="RA_OK">OK</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Dismiss">[en-GB]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Shop_Text">[en-GB]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Support_Text">[en-GB]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions product informations and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Benefit_Text">Extend your warranty for 24 months.\nReceive 10% discount in the Philips shop.\nReceive free product accessories</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Email_Text">An email with an extended warranty contract has been sent to your email address</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Extentende_Warranty">Your warranty period has been extended until next year</string>
  <string name="RA_Philips_Shop_Menu_Title">Philips Shop</string>
  <string name="RA_Product_Registration_Text">Register Your Product</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_ACTIVATE_SCREEN_LOCK">[en-GB]Activate screenlock</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_DONT_SHOW_MESSAGE">[en-GB]Do not show this message again</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[en-GB]We’ve detected that you have rooted the device or jailbroken, thereby making it easier for others to access your data and no security on your application data.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_NO_THANKS">[en-GB]No thanks</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_PASSCODE_AND_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[en-GB]We’ve detected that you have jailbroken and not activated screenlock, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SCREEN_LOCK">[en-GB]We’ve detected the screenlock of your mobile phone is to enabled, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SECURE_YOUR_DATA">[en-GB]Secure your data</string>
  <string name="RA_See_a_doctor_Menu_Title">[en-GB]See a doctor</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title">Receive Philips promotional communications based on my preferences and online behaviour</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title_Only">[en-GB]Receive Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Login">Log In</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout">Log Out</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout_Alert">Are you sure you want to log out?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_MyAccount">My Account</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_OrderHistory">Order History</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Promo_Question_Text">What does this mean?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Purchases">Purchases</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Screen_Header_Title">Settings</string>
  <string name="RA_Skip_Button_Text">Skip</string>
  <string name="RA_SplashScreen_Title">Mobile Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_SupportScreen_Title">Support</string>
  <string name="RA_Support_Menu_Title">Support</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert">Change configuration</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert_Msg">Configuration can only be changed at launch. You need to relaunch the app to change it</string>
  <string name="RA_Update_Userdata_Error">There was an error updating User Data. Please try again later</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_A">Vertical App Setting A</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_B">Vertical App Setting B</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_C">Vertical App Setting C</string>
  <string name="RA_Warning">WARNING</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Text">[en-GB]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Title">[en-GB]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Text">[en-GB]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 Platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Title">[en-GB]What\'s in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Text">[en-GB]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Title">[en-GB]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Text">[en-GB]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Title">[en-GB]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Text">[en-GB]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Title">[en-GB]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Text">[en-GB]The Security &amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rules.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Title">[en-GB]Secure &amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Text">[en-GB]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Title">[en-GB]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Text">[en-GB]Functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Title">[en-GB]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro">[en-GB]This app integrates the common components to development new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro_Title">[en-GB]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_You_are_not_LoggedIn">You are not logged in. Please go to Settings and log in</string>
  <string name="RA_change_config_desc">[en-GB]Configuration can only be changed at launch time. You need to relaunch the app to change it.</string>
  <string name="RA_loading_articles">[en-GB]Loading Article</string>
  <string name="RA_reference_device_scan">Reference Device Scan</string>
  <string name="RA_something_wrong">Something went wrong</string>
  <string name="chapters">[en-GB]Chapters</string>
  <string name="common_components">[en-GB]Common Components</string>
  <string name="description_close">[en-GB]Close</string>
  <string name="label_last_synced">[en-GB]Last updated: %1$s</string>
  <string name="label_last_synced_default">[en-GB]Last updated: No update yet</string>
  <string name="label_sleep_time_format">[en-GB]%d mins</string>
  <string name="label_sleep_tips">[en-GB]How can I improve my sleep score?</string>
  <string name="mya_config_tab">[en-GB]Configuration tab</string>
</resources>
