<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  Copyright (c) Koninklijke Philips N.V., 2018
  All rights are reserved. Reproduction or dissemination
  in whole or in part is prohibited without the prior written
  consent of the copyright holder.
  -->


<resources>
  <string name="BA_Add_Edit_Temp">新增或編輯溫度</string>
  <string name="BA_AppFramework">AppFramework </string>
  <string name="BA_HSDP_login_not_available">HSDP 登入不可用</string>
  <string name="BA_Sync_Settings">同步設定</string>
  <string name="RA_AboutScreen_Title">關於</string>
  <string name="RA_About_App_Version">版本</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Description_New">[zh-HK]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Menu_Title">關於</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsDescription">[zh-HK]\"Special offers, promotions and first hand information about new product releases.\nTailored for you!\n\nJoin 140.000 of your peers now!\"</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsTitle">[zh-HK]What do we have to offer?</string>
  <string name="RA_Cancel">取消</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_AppInfra">[zh-HK]AppInfra is the component\'s top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_Connectivity">[zh-HK]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ConsumerCare">[zh-HK]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_DataServices">[zh-HK]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data: Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_InAppPurchase">[zh-HK]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ProductRegistration">[zh-HK]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UIToolkit">[zh-HK]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UserRegistration">[zh-HK]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization / social media specific credentials</string>
  <string name="RA_ConnectivityScreen_Title">連接</string>
  <string name="RA_Done_Button_Text">完成</string>
  <string name="RA_Empty_Invalid_Data">數據欄空白或無效</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Body_Text">命題具體大文本於主體部分</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Header_Text">命題具體標題於此</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Menu_Title">應用程式主頁</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Title">應用程式主頁</string>
  <string name="RA_Invalid_Param_Msg">您已輸入或選取無效的參數值。請選擇正確參數值並重新啟動。</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Binary_Hosting_Consent">[zh-HK]I allow Philips to store binary data</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Click_Stream_Hosting_Consent">[zh-HK]I allow Philips to use my mobile application usage statistics</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Coaching_Consent">[zh-HK]I allow Philips to use my data for Coaching purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Binary_Help_Text">[zh-HK]The actual content of the binary consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream">我允許 Philips 收集我的應用程式資料以協助應用程式運作、改善應用程式、為應用程式作個人化設置、與社交媒體整合並展示相關內容及廣告。</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream_Help_Text">Cookie 聲明\n\n此應用程式會使用由 Adobe Systems Software Ireland Limited（「Adobe」）提供的分析服務「Adobe Analytics」。Adobe Analytics 會使用「Cookie」或相似的技術，將文字檔案儲存於您的應用程式中，以協助應用程式分析其中的整體流量模式。向 Adobe 傳輸由 Cookie 產生的應用程式使用資料時，設定會確保 IP 地址經過匿名方式後才用於地理位置定位，而儲存前亦會以一般 IP 地址代替。Adobe 代表 Philips 使用這些資料以評估您使用應用程式的情況、為 Philips 製作應用程式相關的報告，並向 Philips 提供其他與應用程式活動及使用相關的服務。Adobe 不會將您的 IP 地址與其他 Adobe 所擁有的資料混合使用。如您不希望 Adobe 及 Philips 收集並使用您的資料（Cookie 及 IP 地址），您可在關閉此畫面後選擇退出。\n</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Coaching_Help_Text">[zh-HK]The actual content of the coaching consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Marketing_Help_Text">由於您表示同意，Philips 集團公司可能會透過電郵、短訊及其他數碼渠道（如流動應用程式及社交媒體）就宣傳通訊事宜聯絡您。為令通訊內容更能貼近您的喜好及行為，並向您提供最佳的個人體驗，我們可能會分析並整合您的個人資料，包括： \n\n您提供的資料\n您主動樂意分享的個人資料如：您的姓名、生日、年齡、電郵地址、居住住址、國家、性別、電話號碼以及社交媒體資料。\n\n我們從您與 Philips 交互活動中所取得的資訊\n有關您與 Philips 數碼頻道（例如社交媒體、網站、電子郵件、應用程式和連線的產品）互動和相關使用情況的資料。這些資料可能包括：IP 地址、Cookie、裝置資訊、您點擊的通訊、位置詳細資料和您瀏覽的網站。\n\nPhilips 讓您隨時取消同意以上內容。\n詳情請參閱 Philips 私隱聲明及 Philips Cookie 聲明。</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Moment_Help_Text">[zh-HK]The actual content of the moment consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Research_Analytics_Help_Text">[zh-HK]The actual content of the research and analytics consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Moment_Consent">[zh-HK]I allow Philips to store my data in cloud</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Research_Analytics_Consent">[zh-HK]I allow Philips to use my data for Research and Analytics purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_NO_Order_History">訂單記錄不適用</string>
  <string name="RA_OK">確定</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Dismiss">[zh-HK]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Shop_Text">[zh-HK]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Support_Text">[zh-HK]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions product informations and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Benefit_Text">保用期已延長 24 個月。\n於 Philips 享受 9 折優惠。\n獲取免費產品配件</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Email_Text">我們已向您的電郵地址發出一封電郵，內容載有延長保用的合約</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Extentende_Warranty">您的保用期已延長至下年。</string>
  <string name="RA_Philips_Shop_Menu_Title">Philips 商店</string>
  <string name="RA_Product_Registration_Text">註冊您的產品</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title">按照我的偏好及網上瀏覽行為接收 Philips 的推廣通訊</string>
  <string name="RA_SettingsScreen_Title">帳戶設定</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Login">登入</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout">登出</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout_Alert">您確定要登出？</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_MyAccount">我的帳戶</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_OrderHistory">訂單記錄</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Promo_Question_Text">這意味著什麼呢？</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Purchases">購買</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Screen_Header_Title">設定</string>
  <string name="RA_Skip_Button_Text">跳過</string>
  <string name="RA_SplashScreen_Title">手機應用程式</string>
  <string name="RA_SupportScreen_Title">支援</string>
  <string name="RA_Support_Menu_Title">支援</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert">變更配置</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert_Msg">配置只可於啟動時變更。如要變更，請重新啟動應用程式</string>
  <string name="RA_Update_Userdata_Error">更新用戶數據時發出錯誤，請稍後再試</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_A">垂直應用程式設定 A</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_B">垂直應用程式設定 B</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_C">垂直應用程式設定 C</string>
  <string name="RA_Warning">警告</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Text">[zh-HK]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Title">[zh-HK]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Text">[zh-HK]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 Platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Title">[zh-HK]What\'s in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Text">[zh-HK]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Title">[zh-HK]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Text">[zh-HK]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Title">[zh-HK]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Text">[zh-HK]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Title">[zh-HK]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Text">[zh-HK]The Security &amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rules.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Title">[zh-HK]Secure &amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Text">[zh-HK]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Title">[zh-HK]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Text">[zh-HK]Functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Title">[zh-HK]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro">[zh-HK]This app integrates the common components to development new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro_Title">[zh-HK]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_You_are_not_LoggedIn">您尚未登入。請前往設定並登入</string>
  <string name="RA_reference_device_scan">參考裝置掃描</string>
  <string name="RA_something_wrong">出錯</string>
</resources>
