<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Copyright (c) Koninklijke Philips N.V., 2018
   - All rights are reserved. Reproduction or dissemination
   - in whole or in part is prohibited without the prior written
   - consent of the copyright holder. -->

<resources>
  <string name="BA_AppFramework">AppFramework </string>
  <string name="RA_AboutScreen_Title">Относно</string>
  <string name="RA_About_App_Version">Версия</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Menu_Title">Относно</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra">[bg]ail : App Infrastructure Library</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra_desc">[bg]AppInfra is the components top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC">[bg]dcc : Consumer Care</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC_desc">[bg]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP">[bg]iap : In-app Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP_desc">[bg]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR">[bg]prg : Product Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR_desc">[bg]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR">[bg]usr : User Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR_desc">[bg]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization social media specific credentials.</string>
  <string name="RA_Cancel">Отказ</string>
  <string name="RA_Coco_Version">[bg]App Info</string>
  <string name="RA_DLSS_avatar_default_text">[bg]Hello User,\nPlease sign in.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Philips_Shop">[bg]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Support_screen_sub">[bg]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions, product information and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_HomeScreen_Title">[bg]Reference App Home</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_copyright">[bg]Copyright © 2017 Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_description">[bg]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_privacy">[bg]Privacy policy</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_terms">[bg]Terms &amp; conditions</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_check_internet_connectivity">[bg]Check Internet Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_sub_text">[bg]ReferenceApp is a base platform used by all propositions to develop and maintain features both generic and specific to the propositions. App infra, Data Gateway, App FWK, and UIToolkit allow Apps to be created from uApps and UI-less services/libraries. ReferenceApp acts as a foundation over which CDP2 uApps and proposition specific uApps are integrated to form individual apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_text">[bg]Reference App</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_sub_text">[bg]This app integrates the common components required to develop new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_title">[bg]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_sub_text">[bg]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_title">[bg]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_sub_text">[bg]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_title">[bg]What is in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_sub_text">[bg]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_title">[bg]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_sub_text">[bg]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_title">[bg]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_sub_text">[bg]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_title">[bg]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_sub_text">[bg]The Security &amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rule.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_title">[bg]Secure &amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_sub_text">[bg]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_title">[bg]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_sub_text">[bg]The CDP2 platform is fully integrated with HSDP and IT to ensure all functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_title">[bg]Integrated with HSDP &amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_overlay_got_it">[bg]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_splash_title">[bg]CDP2 Reference App</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_theme_title">[bg]Theme Setting</string>
  <string name="RA_Done_Button_Text">Готово</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Title">Начална страница на мобилно приложение</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Click_Stream_Hosting_Consent">[bg]I allow Philips to use my mobile application usage statistics</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream">Позволявам на Philips да събира данните ми от приложението, за да подпомогне функционирането му, да го подобри, да го персонализира, да го интегрира със социалните медии и да показва подходящо съдържание и реклами.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream_Help_Text">Бележка за бисквитки\n\nТова приложение използва Adobe Analytics – услуга за анализи (\"Adobe Analytics\"), – осигурена от Adobe Systems Software Ireland Limited (\"Adobe\"). Adobe Analytics използва \"бисквитки\" или подобни техники, които представляват текстови файлове, поставени в приложението ви, за да го подпомогнат да анализира цялостните модели на трафик през приложението ни. Чрез предаването на информацията, генерирана от \"бисквитката\", относно използването на приложението към Adobe настройка гарантира, че IP адресът става анонимен, преди да бъде геолокализиран и ще бъде заменен от общ IP адрес преди съхранение. От името на Philips Adobe ще използва тази информация, за да оценява вашата употреба на приложението, да създава доклади за дейността на приложението за Philips и за да осигури други услуги, свързани с дейността и употребата на приложението на Philips. Adobe няма да свърже вашия IP адрес с други данни, съхранявани от Adobe. Можете да предотвратите събирането и използването на данни от Adobe и Philips (\"бисквитки\" и IP адрес), ако се откажете, след като затворите този екран.\n</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Clickstream_Revoke_Warning_Text">[bg]By revoking consent your data will be deleted from our servers.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Marketing_Help_Text">В резултат от съгласието ви компаниите от групата Philips могат да се свързват с вас за промоционални известия чрез имейл, SMS или други цифрови канали като мобилни приложения и социални медии. За да можем да изберем известия за вашите предпочитания и поведение и за да ви предоставим най-доброто, персонализирано изживяване, можем да анализираме и комбинираме личните ви данни. Тези данни могат да включват: \n\nДанни, които ни предоставяте\nДанни, които искате да споделяте активно с нас, като например: вашето име, дата на раждане или възраст, имейл адрес, пощенски адрес, страна, пол, телефонен номер, профил в социални медии.\n\nДанни, които получаваме от вашите взаимодействия с Philips\nДанни относно вашите взаимодействия и употреба на цифровите канали на Philips като социални медии, уебсайтове, имейли, приложения и свързани продукти. Тези данни могат да включват: IP адрес, бисквитки, информация за устройство, известия, върху които сте щракнали, подробности за местоположението и уебсайтове, които посещавате\n\nPhilips ще ви даде възможност да оттеглите съгласието си по всяко време.\nЗа повече информация, моля, прочетете бележката за поверителност на Philips и бележката за бисквитките на Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_Menu_title_Demo">[bg]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_OK">OK</string>
  <string name="RA_Philips_Shop_Menu_Title">Магазин на Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_Product_Registration_Text">Регистрирайте продукта си</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_ACTIVATE_SCREEN_LOCK">[bg]Activate screenlock</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_DONT_SHOW_MESSAGE">[bg]Do not show this message again</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[bg]We’ve detected that you have rooted the device or jailbroken, thereby making it easier for others to access your data and no security on your application data.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_NO_THANKS">[bg]No thanks</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_PASSCODE_AND_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[bg]We’ve detected that you have jailbroken and not activated screenlock, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SCREEN_LOCK">[bg]We’ve detected the screenlock of your mobile phone is to enabled, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SECURE_YOUR_DATA">[bg]Secure your data</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Login">Влизане</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_OrderHistory">Хронология на поръчките</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Progress_Title">[bg]Please Wait!!</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Promo_Question_Text">Какво означава това?</string>
  <string name="RA_Skip_Button_Text">Пропускане</string>
  <string name="RA_Support_Menu_Title">Помощ</string>
  <string name="RA_change_config_desc">[bg]Configuration can only be changed at launch time. You need to relaunch the app to change it.</string>
  <string name="RA_cookie_accept">[bg]Accept</string>
  <string name="RA_cookie_description">[bg]I want to share my app data to help improve the app and provide me with personalized services</string>
  <string name="RA_cookie_nav_title">[bg]Consent</string>
  <string name="RA_cookie_reject">[bg]Reject</string>
  <string name="RA_cookie_title">[bg]Cookies</string>
  <string name="RA_cookie_what_text_description">[bg]Adobe Analytics\\n\\nThis App uses Adobe Analytics, an analytics service (\\\"Adobe Analytics”) provided by Adobe Systems Software Ireland Limited (\\\"Adobe\\\") Adobe Analytics uses \\\"cookies\\\" or similar techniques, which are text files placed in your App, in order to help the App to analyze overall traffic patterns through our App. By transmitting the information generated by the cookie about the use of the App to Adobe, setting ensures that IP address is anonymized before geo-localization und will be replaced by a generic IP address before storage. On behalf of Philips, Adobe will use this information for the evaluation of your use of the App, compiling reports on App activity for Philips, and in order to provide other services relating to App activity and use of the App to IP address with any other data held Philips Adobe will not associate your by Adobe. You can prevent Adobe\\\'s and Philips collection and use of data out after you close this screen (cookies and IP address) if you opt-out after you close this screen.\\n\\nGoogle Firebase\\n\\nThis App uses Google Firebase, an app development service (Firebase) provided by Google Ireland Ltd (\\\"Google\\\"). Firebase uses cookies or similar techniques- SDK, which are text files placed in your App and web browser.\\n\\nOn behalf of Philips, Firebase will use information from your device such as your Device ID. IP address, your IDFA or Google Play Services ID and your MAC address and replace them with unique code. When you use the App we will measure the numbers of visits to the App, which pages you visit your network connection, load times and when the app crashes. We use this information to evaluate and understand your use of the App, to test and analyze performance and ultimately optimize our products and services.</string>
  <string name="RA_something_wrong">Нещо се обърка</string>
  <string name="chapters">[bg]Chapters</string>
  <string name="common_components">[bg]Common Components</string>
  <string name="description_close">[bg]Close</string>
  <string name="iap_auth_error">[bg]Authentication error</string>
  <string name="mya_config_tab">[bg]Configuration tab</string>
</resources>