<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  Copyright (c) Koninklijke Philips N.V., 2018
  All rights are reserved. Reproduction or dissemination
  in whole or in part is prohibited without the prior written
  consent of the copyright holder.
  -->


<resources>
  <string name="BA_Add_Edit_Temp">Temperatuur toevoegen of bewerken </string>
  <string name="BA_AppFramework">AppFramework </string>
  <string name="BA_HSDP_login_not_available">Aanmelden bij HSDP niet mogelijk</string>
  <string name="BA_Sync_Settings">Synchronisatie-instellingen</string>
  <string name="RA_AboutScreen_Title">Over</string>
  <string name="RA_About_App_Version">Versie</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Description_New">[nl]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Menu_Title">Over</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra">[nl]ail : App Infrastructure Library</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra_desc">[nl]AppInfra is the components top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC">[nl]dcc : Consumer Care</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC_desc">[nl]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_Connectivity">[nl]cml : CommLib</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_Connectivity_desc">[nl]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_DS">[nl]dsc : Data Services</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_DS_desc">[nl]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data -\n&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP">[nl]iap : In-app Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP_desc">[nl]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR">[nl]prg : Product Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR_desc">[nl]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UIKIT">[nl]uit : Mobile UI Toolkit Non DLS</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UIKIT_desc">[nl]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR">[nl]usr : User Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR_desc">[nl]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization social media specific credentials.</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsDescription">[nl]\"Special offers, promotions and first hand information about new product releases.\nTailored for you!\n\nJoin 140.000 of your peers now!\"</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsTitle">[nl]What do we have to offer?</string>
  <string name="RA_Cancel">Annuleren</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_AppInfra">[nl]AppInfra is the component\'s top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_Connectivity">[nl]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ConsumerCare">[nl]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_DataServices">[nl]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data: Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_InAppPurchase">[nl]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ProductRegistration">[nl]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UIToolkit">[nl]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UserRegistration">[nl]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization / social media specific credentials</string>
  <string name="RA_Coco_Version">[nl]App Info</string>
  <string name="RA_ConnectivityScreen_Title">Connectiviteit</string>
  <string name="RA_DLSS_avatar_default_text">[nl]Hello User, \nPlease sign in.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Philips_Shop">[nl]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Support_screen_sub">[nl]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions, product information and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_HomeScreen_Title">[nl]Reference App Home</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_copyright">[nl]Copyright \u00A9 2017 Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_description">[nl]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_privacy">[nl]Privacy policy</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_terms">[nl]Terms &amp;amp;amp; conditions</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_check_internet_connectivity">[nl]Check Internet Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_data_fetch_error">[nl]Not able to fetch data</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_data_fetch_wait">[nl]Wait..While we fetch your sleep data from device</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_enable_bluetooth">[nl]Please enable bluetooth</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_healthy_sleep_title">[nl]Healthy Sleep Score</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_sub_text">[nl]ReferenceApp is a base platform used by all propositions to develop and maintain features both generic and specific to the propositions. App infra, Data Gateway, App FWK, and UIToolkit allow Apps to be created from uApps and UI-less services/libraries. ReferenceApp acts as a foundation over which CDP2 uApps and proposition specific uApps are integrated to form individual apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_text">[nl]RA_SettingsScreen_Title</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_insights_error">[nl]Error loading Insights</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_no_internet_connectivity">[nl]Internet connection is not available</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_sub_text">[nl]This app integrates the common components required to develop new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_title">[nl]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_sub_text">[nl]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_title">[nl]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_sub_text">[nl]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_title">[nl]What is in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_sub_text">[nl]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_title">[nl]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_sub_text">[nl]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_title">[nl]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_sub_text">[nl]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_title">[nl]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_sub_text">[nl]The Security &amp;amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rule.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_title">[nl]Secure &amp;amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_sub_text">[nl]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_title">[nl]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_sub_text">[nl]&lt;html&gt;The CDP&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;2&lt;small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;sup&gt; platform is fully integrated with HSDP and IT to ensure all functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_title">[nl]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_overlay_got_it">[nl]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_actual">[nl]Actual</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_connectivity">[nl]PowerSleep Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_deep_sleep_title">[nl]Time spent in deep sleep</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_default_data">[nl]--</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_ideal_deep_sleep">[nl](Ideal 120 mins)</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_ideal_sleep_time">[nl](Ideal 450-540 mins)</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_percentage_label">[nl]of 100</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_time_sleep">[nl]Time asleep</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_ps_tips_title">[nl]Tips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_sleep_element">[nl]Sleep element</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_splash_title">[nl]&lt;html&gt;&lt;b&gt;CDP&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;2&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Reference App&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_theme_title">[nl]Theme Setting</string>
  <string name="RA_Demo_Menu_Title">[nl]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_Done_Button_Text">Gereed</string>
  <string name="RA_Empty_Invalid_Data">Gegevensveld is leeg of bevat ongeldige gegevens</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Body_Text">In het tekstvak komt specifieke grote concepttekst </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Header_Text">Hier komt specifieke concepttitel </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Menu_Title">Beginscherm mobiele app</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Title">Beginscherm mobiele app</string>
  <string name="RA_Invalid_Param_Msg">U hebt ongeldige parameters ingevoerd of geselecteerd. Selecteer de juiste parameters en probeer het opnieuw</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Binary_Hosting_Consent">[nl]I allow Philips to store binary data</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Click_Stream_Hosting_Consent">[nl]I allow Philips to use my mobile application usage statistics</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Coaching_Consent">[nl]I allow Philips to use my data for Coaching purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Binary_Help_Text">[nl]The actual content of the binary consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Binary_Revoke_Warning_Text">[nl]By revoking consent your data will be deleted from our servers.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream">Ik geef Philips toestemming om mijn appgegevens te verzamelen zodat er relevante content en advertenties kunnen worden getoond en zodat de app kan functioneren, kan worden verbeterd, kan worden gepersonaliseerd en kan worden geïntegreerd met sociale media.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream_Help_Text">Cookieverklaring\n\nDeze app maakt gebruik van Adobe Analytics, een analyseservice (\'Adobe Analytics\') van Adobe Systems Software Ireland Limited (\'Adobe\'). Adobe Analytics maakt gebruik van \'cookies\' of vergelijkbare technieken. Dit zijn tekstbestanden die in de app worden geplaatst om gebruikspatronen van de app te kunnen analyseren. Wanneer de cookie-informatie over het gebruik van de app naar Adobe wordt verzonden, wordt het IP-adres eerst geanonimiseerd voordat de geografische locatie wordt bepaald. Dit adres wordt vervangen door een algemeen IP-adres voordat de gegevens worden opgeslagen. Adobe gebruikt deze gegevens namens Philips om het gebruik van de app te analyseren, rapporten over de activiteit van de app op te stellen voor Philips en andere diensten te verlenen aan Philips die te maken hebben met de activiteit en het gebruik van de app. Adobe koppelt uw IP-adres niet aan andere gegevens waarover Adobe beschikt. U kunt voorkomen dat Adobe en Philips de gegevens (de cookies en het IP-adres) verzamelen en gebruiken door u zich hiervoor af te melden nadat u dit scherm sluit.\n</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Clickstream_Revoke_Warning_Text">[nl]By revoking consent your data will be deleted from our servers.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Coaching_Help_Text">[nl]The actual content of the coaching consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Coaching_Revoke_Warning_Text">[nl]By revoking consent your data will be deleted from our servers.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Marketing_Help_Text">Door uw toestemming kunnen de bedrijven uit de Philips-groep u voor promotionele doeleinden benaderen via e-mail, sms en andere digitale kanalen, zoals mobiele apps en sociale media. Om de berichtgeving te kunnen aanpassen aan uw voorkeuren en gedrag en u de beste persoonlijke ervaring te bieden, kunnen we mogelijk uw persoonsgegevens analyseren en combineren. Deze gegevens kunnen bestaan uit: \n\nGegevens die u ons verstrekt\nGegevens die u met ons hebt gedeeld, zoals uw naam, geboortedatum of leeftijd, e-mailadres, woonadres, land, geslacht, telefoonnummer, social-mediaprofiel.\n\nGegevens die wij hebben verkregen via uw interactie met Philips\nGegevens over uw interactie met en het gebruik van de digitale kanalen van Philips, zoals social media, websites, e-mail, apps en verbonden producten. Deze gegevens kunnen het volgende omvatten: IP-adres, cookies, apparaatinformatie, berichten waar u op klikt, locatiegegevens en websites die u bezoekt\n\nU kunt uw toestemming aan Philips op ieder gewenst moment intrekken.\nLees voor meer informatie de Philips-privacyverklaring en de Philips-cookieverklaring.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Moment_Help_Text">[nl]The actual content of the moment consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Moments_Revoke_Warning_Text">[nl]By revoking consent your data will be deleted from our servers.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Research_Analytics_Help_Text">[nl]The actual content of the research and analytics consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Research_Analytics_Revoke_Warning_Text">[nl]By revoking consent your data will be deleted from our servers.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Moment_Consent">[nl]I allow Philips to store my data in cloud</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Research_Analytics_Consent">[nl]I allow Philips to use my data for Research and Analytics purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_Menu_title_Demo">[nl]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_NO_Order_History">Bestelgeschiedenis niet beschikbaar</string>
  <string name="RA_OK">OK</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Dismiss">[nl]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Shop_Text">[nl]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Support_Text">[nl]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions product informations and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Benefit_Text">Verleng uw garantie met 24 maanden. \nOntvang 10% korting in de Philips Store. \nOntvang gratis productaccessoires</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Email_Text">Een e-mail met contract voor uitgebreide garantie is verzonden naar uw e-mailadres</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Extentende_Warranty">Uw garantieperiode is verlengd tot volgend jaar</string>
  <string name="RA_Philips_Shop_Menu_Title">Philips Shop</string>
  <string name="RA_Product_Registration_Text">Registreer uw product</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_ACTIVATE_SCREEN_LOCK">[nl]Activate screenlock</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_DONT_SHOW_MESSAGE">[nl]Do not show this message again</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[nl]We’ve detected that you have rooted the device or jailbroken, thereby making it easier for others to access your data and no security on your application data.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_NO_THANKS">[nl]No thanks</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_PASSCODE_AND_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[nl]We’ve detected that you have jailbroken and not activated screenlock, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SCREEN_LOCK">[nl]We’ve detected the screenlock of your mobile phone is to enabled, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SECURE_YOUR_DATA">[nl]Secure your data</string>
  <string name="RA_See_a_doctor_Menu_Title">[nl]See a doctor</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title">Promotionele berichten van Philips ontvangen gebaseerd op mijn voorkeuren en online gedrag</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title_Only">[nl]Receive Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Login">Aanmelden</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout">Afmelden</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout_Alert">Weet u zeker dat u zich wilt afmelden?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_MyAccount">Mijn account</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_OrderHistory">Bestelgeschiedenis</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Promo_Question_Text">Wat betekent dit?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Purchases">Aankopen</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Screen_Header_Title">Instellingen</string>
  <string name="RA_Skip_Button_Text">Overslaan</string>
  <string name="RA_SplashScreen_Title">Mobiele apps</string>
  <string name="RA_SupportScreen_Title">Ondersteuning</string>
  <string name="RA_Support_Menu_Title">Ondersteuning</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert">Configuratie wijzigen</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert_Msg">Configuratie kan alleen worden gewijzigd bij het starten van de app. U dient de app opnieuw te starten om de configuratie te wijzigen</string>
  <string name="RA_Update_Userdata_Error">Er is een fout opgetreden bij het bijwerken van de gebruikersgegevens. Probeer het later opnieuw</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_A">Verticale appinstelling A</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_B">Verticale appinstelling B</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_C">Verticale appinstelling C</string>
  <string name="RA_Warning">WAARSCHUWING</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Text">[nl]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Title">[nl]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Text">[nl]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 Platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Title">[nl]What\'s in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Text">[nl]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Title">[nl]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Text">[nl]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Title">[nl]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Text">[nl]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Title">[nl]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Text">[nl]The Security &amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rules.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Title">[nl]Secure &amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Text">[nl]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Title">[nl]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Text">[nl]Functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Title">[nl]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro">[nl]This app integrates the common components to development new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro_Title">[nl]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_You_are_not_LoggedIn">U bent niet aangemeld. Ga naar Instellingen en meld u aan.</string>
  <string name="RA_change_config_desc">[nl]Configuration can only be changed at launch time. You need to relaunch the app to change it.</string>
  <string name="RA_loading_articles">[nl]Loading Article</string>
  <string name="RA_reference_device_scan">Scan referentie-apparaat</string>
  <string name="RA_something_wrong">Er is iets misgegaan</string>
  <string name="chapters">[nl]Chapters</string>
  <string name="common_components">[nl]Common Components</string>
  <string name="description_close">[nl]Close</string>
  <string name="label_last_synced">[nl]Last updated: %1$s</string>
  <string name="label_last_synced_default">[nl]Last updated: No update yet</string>
  <string name="label_sleep_time_format">[nl]%d mins</string>
  <string name="label_sleep_tips">[nl]How can I improve my sleep score?</string>
  <string name="mya_config_tab">[nl]Configuration tab</string>
</resources>
