<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  Copyright (c) Koninklijke Philips N.V., 2018
  All rights are reserved. Reproduction or dissemination
  in whole or in part is prohibited without the prior written
  consent of the copyright holder.
  -->


<resources>
  <string name="BA_Add_Edit_Temp">Přidat nebo upravit teplotu </string>
  <string name="BA_AppFramework">Rozhraní aplikace </string>
  <string name="BA_HSDP_login_not_available">Přihlášení přes systém HSDP není k dispozici</string>
  <string name="BA_Sync_Settings">Nastavení synchronizace</string>
  <string name="RA_AboutScreen_Title">Informace</string>
  <string name="RA_About_App_Version">Verze</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Description_New">[cs]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Menu_Title">Informace</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsDescription">[cs]\"Special offers, promotions and first hand information about new product releases.\nTailored for you!\n\nJoin 140.000 of your peers now!\"</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsTitle">[cs]What do we have to offer?</string>
  <string name="RA_Cancel">Zrušit</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_AppInfra">[cs]AppInfra is the component\'s top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_Connectivity">[cs]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ConsumerCare">[cs]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_DataServices">[cs]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data: Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_InAppPurchase">[cs]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ProductRegistration">[cs]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UIToolkit">[cs]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UserRegistration">[cs]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization / social media specific credentials</string>
  <string name="RA_ConnectivityScreen_Title">Možnosti připojení</string>
  <string name="RA_Done_Button_Text">Hotovo</string>
  <string name="RA_Empty_Invalid_Data">Datové pole je prázdné nebo neplatné</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Body_Text">Velký text specifický pro nabídku patří do základní části </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Header_Text">Zde zadejte specifický název nabídky </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Menu_Title">Domácí stránka mobilní aplikace</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Title">Domácí stránka mobilní aplikace</string>
  <string name="RA_Invalid_Param_Msg">Zadali jste nebo jste zvolili neplatné hodnoty parametru. Zvolte příslušné hodnoty parametru a spusťte aplikaci znovu</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Binary_Hosting_Consent">[cs]I allow Philips to store binary data</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Click_Stream_Hosting_Consent">[cs]I allow Philips to use my mobile application usage statistics</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Coaching_Consent">[cs]I allow Philips to use my data for Coaching purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Binary_Help_Text">[cs]The actual content of the binary consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream">Uděluji společnosti Philips souhlas se shromažďováním mých údajů z aplikace za účelem zlepšení fungování aplikace, vylepšení aplikace, přizpůsobení aplikace, integrace se sociálními sítěmi a za účelem zobrazení relevantního obsahu a reklamy.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream_Help_Text">Oznámení o souborech cookie\n\nTato aplikace používá analytickou službu Adobe Analysis. Tato služba („Adobe Analytics“) je poskytována společností Adobe Systems Software Ireland Limited („Adobe”). Služba Adobe Analytics používá soubory cookie nebo podobné textové soubory, které jsou umístěny ve vaší aplikaci, za účelem sledování vzorců používání této aplikace. Při poskytování informací ze souborů cookie o užívání aplikace společnosti Adobe je v nastavení zajištěno, že IP adresa bude před geo-lokalizací anonymizována a před uložením nahrazena obecnou IP adresou. Společnost Adobe, která zastupuje společnost Philips, použije tyto informace pro hodnocení vašeho užívání aplikace a vytvoří zprávy o aktivitách v aplikaci pro společnost Philips za účelem poskytnutí informací o aktivitě služeb v rámci aplikace a užívání aplikace společnosti Philips. Společnost Adobe nebude vaši IP adresu přidružovat k jakýmkoli údajům, vedeným u společnosti Adobe. Shromažďování a použití dat (soubory cookie a IP adresa) společnostmi Adobe a Philips můžete předejít tím, že po zavření této obrazovky zrušíte souhlas.\n</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Coaching_Help_Text">[cs]The actual content of the coaching consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Marketing_Help_Text">Na základě vašeho souhlasu vás mohou společnosti skupiny Philips kontaktovat s reklamními zprávami prostřednictvím e-mailu, SMS zprávy či jiných digitálních prostředků, jako jsou například mobilní aplikace nebo sociální média. Abychom vám mohli tyto zprávy přizpůsobit na míru a poskytnout vám tu nejlepší individuální zkušenost, analyzujeme a kombinujeme vaše osobní údaje. Mezi tyto údaje mohou patřit: \n\nVámi poskytované údaje\nÚdaje, které s námi aktivně sdílíte: vaše jméno, datum narození či věk, e-mailová adresa, adresa bydliště, země, pohlaví, telefonní číslo, profily na sociálních médiích.\n\nÚdaje získané z vašich interakcí se společností Philips\nÚdaje o vašich interakcích a používání digitálních prostředků Philips, jako jsou sociální média, webové stránky, e-maily, aplikace a připojené výrobky. Tyto údaje mohou zahrnovat: IP adresu, soubory cookie, informace o zařízení, zprávy, na které kliknete, údaje o poloze a navštívené webové stránky.\n\nSpolečnost Philips vám dává možnost svůj souhlas kdykoliv zrušit.\nVíce informací naleznete v Oznámení o ochraně osobních údajů společnosti Philips a v Oznámení o souborech cookie společnosti Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Moment_Help_Text">[cs]The actual content of the moment consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Research_Analytics_Help_Text">[cs]The actual content of the research and analytics consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Moment_Consent">[cs]I allow Philips to store my data in cloud</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Research_Analytics_Consent">[cs]I allow Philips to use my data for Research and Analytics purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_NO_Order_History">Historie objednávek není k dispozici</string>
  <string name="RA_OK">OK</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Dismiss">[cs]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Shop_Text">[cs]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Support_Text">[cs]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions product informations and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Benefit_Text">Prodlužte svou záruku o 20 měsíců\nZískejte slevu 10 % v obchodě Philips\nZískejte příslušenství k výrobku zdarma</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Email_Text">Na vaši e-mailovou adresu byl zaslán email se smlouvou o prodloužení záruky</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Extentende_Warranty">Vaše záruční doba byla prodloužena do příštího roku</string>
  <string name="RA_Philips_Shop_Menu_Title">Obchod Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_Product_Registration_Text">Registrace výrobku</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title">Dostávat reklamní zprávy společnosti Philips na základě mých preferencí a chování online</string>
  <string name="RA_SettingsScreen_Title">Nastavení účtu</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Login">Přihlásit</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout">Odhlásit</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout_Alert">Opravdu se chcete odhlásit?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_MyAccount">Můj účet</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_OrderHistory">Historie objednávky</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Promo_Question_Text">Co to znamená?</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Purchases">Nákupy</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Screen_Header_Title">Nastavení</string>
  <string name="RA_Skip_Button_Text">Přeskočit</string>
  <string name="RA_SplashScreen_Title">Mobilní aplikace</string>
  <string name="RA_SupportScreen_Title">Podpora</string>
  <string name="RA_Support_Menu_Title">Podpora</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert">Změnit konfiguraci</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert_Msg">Konfiguraci lze změnit pouze při spouštění. Pokud ji chcete změnit, znovu spusťte aplikaci.</string>
  <string name="RA_Update_Userdata_Error">Při aktualizaci uživatelských dat došlo k chybě. Zkuste to znovu později.</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_A">Vertikální nastavení aplikace A</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_B">Vertikální nastavení aplikace B</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_C">Vertikální nastavení aplikace C</string>
  <string name="RA_Warning">UPOZORNĚNÍ</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Text">[cs]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Title">[cs]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Text">[cs]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 Platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Title">[cs]What\'s in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Text">[cs]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Title">[cs]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Text">[cs]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Title">[cs]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Text">[cs]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Title">[cs]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Text">[cs]The Security &amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rules.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Title">[cs]Secure &amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Text">[cs]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Title">[cs]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Text">[cs]Functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Title">[cs]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro">[cs]This app integrates the common components to development new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro_Title">[cs]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_You_are_not_LoggedIn">Nejste přihlášeni. Přejděte do nabídky Nastavení a přihlaste se</string>
  <string name="RA_reference_device_scan">Vyhledávání referenčního zařízení</string>
  <string name="RA_something_wrong">Něco se pokazilo</string>
</resources>
