<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  Copyright (c) Koninklijke Philips N.V., 2018
  All rights are reserved. Reproduction or dissemination
  in whole or in part is prohibited without the prior written
  consent of the copyright holder.
  -->


<resources>
  <string name="BA_Add_Edit_Temp">Προσθήκη ή επεξεργασία θερμοκρασίας </string>
  <string name="BA_AppFramework">Πλαίσιο εφαρμογής </string>
  <string name="BA_HSDP_login_not_available">Η σύνδεση HSDP δεν είναι διαθέσιμη</string>
  <string name="BA_Sync_Settings">Ρυθμίσεις συγχρονισμού</string>
  <string name="RA_AboutScreen_Title">Πληροφορίες</string>
  <string name="RA_About_App_Version">Έκδοση</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Description_New">[el]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_About_Menu_Title">Πληροφορίες</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra">[el]ail : App Infrastructure Library</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_AppInfra_desc">[el]AppInfra is the components top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC">[el]dcc : Consumer Care</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_CC_desc">[el]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_Connectivity">[el]cml : CommLib</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_Connectivity_desc">[el]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_DS">[el]dsc : Data Services</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_DS_desc">[el]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data -\n&lt;ul&gt;&lt;li&gt;Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics.&lt;/li&gt;&lt;/ul&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP">[el]iap : In-app Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_IAP_desc">[el]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR">[el]prg : Product Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_PR_desc">[el]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UIKIT">[el]uit : Mobile UI Toolkit Non DLS</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UIKIT_desc">[el]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application.</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR">[el]usr : User Registration</string>
  <string name="RA_COCO_UR_desc">[el]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization social media specific credentials.</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsDescription">[el]\"Special offers, promotions and first hand information about new product releases.\nTailored for you!\n\nJoin 140.000 of your peers now!\"</string>
  <string name="RA_CSW_JustInTime_UserBenefitsTitle">[el]What do we have to offer?</string>
  <string name="RA_Cancel">Ακύρωση</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_AppInfra">[el]AppInfra is the component\'s top level module. It gathers all the modules delivered by the AppInfra Common Component into one single structure. AppInfra facilitates dependency injection into common components and other software pieces that make use of the AppInfra functionalities.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_Connectivity">[el]Connectivity feature in Reference App, provides the ability to pair the mobile application with a reference device using Bluetooth capability for capturing the data from the device to the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ConsumerCare">[el]Whenever users find any difficulty in using the app, they can use the Consumer Care feature to get the issues resolved. The app provides a number of ways the users can access Consumer Care support, such as live chat, e-mail, call, tweet, Facebook post, and so on.</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_DataServices">[el]Data Services is a common component that acts as a gateway to data core. It will provide synchronization with application data base for the below support the following types of data: Moments, Consents, Insights, Push notification and user characteristics</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_InAppPurchase">[el]In App Purchase feature in Reference App, provides the ability to buy products from the app for the users, which would give users the convenience of shopping anytime-anywhere. This approach also will boost marketing and sales</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_ProductRegistration">[el]Product registration is a common component, which facilitates the user to create/login into My Philips account and Register a Normal Product where by providing CTN Number, Serial Number(Mandatory) and Date of Purchase</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UIToolkit">[el]UI Toolkit is a component that provides UI controls that are present in the designs provided by the design team on all the screens of the mobile application</string>
  <string name="RA_CoCo_Description_UserRegistration">[el]User registration feature in Reference App provides the ability of registering a new user accessing the mobile application, for logging into the application using valid organization / social media specific credentials</string>
  <string name="RA_Coco_Version">[el]App Info</string>
  <string name="RA_ConnectivityScreen_Title">Συνδεσιμότητα</string>
  <string name="RA_DLSS_avatar_default_text">[el]Hello User, \nPlease sign in.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Philips_Shop">[el]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_Help_Support_screen_sub">[el]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions, product information and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_copyright">[el]Copyright \u00A9 2017 Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_description">[el]This reference app is the starting point for any new patient medical or consumer mobile app. It is made up of configurable common components which are all part of the CDP2 Platform. It will help accelerate your app development, harmonize UX across Philips and ensures appropriate integration with HSDP.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_privacy">[el]Privacy policy</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_about_terms">[el]Terms &amp;amp;amp; conditions</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_check_internet_connectivity">[el]Check Internet Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_data_fetch_error">[el]Not able to fetch data</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_data_fetch_wait">[el]Wait..While we fetch your sleep data from device</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_enable_bluetooth">[el]Please enable bluetooth</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_healthy_sleep_title">[el]Healthy Sleep Score</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_sub_text">[el]ReferenceApp is a base platform used by all propositions to develop and maintain features both generic and specific to the propositions. App infra, Data Gateway, App FWK, and UIToolkit allow Apps to be created from uApps and UI-less services/libraries. ReferenceApp acts as a foundation over which CDP2 uApps and proposition specific uApps are integrated to form individual apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_home_page_text">[el]Reference App</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_insights_error">[el]Error loading Insights</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_no_internet_connectivity">[el]Internet connection is not available</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_sub_text">[el]This app integrates the common components required to develop new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen1_title">[el]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_sub_text">[el]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen2_title">[el]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_sub_text">[el]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen3_title">[el]What is in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_sub_text">[el]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen4_title">[el]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_sub_text">[el]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen5_title">[el]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_sub_text">[el]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen6_title">[el]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_sub_text">[el]The Security &amp;amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rule.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen7_title">[el]Secure &amp;amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_sub_text">[el]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen8_title">[el]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_sub_text">[el]&lt;html&gt;The CDP&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;2&lt;small&gt;&amp;amp;&lt;sup&gt; platform is fully integrated with HSDP and IT to ensure all functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_onboarding_screen9_title">[el]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_overlay_got_it">[el]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_actual">[el]Actual</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_connectivity">[el]PowerSleep Connectivity</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_deep_sleep_title">[el]Time spent in deep sleep</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_default_data">[el]--</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_ideal_deep_sleep">[el](Ideal 120 mins)</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_ideal_sleep_time">[el](Ideal 450-540 mins)</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_percentage_label">[el]of 100</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_power_sleep_time_sleep">[el]Time asleep</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_ps_tips_title">[el]Tips</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_sleep_element">[el]Sleep element</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_splash_title">[el]&lt;html&gt;&lt;b&gt;CDP&lt;sup&gt;&lt;small&gt;2&lt;/small&gt;&lt;/sup&gt;&lt;/b&gt; Reference App&lt;/html&gt;</string>
  <string name="RA_DLS_theme_title">[el]Theme Setting</string>
  <string name="RA_Demo_Menu_Title">[el]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_Done_Button_Text">Πραγμ</string>
  <string name="RA_Empty_Invalid_Data">Το πεδίο δεδομένων είναι κενό ή έχει μη έγκυρη τιμή</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Body_Text">Ειδική υπόθεση, το μεγάλο κείμενο μπαίνει στο σώμα κειμένου </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Header_Text">Ειδική υπόθεση - Ο τίτλος μπαίνει εδώ </string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Menu_Title">Αρχική οθόνη εφαρμογής για κινητά</string>
  <string name="RA_HomeScreen_Title">Αρχική οθόνη εφαρμογής για κινητά</string>
  <string name="RA_Invalid_Param_Msg">Εισαγάγατε ή επιλέξατε μη έγκυρες τιμές παραμέτρου. Επιλέξτε τις κατάλληλες τιμές παραμέτρου και ξεκινήστε ξανά</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Binary_Hosting_Consent">[el]I allow Philips to store binary data</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Click_Stream_Hosting_Consent">[el]I allow Philips to use my mobile application usage statistics</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Coaching_Consent">[el]I allow Philips to use my data for Coaching purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Binary_Help_Text">[el]The actual content of the binary consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream">Επιτρέπω στην Philips να συλλέγει τα δεδομένα της εφαρμογής μου προς όφελος της λειτουργίας της εφαρμογής, για τη βελτίωση της εφαρμογής, για την εξατομίκευση της εφαρμογής, για την ενσωμάτωση στα μέσα κοινωνικής δικτύωσης και για την προβολή σχετικού περιεχομένου και διαφήμισης.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Click_Stream_Help_Text">Πολιτική για τα cookies\n\nΑυτή η Εφαρμογή χρησιμοποιεί την Adobe Analytics, μια υπηρεσία αναλύσεων (\"Adobe Analytics\") που παρέχεται από την Adobe Systems Software Ireland Limited (\"Adobe\"). Η Adobe Analytics χρησιμοποιεί \"cookies\" ή παρόμοιες τεχνικές, που αποτελούν αρχεία κειμένου τοποθετημένα στην Εφαρμογή σας, έτσι ώστε να βοηθήσουν την Εφαρμογή να αναλύσει τα γενικά μοτίβα κυκλοφορίας μέσω της Εφαρμογής σας. Με τη μετάδοση των πληροφοριών που προκύπτουν από τα cookies σχετικά με την χρήση της Εφαρμογής στην Adobe, η ρύθμιση εξασφαλίζει ότι η διεύθυνση IP γίνεται ανώνυμη πριν από τον γεωγραφικό εντοπισμό και αντικαθίσταται από μια γενική διεύθυνση IP πριν από την αποθήκευση. Εκ μέρους της Philips, η Adobe θα χρησιμοποιεί τις πληροφορίες για την αξιολόγηση της χρήσης της Εφαρμογής από εσάς, συγκεντρώνοντας αναφορές για τη δραστηριότητα της Εφαρμογής για την Philips και με σκοπό να παρέχει άλλες υπηρεσίες που σχετίζονται με τη δραστηριότητα της εφαρμογής και τη χρήση της Εφαρμογής στην Philips. Η Adobe δεν συσχετίζει τη διεύθυνση σας IP με άλλα δεδομένα που διατηρεί η Adobe. Μπορείτε να αποφύγετε τη συλλογή και χρήση των δεδομένων από την Adobe και τη Philips (cookies και διεύθυνση IP), αν επιλέξετε να εξαιρεθείτε, αφού κλείσετε αυτήν την οθόνη.\n</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Coaching_Help_Text">[el]The actual content of the coaching consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Marketing_Help_Text">Ως αποτέλεσμα της συναίνεσής σας, οι εταιρείες του ομίλου Philips ενδέχεται να επικοινωνήσουν μαζί σας για προωθητικούς σκοπούς μέσω email, SMS ή άλλων καναλιών ψηφιακής επικοινωνίας, όπως εφαρμογές κινητού και μέσα κοινωνικής δικτύωσης. Για να μπορέσουμε να προσαρμόσουμε την επικοινωνία μας σύμφωνα με τις προτιμήσεις και τη συμπεριφορά σας και για να σας παρέχουμε την καλύτερη δυνατή, εξατομικευμένη εμπειρία, ενδέχεται να αναλύσουμε και να συνδυάσουμε τα προσωπικά σας δεδομένα. Τα δεδομένα αυτά ενδέχεται να περιλαμβάνουν τα εξής: \n\nΔεδομένα που μας παρέχετε εσείς\nΔεδομένα που θέλετε να μοιραστείτε μαζί μας, όπως το ονοματεπώνυμό σας, η ημερομηνία γέννησης ή η ηλικία σας, η διεύθυνση email, η φυσική σας διεύθυνση, η χώρα, το φύλο, το τηλέφωνό σας και το προφίλ σας σε μέσα κοινωνικής δικτύωσης.\n\nΔεδομένα που λαμβάνουμε από τις αλληλεπιδράσεις σας με την Philips\nΔεδομένα σχετικά με την αλληλεπίδρασή σας και τη χρήση των καναλιών ψηφιακής επικοινωνίας της Philips, όπως μέσα κοινωνικής δικτύωσης, διαδικτυακές τοποθεσίες, email, εφαρμογές και συνδεδεμένα προϊόντα. Τα δεδομένα αυτά ενδέχεται να περιέχουν τις εξής πληροφορίες: διεύθυνση IP, cookies, στοιχεία συσκευής, μηνύματα με δυνατότητα αλληλεπίδρασης με κλικ, στοιχεία τοποθεσίας και διαδικτυακές τοποθεσίες που επισκέπτεστε\n\nΗ Philips σας δίνει την επιλογή να άρετε την συναίνεσή σας, οποιαδήποτε στιγμή.\nΓια περισσότερες πληροφορίες, διαβάστε τη Δήλωση ιδιωτικού απορρήτου της Philips και την Πολιτική για τα cookies της Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Moment_Help_Text">[el]The actual content of the moment consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Consent_Research_Analytics_Help_Text">[el]The actual content of the research and analytics consent help text here</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Moment_Consent">[el]I allow Philips to store my data in cloud</string>
  <string name="RA_MYA_Research_Analytics_Consent">[el]I allow Philips to use my data for Research and Analytics purposes</string>
  <string name="RA_Menu_title_Demo">[el]Test Demo Apps</string>
  <string name="RA_NO_Order_History">Μη διαθέσιμο ιστορικό παραγγελίας</string>
  <string name="RA_OK">ΟΚ</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Dismiss">[el]Got it</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Shop_Text">[el]You can make Philips purchases or via 3rd party retailers here.</string>
  <string name="RA_Overlay_Support_Text">[el]You can contact Philips consumer care here. Consumer Care is the destination for all Philips questions product informations and reviews.</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Benefit_Text">Επεκτείνετε την εγγύησή σας για 24 μήνες.\nΛάβετε έκπτωση 10% στη Philips.\nΛάβετε δωρεάν αξεσουάρ προϊόντων</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Email_Text">Ένα email σχετικά με το συμβόλαιο επέκτασης της εγγύησης εστάλη στη διεύθυνση email σας</string>
  <string name="RA_PR_Extentende_Warranty">Η περίοδος της εγγύησης επεκτάθηκε μέχρι τον επόμενο χρόνο</string>
  <string name="RA_Philips_Shop_Menu_Title">Κατάστημα Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_Product_Registration_Text">Δηλώστε το προϊόν σας</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_ACTIVATE_SCREEN_LOCK">[el]Activate screenlock</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_DONT_SHOW_MESSAGE">[el]Do not show this message again</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[el]We’ve detected that you have rooted the device or jailbroken, thereby making it easier for others to access your data and no security on your application data.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_NO_THANKS">[el]No thanks</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_PASSCODE_AND_JAILBREAK_VIOLATION">[el]We’ve detected that you have jailbroken and not activated screenlock, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SCREEN_LOCK">[el]We’ve detected the screenlock of your mobile phone is to enabled, thereby making it easier for others to access your data. We recommend enabling your screenlock.</string>
  <string name="RA_SECURITY_SECURE_YOUR_DATA">[el]Secure your data</string>
  <string name="RA_See_a_doctor_Menu_Title">[el]See a doctor</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title">Λήψη προωθητικών επικοινωνιών από την Philips, με βάση τις προτιμήσεις και την ηλεκτρονική συμπεριφορά μου</string>
  <string name="RA_Setting_Philips_Promo_Title_Only">[el]Receive Philips</string>
  <string name="RA_SettingsScreen_Title">Ρυθμίσεις λογαριασμού</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Login">Σύνδεση</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout">Έξοδος</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Logout_Alert">Είστε βέβαιοι ότι θέλετε να αποσυνδεθείτε;</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_MyAccount">Ο λογαριασμός μου</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_OrderHistory">Ιστορικό παραγγελίας</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Promo_Question_Text">Τι σημαίνει αυτό;</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Purchases">Αγορές</string>
  <string name="RA_Settings_Screen_Header_Title">Ρυθμίσεις</string>
  <string name="RA_Skip_Button_Text">Παράλειψη</string>
  <string name="RA_SplashScreen_Title">Εφαρμογές για κινητά</string>
  <string name="RA_SupportScreen_Title">Υποστήριξη</string>
  <string name="RA_Support_Menu_Title">Υποστήριξη</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert">Αλλαγή διαμόρφωσης</string>
  <string name="RA_UR_Env_Alert_Msg">Η διαμόρφωση μπορεί να αλλάξει μόνο κατά τη στιγμή της έναρξης. Πρέπει να ξεκινήσετε ξανά την εφαρμογή για να την αλλάξετε</string>
  <string name="RA_Update_Userdata_Error">Προέκυψε σφάλμα κατά την ενημέρωση των δεδομένων χρήστη. Δοκιμάστε ξανά μετά από λίγη ώρα</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_A">Ρύθμιση A για κάθετη εφαρμογή</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_B">Ρύθμιση B για κάθετη εφαρμογή</string>
  <string name="RA_Vertical_App_Setting_C">Ρύθμιση C για κάθετη εφαρμογή</string>
  <string name="RA_Warning">ΠΡΟΕΙΔΟΠΟΙΗΣΗ</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Text">[el]Designers, developers and business leaders across Philips.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen1_Title">[el]Who is it for?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Text">[el]Reference App comprises all of the configurable common components that are part of the CDP2 Platform.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen2_Title">[el]What\'s in it?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Text">[el]It provides all the reference information and tools needed to accelerate and harmonize UX development and ensure appropriate HSDP integration.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen3_Title">[el]What does it do?</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Text">[el]The UX has been fully approved by Philips Design and will soon be in DLS.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen4_Title">[el]Fully DLS compliant</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Text">[el]The complete platform is tagged and delivers data to monitor &amp;amp; improve your proposition.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen5_Title">[el]Analyze to perform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Text">[el]The Security &amp;amp; Privacy actions of the complete platform are fully in line with Philips rules.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen6_Title">[el]Secure &amp;amp; personal</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Text">[el]Localization of your proposition is enabled by the platform, including China.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen7_Title">[el]A global platform</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Text">[el]Functionalities are enabled end-2-end within the Philips landscape.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen8_Title">[el]Integrated with HSDP &amp;amp; IT</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro">[el]This app integrates the common components to development new IoT solutions for acceleration across Philips. It is the first reference for the development of all new patient medical or consumer mobile apps.</string>
  <string name="RA_WelcomeScreen_Intro_Title">[el]What is Reference App?</string>
  <string name="RA_You_are_not_LoggedIn">Δεν είστε συνδεδεμένοι. Μεταβείτε στις Ρυθμίσεις και έπειτα Σύνδεση.</string>
  <string name="RA_change_config_desc">[el]Configuration can only be changed at launch time. You need to relaunch the app to change it.</string>
  <string name="RA_loading_articles">[el]Loading Article</string>
  <string name="RA_reference_device_scan">Σάρωση συσκευής αναφοράς</string>
  <string name="RA_something_wrong">Παρουσιάστηκε κάποιο πρόβλημα</string>
  <string name="chapters">[el]Chapters</string>
  <string name="common_components">[el]Common Components</string>
  <string name="description_close">[el]Close</string>
  <string name="label_last_synced">[el]Last updated: %1$s</string>
  <string name="label_last_synced_default">[el]Last updated: No update yet</string>
  <string name="label_sleep_time_format">[el]%d mins</string>
  <string name="label_sleep_tips">[el]How can I improve my sleep score?</string>
  <string name="mya_config_tab">[el]Configuration tab</string>
</resources>
