<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Used the following tool to add line breaks http://textmechanic.com/Add-Remove-Line-Breaks.html -->
    <string name="eula_text"> <![CDATA[
Philips Smart Air App – Conditions of use\n\nIn order to use the full functionality of the App, you will need to create an account and register with the help of the App offered to you by [INSERT ENTITY & ADDRESS] ("Philips"). The App will guide you through this process automatically when required. When you only use the outdoor air quality and weather functionality of the App, no registration is required\nWe welcome you to use this App for your personal entertainment, there are just a few rules and restrictions we ask you to keep in mind!\nWhat this App does for you: [SELECT APPLICABLE OPTIONS, OR ADD NEW OPTIONS]\n1. It allows you to manage certain aspects and functions of your Connected Product remotely\n2. It allows transmission of certain information and notifications from and between your App and Connected Product to Philips and vice versa \n3. Provide you with information on Philips connected air purifier products and accessories.\n4. Provide you with your indoor air quality data and  local cities’ AQI and weather data\n5. Offer you the newest updates on our products, competitions and other news related to Philips\nWe encourage you to read on; by using the App, you accept the terms as mentioned below.\n\nOther things you should know about this App:\n\nPrivacy: please see Privacy Policy in this document\n\nLicense:  You may use this App in connection with the Connected Product related services (for which you need to subscribe separately, and subject to the terms for these services),  on an Apple device owned or controlled by you. This license is non- transferable and is between you and Philips, and also covers the software embedded in the Connected Product (and any updates thereto) \n\nThird parties: It is possible that when you use this App you will (also) use a service, download a piece of software, or purchase goods that are provided by a third party. Please know that those third parties may have their own applicable rules and restrictions, separate from these conditions of use.\n\nWarranties: Our goal is to provide you with a great App and a great App user experience. Do know that we are only able to provide you the App "as-is". Although we would like to, we unfortunately cannot warrant anything about the App or its content. \n\nLiability: As much faith as we have in our App, there is always the possibility that things don\'t work as they are supposed to. In the unfortunate event that the App would not work or any content may be lost, please accept our sincerest apologies. We certainly understand that it is unfortunate and inconvenient. In the event of any failure of the App to conform to any applicable warranty provided herein, you may notify Apple, and Apple will refund the purchase price for the App to you. Unfortunately, to the maximum extent permitted by applicable law, we cannot accept any liability for any damages incurred as a result of your use of the App. IN ANY EVENT WE ARE NOT LIABLE FOR AMOUNTS EXCEEDING THE FEES PAID IN CONNECTION WITH THE APP. \n\nJurisdiction: These conditions of use shall be construed, interpreted and governed by the laws of the Netherlands without regard to conflicts of law provisions thereof.\nSole point of contact: Apple is not responsible for the App nor its content. Therefore you should contact Philips via [insert email and telephone number] for any questions, support, product claims and third party intellectual property claims related to this App.\n\nFinally: You represent and warrant that (i) you are not located in a country that is subject to a U.S. Government embargo, or that has been designated by the U.S. Government as a “terrorist supporting” country; and (ii) you are not listed on any U.S. Government list of prohibited or restricted parties. Also you irrevocably grant Apple the right (who will be deemed to have accepted that right) to enforce these conditions against you as a third party beneficiary thereof.\n\nHave fun!
]]>
    </string>
</resources>
