<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Used the following tool to add line breaks http://textmechanic.com/Add-Remove-Line-Breaks.html -->
    <string name="privacy_policy_text"> <![CDATA[
PRIVACY POLICY PHILIPS SMART AIR PURIFIER\n\nThis privacy policy governs your use of the software application Smart Air Purifier App (“Application”) for mobile devices that was created by Philips. The Application is measures indoor air particle level as measured by the Philips smart air purifier, lets you control the smart air purifier via the app, and displays outdoor air quality based upon your location. \n\nThe Philips Smart Air Purifier uses Philips VitaShield IPS filtration technology that is proven to act on many of the causes of unhealthy air in the home. Its multi-layer filter system diminishes airborne particles like pollen, PM 2.5, viruses, bacteria, and TVOCs like toluene.\n\nThe Smart Air Purifier measures particles ≥1.0 um. Particles larger than one micron gives an indication on the particle level in you room where the smart air purifier is placed. The sensor detects a part of the amount of particles belonging to PM2.5. Particle Matter (PM) is represented by mass, the current sensor counts particles \n\n\nIf 1-2 for one hour our longer, then the PM2.5 level is expected to be lower than the Chinese AQI standard of outdoor air of 75 micro gram per cubic meter\n\nIf level above 2 for one hour our longer, then PM2.5 is expected to be higher than the Chinese AQI standard of outdoor air of 75 micro grams per cubic meter.\n\nThere is no standard for PM2.5 indoor, therefore there is no indoor PM2.5 level shown. Philips measures both indoor and outdoor PM2.5 levels, there is a correlation between outdoor and indoor air quality, the higher the level of PM2.5 indoors is strongly correlated to the PM2.5 level outdoors. \n\n\nWhat information does the Application obtain and how is it used?\n\nUser Provided Information \n\nThe Application obtains the information you provide when you download and register the Application. Registration with us is optional. However, please keep in mind that you may not be able to use some of the features offered by the Application unless you register with us (for example setting up the smart air puriifer or controlling the smart air purifier)\n\nWhen you register with us and use the Application, you generally provide (a) your name, email address, password and smart air purifier (s) you are are using; (b) air particle level as measured by the smart air purifier in the location where it is placed and details of when the air purifier is operated, at what fan speeds and when filters need to be replaced (c) transaction-related information, such as when you make purchases or respond to any offers, or download or use applications from us, or when you share air quality information via social media; (d) information you provide us when you contact us for help; (e) information you enter into our system when using the Application, such as name of the smart air purifer or number of smart air purifiers or users.\n\nWe may also use the information you provided us to contact your from time to time to provide you with important information, required notices. We may contact you for marketing promotions if we have received your consent for this.  \n\nAutomatically Collected Information \n\nIn addition, the Application will collect certain information automatically, including, but not limited to, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile devices unique device ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use, and information about the way you use the Application. Next to that we collect the connection and disconnection timestamps, IP address of air purifier, and gateway (i.e. router), MAC addresses of app and air purifier, software, app and firmware versions.\n\nWe collect this data for research purposes and/or to provide you with useful tips, both to improve the performance of the air purifier.\n\nDoes the Application collect precise real time location information of the device?\n\nWhen you visit the mobile application, we may use GPS technology (or other similar technology) to determine your current location in order to determine the city you are located within and display a location map with relevant air quality information and where your smart air purifier(s) is (are) located. In order to provide you with weather data and outdoor air quality data based on your location, the information is shared with thrid parties. Our agreements with these third parties will limit the purposes for which your personal data can be used and disclosed, and will require your personal data to be adequately safeguarded. We will not sell your Personal Data to third parties for their own purposes. \n\nIf you do not want us to use your location for the purposes set forth above, you should turn off the location services for the mobile application located in your account settings or in your mobile phone settings and/or within the mobile application. \n\nDo third parties see and/or have access to information obtained by the Application?\n\nYes. We will share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement.\n\nWe may disclose User Provided and Automatically Collected Information:\n\n•	as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process;\n\n•	when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request;\n\n•	with our trusted services providers who work on our behalf, do not have an independent use of the information we disclose to them, and have agreed to adhere to the rules set forth in this privacy statement.\n\n•	if Philips is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of this information, as well as any choices you may have regarding this information.\n\n Cloud\n\nPhilips may store your personal data in a cloud. This means that your personal data may be processed on behalf of Philips by a cloud service provider and could be stored in different locations around the world. Philips has implemented organizational and contractual measures to protect your personal data and to impose security and privacy requirements on our cloud services providers, including requirements that your personal data are exclusively processed for the purposes mentioned above.\n\nWhat are my opt-out rights?\n\nYou can stop all collection of information easily by disconnecting the smart air purifier from the internet and uninstalling the Application. You can turn-off the wi-fi function of the smart air purifier and no data will be collected any longer. You may use the standard app uninstall processes as may be available as part of your mobile device or via the mobile application marketplace or network. \n\nData Retention Policy, Managing Your Information\n\nWe will retain User Provided data for as long as you use the Application and for a reasonable time thereafter. We will retain Automatically Collected information for up to 1 year and thereafter may store it in aggregate and will be anonymized. If you’d like us to delete User Provided Data that you have provided via the Application, please contact us at airpurifier-support@philips.comand we will respond in a reasonable time. Please note that some or all of the User Provided Data may be required in order for the Application to function properly.\n\n\nChildren\n\nWe do not use the Application to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should contact us at airpurifier-support@philips.com. We will delete such information from our files within a reasonable time.\n\n\nSecurity\n\nWe are concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your information. We provide physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect information we process and maintain. For example, we limit access to this information to authorized employees and contractors who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our Application. Please be aware that, although we endeavor provide reasonable security for information we process and maintain, no security system can prevent all potential security breaches.\n\n\nChanges\n\nThis Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy in the app. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes, as continued use is deemed approval of all changes. You can check the history of this policy by consulting the app.\n\nContact us\n\nIf you have any questions regarding privacy while using the Application, or have questions about our practices, please contact us via:\n\nTelephone: 4008 800 008\n\nWeChat: ID:飞利浦优质生活，  Signal: philipslifestyle\n\n\nYour Consent\n\nBy using the Application, you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. "Processing,” means using cookies on a computer/hand held device or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information, all of which activities will take place in the China. If you reside outside the China your information will be transferred, processed and stored there under China privacy standards. \n\n\nBy clicking I accept, I consent to the collection of data as described above. \n\n 
]]>
    </string>
</resources>
