<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <!-- Used the following tool to add line breaks http://textmechanic.com/Add-Remove-Line-Breaks.html -->
    <string name="privacy_policy_text"> 
<b>PRIVACY NOTICE PHILIPS SMART AIR PURIFIER</b> \n\n\n Royal Philips N.V. (\"Philips\") strongly beliefs in protecting the privacy of the personal data you share with us. Please read this Privacy Notice carefully as it informs you how Philips uses and protects your personal data and about choices you have about how your personal data is used.\n\n This privacy notice governs your use of the software application Smart Air Purifier App (\"Application\") for mobile devices that was created by Philips. The Application measures indoor air particle level as measured by the Philips Smart Air Purifier, lets you control the smart air purifier via the app, and displays outdoor air quality based upon your location. \n\n The Philips Smart Air Purifier uses Philips VitaShield IPS filtration technology that is proven to act on many of the causes of unhealthy air in the home. Its multi-layer filter system diminishes airborne particles like pollen, PM 2.5, viruses, bacteria, and TVOCs like toluene.\n\n <b>What information does the Application obtain and how is it used?</b>\n\n Philips is committed to making your use of the App the best possible experience. One way to achieve this is by using tracking mechanisms to store information about your use of the App. This information is necessary to allow the App to operate properly. We feel that it is very important that you know what cookies our App uses and for what purposes. This will help protect your privacy, while ensuring our App’s user-friendliness as much as possible. \n\n All our Philips apps make use of Adobe Sitecatalyst cookies to gain insight in the usage of the app on a purely aggregated basis. \n\n\n <b>Cookies that ensure that the App functions properly</b>\n\n These cookies are necessary to make it possible to surf the Philips App(s) and use the Apps functions, such as accessing protected areas of the App. Without these cookies, such functions are not possible.\n\n Our App uses cookies for:\n\n 1. Remembering information that you fill in on the various pages so that you dont have to fill in all your details repeatedly.\n 2. Passing on information from one page to the next, for instance if a long survey is being filled in. \n 3. Storing preferences such as language, location, the number of search results to be displayed etc.\n 4. Storing settings for optimal video display, such as buffer size and your screens resolution details.\n 5. Reading your browser settings so that we can display our App optimally on your screen.\n 6. Locating misuse of our App and services, for example by recording several consecutive failed log-in attempts.\n 7. Loading the App evenly so that it remains accessible.\n 8. Offering the option of storing log-in details so that you dont have to enter them every time.\n 9. Making it possible to place a reaction on our App.\n\n <b>Cookies that enable us to measure App usage</b>\n\n These cookies gather information about the surfing behaviour of visitors to our Apps, such as which pages are visited often and whether visitors receive error messages. By doing this we are able to make the structure, navigation and content of the App as user-friendly as possible for you. We do not link the statistics and other reports to people. We use cookies for:\n\n 1. Keeping track of the number of visitors to our web pages.\n 2. Keeping track of the length of time that each visitor spends on our web pages. \n 3. Determining the order in which a visitor visits the various pages on our App. \n 4. Assessing which parts of our site need to be improved. \n 5. Optimizing the App. \n\n For these purposes as mentioned above we process session and usage data as well as log data. Session and usage data is information about your use of the App. It includes connection and service-related data such as information relating to the connection request, server communication and data sharing, network measurements, quality of service, and date, time and location of the App. Log data includes your unique User Device number, the IP address of your device, the type of mobile internet browser or operating system you use, the identity of the phone (i.e. the name of the phone), browsing history, and/or the dates and times of your use of the App. \n\n\n <b>Does the Application collect precise real time location information of the device?</b>\n\n When you give us your prior explicit consent for using your location data, we may use GPS technology (or other similar technology) to determine your current location in order to determine the city you are located within and display a location map with relevant air quality information and where your smart air purifier(s) is (are) located. In order to provide you with weather data and outdoor air quality data based on your location, the information is shared with third parties. Our agreements with these third parties will limit the purposes for which your personal data can be used and disclosed, and will require your personal data to be adequately safeguarded. We will not sell your Personal Data to third parties for their own purposes. \n\n If you do not want us to use your location for the purposes set forth above, you should change your privacy setting by turning off the location services for the mobile application located in your account settings within the mobile application. \n\n <b>Do third parties see and/or have access to information obtained by the Application?</b>\n\n Yes. We will share your information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy notice. \n\n We may disclose User Provided and Automatically Collected Information: \n\n • as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process; \n\n • when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request; \n\n • with our trusted services providers who work on our behalf, do not have an independent use of the information we disclose to them, and have agreed to adhere to the rules set forth in this privacy notice. \n\n • if Philips is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Website of any change in ownership or uses of this information, as well as any choices you may have regarding this information. \n\n You can stop all collection of information easily by disconnecting the Smart Air Purifier from the internet and uninstalling the Application. You can turn-off the wi-fi function of the Smart Air Purifier and no data will be collected any longer. You may use the standard Application uninstall processes as may be available as part of your mobile device or via the mobile application marketplace or network. \n\n <b>Data Retention Policy, Managing Your Information</b>\n\n We will retain User Provided data for as long as you use the Application and for a reasonable time thereafter. We will retain Automatically Collected information for up to 1 year and thereafter may store it in aggregate and will be anonymized. If you’d like us to delete User Provided Data that you have provided via the Application, please contact us at <a href="privacy@philips.com">privacy@philips.com</a>. Please note that some or all of the User Provided Data may be required in order for the Application to function properly. \n\n\n <b>Children</b>\n\n We do not use the Application to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of 18. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should contact us at <a href="privacy@philips.com">privacy@philips.com</a>. We will delete such information from our files within a reasonable time. \n\n <b>Service Provider</b>\n\n Your personal data which qualifies as ‘private affairs data’ under Chinese Civil Code collected and processed in connection with the operation of the Smart Air Purifier is done by a Chinese service provider. This means that such data will not be transferred to other countries without your prior written consent. Philips has implemented organizational and contractual measures to protect your personal data and to impose the same legal requirements on our service providers, including requirements that your personal data are exclusively processed for the purposes of as mentioned above. \n\n Certain other personal data, such as analytics data, device identifiers and aggregated data related to your usage of the app that is collected through cookies and tags may be processed by service providers outside of China. \n\n <b>Security</b>\n\n We are concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your information. We provide physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect information we process and maintain. For example, we limit access to this information to authorized employees and contractors who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our Application. Please be aware that, although we take appropriate organizational and technical security measures to protect misuse and loss of information we process and maintain, no security system can prevent all potential security breaches. \n\n\n <b>Changes</b>\n\n The services that Philips provides are always evolving and the form and nature of the services that Philips provides may change from time to time without prior notice to you. For this reason, we reserve the right to change or add provisions to this Privacy Notice from time to time. We will notify you of any changes to our Privacy Notice by posting the new Privacy Notice in the App. We encourage you to check back often to review the latest version. \n\n The new Privacy Notice will be effective upon posting, if you do not agree to the revised notice, you should alter your preferences, or consider stop using the App. The most recent version shall supersede any and all other versions of this Privacy Notice. By continuing to access or make use of our services after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Notice. \n\n <b>Contact us</b>\n\n If you have any questions, complaints or suggestions about this Privacy Notice or your experiences with the App. please contact us at <a href="privacy@philips.com">privacy@philips.com</a>.\n\n
    </string>
</resources>
